{
  "1": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Region of Central Greece?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?population WHERE { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Central_Greece_(region)> y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population }",
    "Answer": "570922^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "2": {
    "Question": "Where is the Dorset county located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?wkt WHERE { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dorset> geo:hasGeometry ?geo. ?geo geo:asWKT ?wkt }",
    "Answer": "http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/Geometry_gadm_GBR.1.28_1                                                   http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/Geometry_OS_14362"
  },
  "3": {
    "Question": "Where is Lough Ramor located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?wkt WHERE { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lough_Ramor> geo:hasGeometry ?geo. ?geo geo:asWKT ?wkt }",
    "Answer": "http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/Geometry_osm_ee9e8c3b-6926-3073-a78b-6f95151fba98"
  },
  "4": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Moschato Tavros Municipality?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population WHERE {             yago:Moschato-Tavros y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population     }",
    "Answer": "population 38116^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "5": {
    "Question": "Where is Oxfordshire located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?WKT WHERE {             yago:Oxfordshire geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT. }",
    "Answer": "WKT <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-1.1023016 51.50300217,-1.10958195 5...   more <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-1.6028258490004 51.5182943464847,-1...   more"
  },
  "6": {
    "Question": "What is the area of County Galway?",
    "Query": "SELECT (strdf:area(?WKT) AS ?area) WHERE {         yago:County_Galway geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT    }",
    "Answer": "area 0.006825249642133713^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "7": {
    "Question": "Where is Liverpool located?",
    "Query": "select ?geoWKT where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Liverpool> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-1.26022720336914 51.8016967773438,- -1.26052832603449 51.7833938598634,-1.22436201572413 51.7645225524902,-1.20710623264313 51.7697334289551,-1.20545148849482 51.7417640686036,-1.1946592330932 51.7456855773926,-1.20810759067535 51.7124938964843,-1.24642372131342 51.7172164916993,-1.24862349033344 51.7247428894044,-1.26774263381952 51.7355117797852,-1.30186176300049 51.7477035522462,-1.3123824596405 51.7610778808595,-1.30241978168482 51.7916450500489,-1.27115225791931 51.7901153564454,-1.26022720336914 51.8016967773438))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral> <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-1.30368765335028 51.7726313487459,- -1.30371817328995 51.7727214156925,-1.3038751904235 51.773156585654,-1.3040986565148 51.7739878277706,-1.30415664479278 51.7743666817804,-1.30419765366075 51.7748084455203,-1.30421616781215 51.7750188887965,-1.3042472325809 51.7753535391645,-1.30424490998843 51.7755046241387,-1.3042355638434 51.7762058609863,-1.30421651301985 51.7765977419684,-1.30418934977582 51.7768565433744,-1.30411576277226 51.7772121471671,-1.3040589420515 51.7774177401921,-1.30395067571502 51.7777668466077,-1.30362056419325 51.7787781792366,-1.30346431810538 51.7792313588685,-1.30334149977221 51.7795857716237,-1.30306339243287 51.780229686274,-1.30283943891876 51.7806473182831,-1.3029958398343 51.7806581327213,-1.30283762016683 51.7809593022663,-1.30269676643175 51.7809710513286,-1.30251540069169 51.781269386619,-1.30255459059867 51.7812624281276,-1.30260969758177 51.7812618560323,-1.30268329028667 51.7812793707359,-1.30265944089404 51.7813223746752,-1.30260021162889 51.7813112371547,-1.3024182740348 51.7813596854687,-1.30207324317011 51.7819240110243,-1.30169257297028 51.7824504616606,-1.30130562524749 51.7829184477775,-1.30112682176446 51.7831349098463,-1.30089109104051 51.7833843810244,-1.30031449040251 51.7839186509799,-1.30014342519283 51.7840129124811,-1.30021089543472 51.7840555603924,-1.30023385897097 51.7840700787912,-1.30020730420423 51.7841022797944,-1.30018134717744 51.7840958333279,-1.30015096809261 51.7840893605436,-1.29962343065823 51.7845493135567,-1.29904953885113 51.7850071003426,-1.2981916794348 51.7856313671406,-1.29761267681617 51.7860469598282,-1.29759503148072 51.7860594385049,-1.2972732192842 51.7862462770116,-1.29728504506999 51.7863237395744,-1.2972821486422 51.7863255199912,-1.2972858371425 51.7863650919001,-1.29722580681984 51.7864051819687,-1.29715334115325 51.7863993558022,-1.29701439990705 51.7863868402757,-1.29698809287416 51.786402862535,-1.29606862026532 51.7869809036485,-1.29583793580351 51.7870873861092,-1.29547130674191 51.7872650526487,-1.29483873438891 51.7875714587552,-1.29385717419734 51.7880420560337,-1.29335278860394 51.7883060783473,-1.29313078835692 51.7884144053962,-1.29292336077354 51.7885157186315,-1.29264422480695 51.7886542625402,-1.29256964717435 51.7886915661647,-1.2922320797243 51.7888667008178,-1.29222734782946 51.788886447277,-1.29221312398639 51.7889627648343,-1.29234075193847 51.7890570142594,-1.29230122328496 51.7890774502257,-1.29217263046391 51.7891441808752,-1.2918203503385 51.7893272256639,-1.29178236101931 51.7893485695844,-1.29175020756136 51.7893636566091,-1.29135116501288 51.7895707775291,-1.29124739106962 51.7896249827598,-1.2910675737874 51.7897182794587,-1.29038456132094 51.7900963563217,-1.29021331102875 51.7901995908641,-1.28962622182408 51.7905583773084,-1.2896031172865 51.7905528446061,-1.28944703850811 51.7905195428746,-1.28923270453347 51.7905038661375,-1.28878718412803 51.7908068755695,-1.28854392120362 51.7909734913254,-1.28821715994038 51.7911891285379,-1.28784800035127 51.7914323728215,-1.28740817087672 51.7917372091989,-1.28702311836224 51.7919794557466,-1.28670806657754 51.7921869801086,-1.2866596694659 51.7922236297714,-1.28643373809638 51.7923894474031,-1.28627302846883 51.792558446838,-1.28615311186672 51.7927105253929,-1.28605316588076 51.7928924773142,-1.28590704760472 51.7931441700595,-1.28580698718341 51.7934240968278,-1.28569759607001 51.7936437432095,-1.28548710411796 51.7937548222957,-1.28525097002146 51.793831678396,-1.28494637144532 51.7939287017428,-1.28465990690872 51.793982689298,-1.28454624652669 51.7942903969309,-1.28447263186993 51.7946361001695,-1.28439929305105 51.7946922822086,-1.28450666222971 51.794774821504,-1.28456352325774 51.7948533681818,-1.28458204844331 51.7949595463355,-1.28455719207582 51.7950646516597,-1.28416441272816 51.7956034655936,-1.28366816279884 51.7962657806659,-1.28365663791745 51.7962612161821,-1.28343331358673 51.7961699699672,-1.2832578855893 51.7960817117596,-1.28287831988917 51.7958761661208,-1.28285367916249 51.7958769147557,-1.28102797378641 51.7959710262693,-1.28099236270361 51.79611282848,-1.28094461552713 51.7961080423138,-1.27971692605059 51.795984578155,-1.27987551586799 51.7954029080375,-1.27993510638491 51.7951218397223,-1.28004810909205 51.7951279245848,-1.28006047744742 51.7950794618363,-1.27995180705499 51.7950716057851,-1.27995825138131 51.7950347919654,-1.27907436522762 51.7949906371517,-1.27882489706612 51.7949953999401,-1.2787263645083 51.7949965935128,-1.27843256363695 51.7950524085395,-1.27723636291892 51.7952275331603,-1.27723223169292 51.7952167214522,-1.2770439914375 51.7947417753598,-1.27701587033772 51.7946012904118,-1.27640575631492 51.7946703464924,-1.27640420226067 51.7946703369324,-1.27379505536392 51.7949825213055,-1.27283201520404 51.7950880304333,-1.27261260650576 51.7951118419383,-1.27155345878391 51.7952383189025,-1.2715809968227 51.7949760221504,-1.2715730033332 51.7947448755853,-1.27148457441065 51.7947497210994,-1.27125819685433 51.7947609028655,-1.27091646772896 51.7948154134395,-1.27062918394869 51.7949187991117,-1.27029816609052 51.7950354855802,-1.27002133086 51.7951209573746,-1.26937662273622 51.7953543437087,-1.2690626143196 51.7954908174039,-1.26888761625776 51.7955553466551,-1.26866312791117 51.7956268487254,-1.26866031696884 51.795623235806,-1.26811384243464 51.7948905911552,-1.26790409148495 51.794413698609,-1.26768257110458 51.7937631623164,-1.26764916123012 51.7937665497499,-1.26649904100961 51.7938789318111,-1.26627666859707 51.7932823191101,-1.2661766874621 51.7930119471757,-1.26610717586928 51.7928236515084,-1.26501935829212 51.793024496173,-1.26397381199178 51.7932131011357,-1.26395536370945 51.7931860198584,-1.26392135327708 51.7931381673844,-1.2638804758327 51.7929760266597,-1.26386520450613 51.7927611032416,-1.26382123512225 51.7924290583422,-1.2636935004937 51.7923517657075,-1.26325569636773 51.7924336071483,-1.26312775571512 51.7924570749673,-1.26252412126074 51.7925764358501,-1.26237270892464 51.7926096431587,-1.26203154097026 51.7927253438951,-1.26183751015088 51.7927987318824,-1.26175505657813 51.7927892257907,-1.26169582260832 51.7927780676665,-1.26161285688611 51.7927047391006,-1.26145867165815 51.7925562679331,-1.2614149548465 51.7925685774927,-1.26141353508297 51.7925676697162,-1.26041004120157 51.792845494346,-1.26012302365006 51.7929245868236,-1.25934226017453 51.7931498714822,-1.25872332915929 51.7933114529368,-1.25865921565989 51.7933281272373,-1.25823362998663 51.7934656665402,-1.25811260557221 51.793504453171,-1.25795000198958 51.7934324174157,-1.2577175286833 51.7932834474171,-1.25730205608835 51.7929724253807,-1.2570915753137 51.7927221115095,-1.25683127146863 51.7924192585987,-1.25663524635333 51.7921698441841,-1.25646164599118 51.7920617823678,-1.25637876434676 51.7918966768208,-1.25631695730765 51.7917731419877,-1.25623969741366 51.7916224536656,-1.25607874532888 51.791363372566,-1.25598073610411 51.7912387097058,-1.25570080781914 51.7909815720006,-1.25550906664223 51.7908212599498,-1.25499555566621 51.7903971613154,-1.25475216434186 51.790215847012,-1.25430327297537 51.7899117932508,-1.25400579357836 51.7896689219321,-1.25377974230941 51.7894804347668,-1.25356828866137 51.7892912308202,-1.25332115557394 51.7890693510545,-1.25320054934821 51.7889094867111,-1.2531401553894 51.7888821373637,-1.2530489557116 51.7888743673269,-1.25304535096257 51.7888248171163,-1.25301695206017 51.7884380360291,-1.25302070837467 51.7882105577913,-1.25303926693432 51.787962589599,-1.25300562963329 51.7878930736706,-1.25296649127489 51.7878092308778,-1.2529782556439 51.7874442775003,-1.25297873057358 51.787415516913,-1.25296873976583 51.7873183762944,-1.25294214159107 51.7872641857118,-1.25257239676475 51.7870919516133,-1.25249943738152 51.7870294664256,-1.25249209491823 51.7869457356432,-1.25252303328065 51.786918067522,-1.25263045869735 51.7868261673213,-1.25267309363651 51.7867850905424,-1.25269228976391 51.786766336394,-1.25273513318724 51.7867198677407,-1.25273715372217 51.7865975453582,-1.25273727248939 51.7865903552108,-1.25273898880851 51.7865732877228,-1.25272286011036 51.7864931864641,-1.25304873446792 51.7865132337128,-1.25328789489297 51.786514752314,-1.2535107333441 51.7864550441714,-1.25361302164869 51.7864062558806,-1.25370073067615 51.7863644760091,-1.25387639633859 51.7862586258446,-1.25400435711398 51.7861461808138,-1.25378870195047 51.7860386571015,-1.25374757469327 51.7860681485221,-1.25372412108293 51.7860841792411,-1.25241594454815 51.7855067115818,-1.25194676112332 51.7852986977907,-1.25143372934871 51.78502478604,-1.25063093728597 51.7847382398445,-1.25031044763988 51.7845744020709,-1.24938736050252 51.7841117122597,-1.24894727565119 51.7839021642445,-1.24875693452635 51.7838407247717,-1.24869537095491 51.7837908041535,-1.24803876547463 51.7835277353142,-1.24748902734015 51.7832859305595,-1.24741428711166 51.7833312943714,-1.24735244005291 51.7833057304277,-1.24740982129261 51.7832548623969,-1.24579316271034 51.7825719766983,-1.24484200081645 51.782149519664,-1.24398133241521 51.781784354912,-1.24304700478286 51.7813935415561,-1.24279228825861 51.7812876336736,-1.24261508450838 51.7812207856932,-1.24213492812312 51.7810666834456,-1.24199959494244 51.7810118794516,-1.24172752713339 51.780900374342,-1.24162914614808 51.7808871559066,-1.24156833404508 51.7808786739859,-1.2415811462792 51.7808059486103,-1.24158279023156 51.7808005660265,-1.24078055822382 51.7804887874416,-1.23999836606276 51.7801942112624,-1.23902193383668 51.7798165765223,-1.23613147144051 51.7786190673461,-1.23528800993491 51.7782692308578,-1.23436357710961 51.7779026815881,-1.23262148165649 51.7772116055841,-1.23171697898205 51.7768703336006,-1.23120820395991 51.7767033254443,-1.23109854975934 51.7766720471565,-1.23091530823164 51.7766250068499,-1.23080123044436 51.7766008902777,-1.23066234121377 51.7765811056143,-1.23045405693156 51.7765590689906,-1.23010631833656 51.776550500996,-1.22914706852341 51.7766188232352,-1.22874382963729 51.7766341567819,-1.22873383812099 51.7766313946606,-1.22810793702791 51.7764447286848,-1.22801269829311 51.7764162387212,-1.22799973487525 51.7764125581632,-1.22800686257176 51.7763379991152,-1.2278733242153 51.7761798209843,-1.22782094647136 51.7761047813617,-1.22776296977567 51.776021705046,-1.22774357633747 51.7759676457648,-1.22771532981546 51.7758371247683,-1.2277104086341 51.7757893626883,-1.22771217242008 51.7756860047254,-1.22771991714937 51.7755683041864,-1.22778052482722 51.7754131085259,-1.22793710270673 51.7752433520821,-1.22795038776262 51.7752281585809,-1.22773064040926 51.7751079756064,-1.22771061537065 51.7750979565827,-1.22732546917303 51.7749012717322,-1.22660720709922 51.7746106212006,-1.22653234760412 51.7745786685722,-1.22559720745184 51.7741759348286,-1.22557193181748 51.7742144196233,-1.22556885236368 51.7742197925403,-1.22554584101922 51.7742097534788,-1.22472418275028 51.7738662761723,-1.22475223420379 51.7738332030512,-1.22444615957045 51.7737655677416,-1.22443885552464 51.773766418439,-1.22428616451657 51.7737995682819,-1.22426455669524 51.7737913359576,-1.22412633776249 51.7737400876425,-1.22394818747518 51.7736481266886,-1.22381653734645 51.7736319771322,-1.22378469634602 51.7736281715091,-1.2237617165298 51.7736163345715,-1.22369274786313 51.7735825313842,-1.2233981961118 51.7732613992494,-1.22332088394516 51.7732960343463,-1.22262291232538 51.7730027966692,-1.22090629585321 51.7722828603763,-1.22083440035994 51.7722527214565,-1.22017550011088 51.772301387148,-1.21958630148936 51.7723479050093,-1.21892745602838 51.772400159541,-1.21851523462299 51.7724324767311,-1.21744986310437 51.7725260652677,-1.21730396721071 51.7725808240658,-1.21716164874886 51.7726014495664,-1.2167539242841 51.7727120818043,-1.21655459683732 51.7727538996621,-1.216227671522 51.7728011589135,-1.21574048164321 51.7728149893841,-1.21527866858452 51.7727849427064,-1.21499386252688 51.7727461883735,-1.21475459516601 51.7727481864337,-1.21381762746404 51.7725413891466,-1.21323536275355 51.7724359231729,-1.21274575059509 51.772341860996,-1.21225645368105 51.7723053263668,-1.21102072835895 51.7722790649803,-1.21097528621444 51.7723084227077,-1.21072318564384 51.7722995400489,-1.21067880909833 51.7722677818593,-1.21049944926368 51.7722539038417,-1.2103640302099 51.7722008603432,-1.21035976023786 51.7721990339377,-1.21000553363524 51.7720645214312,-1.20987257896393 51.7720483474664,-1.20983541919079 51.7720139408419,-1.20969005528571 51.7718735497452,-1.20931341727614 51.7717020309658,-1.20926556856344 51.7716981137714,-1.20907021525102 51.7716833170429,-1.20899507465515 51.7716684297728,-1.20872514435846 51.7715245029235,-1.2085700283976 51.7715252568386,-1.20831817473439 51.7714273828149,-1.20802655004508 51.7712806116938,-1.20792404041381 51.7712592473424,-1.20779690887518 51.7712314249664,-1.20756618996666 51.7711687475167,-1.20724649611239 51.7710488412028,-1.20698212957787 51.7710039131165,-1.20621699409155 51.7708350671922,-1.20614086349143 51.7707950031188,-1.20593581680442 51.7707540685734,-1.20568997778084 51.7706408588597,-1.20538489834061 51.7706010453708,-1.20518861338777 51.770551180045,-1.20446029770989 51.7702666175683,-1.20435646896188 51.7702389490948,-1.20416163624093 51.7701881930021,-1.20412712158143 51.7701735775362,-1.20382655122302 51.7700474992092,-1.20328852315783 51.7699844401664,-1.20313747624619 51.769998697483,-1.20298842552625 51.7699877998389,-1.20283132554486 51.7700200829786,-1.20277904428945 51.7700305149728,-1.20266770748431 51.7700153782512,-1.20241324661805 51.76997850694,-1.20228957652951 51.7700055329939,-1.2022226383792 51.770020449541,-1.20207440363715 51.7700446121158,-1.20195529637671 51.7700635789689,-1.20183234632756 51.7701310584782,-1.20166137656011 51.7701298979232,-1.20146482827458 51.7700953053242,-1.20120660452228 51.7700279342297,-1.20118642058473 51.7700206061827,-1.20088320742838 51.769875536239,-1.20076879248155 51.7697911639735,-1.20067748199097 51.76979234109,-1.20064271482307 51.7697921047659,-1.20056856432291 51.7697214890111,-1.2005125608036 51.7696923445067,-1.20031411052667 51.7696100071571,-1.20019758833949 51.769557080375,-1.20014788416966 51.7695028102363,-1.20012934078812 51.7694838078814,-1.19990748589968 51.7694885907194,-1.19919093294294 51.7693659615748,-1.19899322818099 51.7693159863066,-1.19824187392565 51.7691886199632,-1.1981294573425 51.7691536964718,-1.19807908737102 51.7691371733673,-1.19811317739213 51.7690069800714,-1.19821110463595 51.7689627043957,-1.19823794559467 51.7689179439942,-1.19824749485263 51.7688712679581,-1.19825064872242 51.7688551098345,-1.19812347355679 51.7687562660715,-1.19779094451124 51.7686280666608,-1.19752999481325 51.7685534778958,-1.1971138926142 51.7684823236753,-1.19690426889632 51.7684512296125,-1.19645869828695 51.7684113322023,-1.19623613441469 51.7683755642943,-1.19597254189349 51.7683692679872,-1.19593480505042 51.7683681110947,-1.19590026252665 51.7683552907443,-1.19576934840759 51.7683058566014,-1.19571401690019 51.7683198600679,-1.19548837360447 51.7683767430062,-1.19535663747462 51.7683668529869,-1.19520219737994 51.7684108294276,-1.19501583542699 51.7684625870797,-1.19493970280896 51.7684234145545,-1.19489377964736 51.7683988307057,-1.19472792777668 51.7684327509546,-1.19454943585999 51.768371214458,-1.1944013709752 51.768379188892,-1.19424646522859 51.7683754309771,-1.1940400793748 51.7683236800114,-1.19387661254236 51.7683108742483,-1.193782670306 51.7682922528552,-1.19372246806045 51.7682576830959,-1.19349041560639 51.7682650804955,-1.19347307636178 51.7682658604428,-1.19346449913025 51.7682577117988,-1.19341324271804 51.7682106190775,-1.19316952173442 51.7682224301496,-1.19264590488583 51.7681640053867,-1.19254774995053 51.7681471518183,-1.19236891659472 51.768098283699,-1.1922195380786 51.7681062463618,-1.19204167963316 51.7681634509304,-1.19191599721636 51.7682228115234,-1.19181822594069 51.7682580943583,-1.19156207592489 51.7682365585412,-1.19129778992508 51.7681888990246,-1.1908586203086 51.7681121707719,-1.19017966842685 51.7679941497241,-1.18901403533948 51.767697489929,-1.18883973397498 51.767636063514,-1.18861883772188 51.7675077990543,-1.18848467541738 51.7673935259078,-1.18840933983308 51.7673103100525,-1.18830631809811 51.7671585890081,-1.18826199693551 51.7670449356992,-1.18826763675756 51.7668103698381,-1.18828274402622 51.7662943435463,-1.18828883353087 51.7661946111177,-1.18829642931452 51.766097495805,-1.18832714843662 51.7656769472258,-1.18823892338379 51.7655864513057,-1.18822460670963 51.7655719705668,-1.18817530724734 51.7655761245692,-1.18776888426874 51.7656137671154,-1.18770224149127 51.7655324085524,-1.18739122782137 51.7655796975172,-1.18700084456219 51.7656156505121,-1.18636966343856 51.7657407221311,-1.18613756458896 51.7657579922281,-1.18445438354676 51.7658821498167,-1.18442311065198 51.7659268763857,-1.18192701555761 51.7659697619542,-1.18070796092232 51.7659900385675,-1.18070648699314 51.7659064334368,-1.18022773990287 51.765859951138,-1.18005872279804 51.7647887583516,-1.17999336449335 51.7644790015279,-1.17990765832373 51.7639273067628,-1.17975034609301 51.7630944852101,-1.17974637131292 51.7630764800843,-1.17968391748737 51.7628440460686,-1.17971002399478 51.7628406327101,-1.18113260591298 51.7626203474204,-1.18180983001114 51.7625109051059,-1.18268548146377 51.7624019394019,-1.18273981423817 51.7623636656339,-1.1829393754159 51.7622220422587,-1.18308180553527 51.7621214595534,-1.18317496708871 51.7620168490723,-1.18342787942742 51.7616526757103,-1.1836814433224 51.7613316520769,-1.18370921757253 51.7612356657978,-1.18413334749634 51.7605382098132,-1.18427714901724 51.7602748497858,-1.18428686567317 51.760139996782,-1.18429468781448 51.7600240967929,-1.18430770770543 51.760024187113,-1.18509476794098 51.7600089703281,-1.18555715680797 51.759998690878,-1.18595866541295 51.7599924825023,-1.18595913398193 51.7599664185131,-1.18597723092219 51.7592787283522,-1.18601222848029 51.7587008172851,-1.1860246330382 51.7584958708388,-1.18608918210343 51.7573238311002,-1.18613345073312 51.7568746123689,-1.18615704209586 51.7568514050238,-1.18615707439946 51.7568496075063,-1.18620872478614 51.7568005271111,-1.18696957835673 51.7560594583047,-1.18706729464701 51.7560259768506,-1.18724605655571 51.7559094605827,-1.18733260618895 51.755852531084,-1.18733135034453 51.7558426348269,-1.1873286869638 51.7558246390056,-1.1872599162585 51.7557828156207,-1.18730724342725 51.7557282217464,-1.18741082074935 51.7556875895519,-1.18742387821057 51.7556921741432,-1.18757076751369 51.7557408293155,-1.18766195315573 51.755745054812,-1.18766126148736 51.7557037019832,-1.18766019903037 51.7556830206176,-1.18782123802156 51.7555088533073,-1.18784153565257 51.7555027014147,-1.18794645515688 51.7554737633389,-1.18805470489405 51.7557387788715,-1.18826783889289 51.7557303628779,-1.18865314234347 51.7558131115945,-1.18878738538398 51.755921003435,-1.18931354379187 51.7559093515091,-1.18938207528965 51.7559646550949,-1.18957624426438 51.7560414986777,-1.18974822373658 51.7560633579318,-1.19000208050933 51.7560489273098,-1.19023609867424 51.7560082922726,-1.19024797343398 51.7559921943828,-1.19029824248342 51.7559332151092,-1.19033291857798 51.7559379482467,-1.19046005361041 51.75595590217,-1.19047969595564 51.7559128916213,-1.19048876835665 51.7558931789316,-1.19057691686447 51.7558200783933,-1.1911543741642 51.7554508411277,-1.19143874627826 51.7552658319252,-1.19146169226256 51.7552785739016,-1.19146604010347 51.7552759071876,-1.19149187573706 51.7552940622516,-1.19177607594692 51.7554398354012,-1.19196871294646 51.7556093380477,-1.1919912423367 51.755645447688,-1.19205449170431 51.7557492524153,-1.19230706876457 51.7558868070128,-1.19235610085403 51.7558970313888,-1.1926347275877 51.7559537759815,-1.19263914679549 51.7559538063256,-1.19264198126354 51.7559556235288,-1.19268492799899 51.7559855811307,-1.192901815365 51.7561687317724,-1.19322769215485 51.7564163597716,-1.19340939338301 51.7565498301603,-1.19396523610676 51.7569042910716,-1.19409987894248 51.7569906066408,-1.19430463719171 51.7571242336479,-1.19430922489667 51.7571080854216,-1.19431241879595 51.7570964219951,-1.19440419132854 51.7566582223913,-1.19450736666218 51.7560690906026,-1.19454619936174 51.7558401447003,-1.19461935924491 51.7553937275137,-1.19466157781052 51.7551422430953,-1.19471988600393 51.7547919931002,-1.19479874191178 51.7541056163147,-1.19486368075779 51.7538794557403,-1.19493246820759 51.7535912994031,-1.19491044833471 51.7532845438588,-1.19490879284886 51.7528871417943,-1.19491602211395 51.7526417096979,-1.19494445854882 51.752426175421,-1.19502580966835 51.752089565964,-1.19506613036491 51.7519378429462,-1.19512558430705 51.7516100721963,-1.19504815845825 51.7515645986084,-1.19508093403195 51.7513534984368,-1.1950923948849 51.7512798694787,-1.1951639634939 51.7504315555083,-1.19512631372861 51.7492903606192,-1.19512407877973 51.749248098371,-1.1951390199877 51.7487365631141,-1.1951389198326 51.747680118863,-1.19516069952883 51.7470256198165,-1.19516911368823 51.7463099958162,-1.19522078174435 51.7455191625802,-1.19526134292345 51.7451921609814,-1.19526642392462 51.7451481510381,-1.19477214447893 51.7453353276621,-1.19467884319522 51.7453706434927,-1.19441721688221 51.7450128079944,-1.19372067618862 51.74402979087,-1.19292278580274 51.7428787935454,-1.19222698289837 51.7418580194663,-1.19256159317586 51.74128126431,-1.19287779928601 51.7407718871557,-1.19327927238926 51.740181206942,-1.19338660227254 51.7400146631618,-1.19340757536119 51.7390779119318,-1.19342359449759 51.7385871473387,-1.19344016728805 51.7380585439479,-1.19348086200032 51.7377243524696,-1.19356882177778 51.7371764634929,-1.19386560645191 51.7367766127391,-1.19401715267677 51.7366409331899,-1.1940136699355 51.7365950667789,-1.19400763410424 51.7365249132868,-1.1936201292151 51.7364134923,-1.1931839613416 51.73626569125,-1.19170137807483 51.7362447206018,-1.18829802730601 51.7361754289768,-1.18697046092826 51.7361527722161,-1.18572822621139 51.7362187811456,-1.18359505745746 51.7363820536145,-1.18273887606619 51.7363994754706,-1.18211228739168 51.7363780392921,-1.18133371517406 51.7363492493784,-1.18126419430684 51.7363442708632,-1.181183163684 51.7363419087635,-1.18033563032494 51.7362838679307,-1.17947892842794 51.73625092546,-1.17924876361626 51.7362421278006,-1.17908331476585 51.7357059627507,-1.17883398411969 51.7353976154525,-1.17881984813669 51.7353804381013,-1.17835075563505 51.7355371600731,-1.17807076947088 51.7356422587849,-1.17798913713709 51.7356731486168,-1.1774112275406 51.7351215121149,-1.17666625974312 51.7344338716342,-1.17662389988665 51.7344587434406,-1.17631207534419 51.7340033465109,-1.17609381716324 51.7337474355586,-1.17581338969801 51.7334766164565,-1.17581356947584 51.7334667300959,-1.17582468817386 51.7333345835876,-1.17583275757489 51.7329696071532,-1.17583511092389 51.7328401856929,-1.17589305396092 51.7326805023119,-1.17593116948386 51.7325738034097,-1.17654255851818 51.7323182229287,-1.17738554664555 51.7319842602835,-1.18025906061961 51.7308264474153,-1.18126105742877 51.730430644489,-1.18322833385573 51.7296530500666,-1.18336965024454 51.7296018971096,-1.18358270649696 51.7298362754363,-1.18362936155629 51.7298177230753,-1.18469539870599 51.7293962682811,-1.18640047989079 51.7287012963497,-1.18750422621503 51.7282710883643,-1.18767926164717 51.7282030846661,-1.18937370322115 51.7275305579228,-1.19015980921606 51.7272095947047,-1.1902495034058 51.7271337183397,-1.19033221960221 51.7270408051093,-1.1903487758797 51.7270094585231,-1.1903685910831 51.7269493703845,-1.19033689598184 51.726859174709,-1.1901377870863 51.7262571749136,-1.18998793570646 51.7260520978064,-1.18903465081167 51.7243083589423,-1.18777309748453 51.7237719190652,-1.18729319390006 51.7234880630581,-1.18679250685065 51.7232319264264,-1.18654270662083 51.7231169397011,-1.18629974774719 51.7230198874227,-1.18594969836455 51.7229239806978,-1.18568068948955 51.7228286343637,-1.18544784650163 51.7227334481396,-1.18529166420249 51.7226433770659,-1.18516454284447 51.7225436196004,-1.18504597929203 51.7224592022143,-1.18492037357858 51.72235487072,-1.18485444499027 51.7222375596901,-1.18475828459631 51.7221154546864,-1.1846407187262 51.7219690213625,-1.18453017521037 51.7218370186473,-1.18435158968412 51.7217053526939,-1.18417310060142 51.7215683837644,-1.18443602961852 51.7214370847799,-1.18462429430879 51.7213556942579,-1.18477910900909 51.7212758692059,-1.18506366409895 51.7210701120917,-1.18543179827818 51.7208029110549,-1.18575191594941 51.7205506571536,-1.18592360550306 51.7204215093032,-1.1861762852603 51.7202155287316,-1.18645541974419 51.7199918430798,-1.18663791187324 51.7198258251409,-1.18684550289458 51.7196312165129,-1.18704447525181 51.7194312445394,-1.18719212189631 51.7192712768676,-1.18730889908598 51.7191354551294,-1.18744237740653 51.7189601082851,-1.1875704562701 51.7187596453203,-1.18767340430778 51.7185894804454,-1.18771405428361 51.7184989748603,-1.1877645487062 51.7184319080697,-1.18786022917683 51.7184208837968,-1.18801802984773 51.7181000863735,-1.18821663273817 51.7171933233362,-1.18832589843245 51.7167498531526,-1.18847284752957 51.7163813396601,-1.18864362684156 51.7159815297817,-1.18880731931829 51.7157308842508,-1.18908587396672 51.7153704691444,-1.18953798164288 51.7148547557353,-1.18947078043217 51.7147284496082,-1.18949132251341 51.7146341193123,-1.18960560496455 51.7145567050221,-1.18980941348308 51.7144915931458,-1.19045025777894 51.7144330872907,-1.19045836397229 51.714380109393,-1.19078354311175 51.7143283260785,-1.19157416171473 51.7142294968132,-1.19260395193749 51.7141098334593,-1.19283447115601 51.7140925402869,-1.19315434950801 51.7140902421233,-1.19329327899657 51.7140893979603,-1.19346266902642 51.7140869648982,-1.19377303502946 51.7140558357258,-1.19410376021349 51.7140139689189,-1.19443319493713 51.7139640923363,-1.19469501892669 51.7138975718483,-1.19520553095696 51.7137581470484,-1.19598718597061 51.7135108222287,-1.19628386449363 51.7134301545944,-1.1968876332059 51.7132535174337,-1.19754148950008 51.7130313764371,-1.19802767238209 51.7128764923981,-1.19825309902212 51.712816007789,-1.19876740903716 51.7127034698625,-1.19919929379079 51.7125886602835,-1.19942024730329 51.7125380306061,-1.19964584646006 51.7124675669753,-1.19976686918107 51.7124126606425,-1.19983768734619 51.7123421315191,-1.19991449395972 51.7122500700781,-1.19999633864571 51.7122038855836,-1.20008686362041 51.7121594679721,-1.20022184016812 51.7121388134445,-1.20036683227656 51.7121254179126,-1.20046217220583 51.7121395496353,-1.20060474187479 51.7121755755433,-1.20074700191713 51.7122359587267,-1.20091946968749 51.7123090414896,-1.20104446923752 51.7123602283108,-1.2016147071108 51.7126086873365,-1.2023947811228 51.7129367699174,-1.20306993507562 51.7132326752823,-1.20419970818503 51.7136826667845,-1.20475898833878 51.7138977778034,-1.20531950104097 51.7141245798604,-1.2056874495269 51.714273583732,-1.20646982498816 51.7145621040299,-1.20664789721087 51.7146433060283,-1.20683877269662 51.7147362795366,-1.20703810707549 51.7148437816982,-1.20738167979275 51.7149746382542,-1.20787285895712 51.7151137695184,-1.20842880543578 51.7152757169077,-1.2088824704228 51.7154038047803,-1.20918621037579 51.7154993317729,-1.20960224467219 51.7156297704085,-1.21016226335432 51.7158053099534,-1.21031130412489 51.7158135023534,-1.21054402272438 51.7158276498545,-1.21087375333673 51.7158496392298,-1.21136627287304 51.7159059783872,-1.21154265144573 51.7159206447668,-1.21240504531999 51.715941707264,-1.21240636806358 51.7159480082549,-1.21242834270819 51.7160983575716,-1.21273144626897 51.7160662307918,-1.21344360664632 51.715982818792,-1.21376267355109 51.7159454029228,-1.21391278007308 51.7158852833545,-1.21399962442165 51.7158049653257,-1.21414691519844 51.7156593435836,-1.21417079831419 51.7155345595789,-1.21430114541591 51.7155264421844,-1.21435380698297 51.7155798278284,-1.21445381247237 51.7156560017433,-1.21450550935927 51.71568241461,-1.21465125599195 51.7157085569972,-1.21476085013753 51.7157272666917,-1.21501072123322 51.7157640816985,-1.21520586685314 51.7157770701578,-1.21547221776229 51.7157788481866,-1.21571726077033 51.7157498317942,-1.2160429016986 51.7156702064663,-1.21659238586646 51.7155381398183,-1.21713647104292 51.7153798773772,-1.21739286218797 51.7152809106946,-1.21755779926789 51.7152047054676,-1.2176196242349 51.7151421957305,-1.21768311040425 51.7150733150025,-1.2177599064182 51.7148139612537,-1.21785460755074 51.7143605695126,-1.21792751462411 51.7141605155277,-1.21804815075095 51.7139608689099,-1.21813303585869 51.7138274112551,-1.21830587815617 51.7136245161203,-1.2185563766087 51.7133681146153,-1.2186867710868 51.7132737006376,-1.2187761267793 51.7132130811436,-1.21883058654056 51.7131622071886,-1.21884850796215 51.7131263712715,-1.21886108867031 51.7130680279709,-1.21879706678308 51.7130019845703,-1.21895774545358 51.7129229625587,-1.21903845793113 51.7129414763658,-1.2191383333642 51.7129421399141,-1.21921512598402 51.7129318635417,-1.21991357131409 51.7126361867062,-1.22015803762037 51.7125632022454,-1.22037589222843 51.7125179059108,-1.22054024702021 51.7124677600272,-1.2206472191806 51.7123956604388,-1.22071953525612 51.7123124545972,-1.22088134156532 51.7120771229763,-1.22104856237879 51.7118669056394,-1.22119848404696 51.7116493824354,-1.22128953297153 51.7114827948115,-1.22138500167205 51.7114897193924,-1.22145837503055 51.7114281829971,-1.22149215935616 51.7113996427479,-1.22176009235158 51.7112242486764,-1.22202297641763 51.7110856744779,-1.22229827771262 51.7109814290151,-1.22230703432976 51.7109787903263,-1.22270691379273 51.711459817038,-1.22302413527945 51.7117855994892,-1.22330576413261 51.7120715953474,-1.22374982234192 51.7125105732611,-1.22398043392046 51.7127378036154,-1.22384785316623 51.7127863663678,-1.2236726505625 51.7128777934874,-1.22404197660366 51.7132003216946,-1.22429198475468 51.7133962188128,-1.22464598656166 51.7136871833098,-1.22506227432702 51.7140558606298,-1.22522602028916 51.7142160409516,-1.22548388955712 51.7143715379145,-1.2257038153096 51.7144637732261,-1.22615421892876 51.7147014355818,-1.22653295646037 51.7149008718841,-1.22772007948335 51.715825709503,-1.22813431842622 51.7160649242917,-1.22870381535738 51.7164525718874,-1.22900004148938 51.7166559530421,-1.23041175617683 51.7174825507104,-1.23038534398685 51.7175057485149,-1.23106621883 51.7179013046429,-1.23113358677151 51.7179403969033,-1.23118927228158 51.7179857048356,-1.23133774652675 51.7181054171112,-1.23141042951144 51.7181760045611,-1.23186381056435 51.7186716410392,-1.23197573139306 51.7187299901804,-1.23212634381193 51.7188082773123,-1.23260481024626 51.7192753107446,-1.2328854154773 51.7195504898479,-1.2334176758261 51.7202606567137,-1.23360344458936 51.7205756648421,-1.23379249338019 51.7209510084524,-1.23391128918287 51.7209490861019,-1.23392143367623 51.7209491522147,-1.23397060958616 51.7210339668039,-1.23400721498759 51.7210998231132,-1.23404088235104 51.721162963645,-1.23403924119343 51.7212601211817,-1.23400428825409 51.7213578706368,-1.23392928818091 51.7214238985279,-1.23376702283709 51.7219497605763,-1.23380786665762 51.7220120490699,-1.2338636812994 51.7220501655392,-1.23413857550214 51.7221490351675,-1.23448103078321 51.7222691081158,-1.23499216386811 51.7224378283125,-1.23598632301042 51.7228076185284,-1.23695972594394 51.723205939594,-1.23716770378546 51.7233169519277,-1.23782629542841 51.7236691776302,-1.23910600338791 51.7242825891054,-1.24104589423161 51.7252365188813,-1.24107002667688 51.7251854389443,-1.241125499996 51.725066247009,-1.24132814339438 51.7251547456468,-1.24185375008698 51.7254108097051,-1.24173151043306 51.7255394589245,-1.24367151756569 51.7264070538978,-1.2450754590643 51.7270463673412,-1.24593171303903 51.7274429621489,-1.24614472535867 51.7272608685396,-1.24668616967972 51.7275224055591,-1.24684181812332 51.7276529303122,-1.24701646303086 51.7277753967981,-1.2476635873909 51.7283019643295,-1.24829238098215 51.7282790205887,-1.2"
  },
  "8": {
    "Question": "Where is Kilkenny located?",
    "Query": "select ?geoWKT where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kilkeasy_2963401> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "POLYGON ((-6.94615558742755 52.5969638972022, -6.95125508751078 52.6005033901233, -6.9699593944144 43 52.6039104644652, -6.97309463671741 52.611360314255, -6.97942291308747 52.6138350217383, -6.98514800398873 52.6185020930624, -6.98015742823538 52.6257485120931, -6.98872998860738 52.6293842320121, -6.99156690141226 52.6338407270587, -6.98537180516497 52.6428561777614, -6.98783818613809 52.6602223735549, -6.97992766914281 52.6689608172785, -6.98746921968693 52.6708694058627, -6.98718839724984 52.6727054060123, -6.99304964155119 52.673655698088, -6.99192162753385 52.6760258105501, -6.99769826672116 52.6791319215522, -6.9957012280409 52.6810852896979, -7.00564501219138 52.6848432957363, -6.99975906773986 52.6885754814082, -7.00652208071692 52.6911674364749, -7.00397054319039 52.6933052619065, -7.0117575514393 52.6976349713826, -7.01565404576867 52.7029183838019, -7.03629943837875 52.7099621021751, -7.04246321961544 52.7154429226994, -7.04931262379567 52.7105062691717, -7.05252493575655 52.7029624503931, -7.05669211003565 52.710404131474, -7.06578121344311 52.7082141577231, -7.08017390548223 52.7265279538787, -7.10786320786172 52.725294298415, -7.10482515251066 52.7314273117421, -7.09994981744557 52.7324279944929, -7.09452618898419 52.7315314672086, -7.09004069482439 52.7339751886076, -7.09200311213205 52.7377495432701, -7.09884210905386 52.7392572277847, -7.10233969470583 52.7464348754469, -7.10168887838548 52.7486394374419, -7.08330816960685 52.757076938846, -7.08151079600863 52.7698825040232, -7.08588642098788 52.775216422771, -7.09068219260423 52.7761634915609, -7.08244889400811 52.7790512381759, -7.07547483448536 52.7838477154918, -7.06763150756429 52.7851781491678, -7.06031542829564 52.7931495555671, -7.07027299577552 52.8127598027792, -7.07665936186073 52.8161024387677, -7.08909560748052 52.8173686231529, -7.09328561834456 52.8208550120895, -7.09091360144449 52.8217698440065, -7.09879930352561 52.8269207012495, -7.11990798247504 52.8239493151213, -7.12225052284795 52.830912540852, -7.12889151958559 52.8380519360892, -7.12862519447442 52.8411227999392, -7.13623471432688 52.8470220227055, -7.14133281866691 52.8478543020694, -7.13858267447123 52.8666974770611, -7.14126220140169 52.8700485192194, -7.14749778565029 52.8727679534111, -7.14864794071803 52.8762743532908, -7.15318694454835 52.875909458049, -7.15955128864879 52.8707740918154, -7.16426189398454 52.8783896014798, -7.16315937093927 52.8822338965977, -7.16887668656444 52.8838593168757, -7.17536199337566 52.8834199668479, -7.17991135261043 52.8896184960806, -7.18464879957338 52.8904219726994, -7.18910065134853 52.8939509460493, -7.19605746412327 52.8939623184639, -7.20443252789802 52.890716893238, -7.20679440666283 52.8869972197691, -7.21191548514765 52.8847119293309, -7.21225985791122 52.8818140650811, -7.22036215188979 52.8770795494009, -7.24736277745115 52.8783288794206, -7.24289907697943 52.8697072283417, -7.24328093555119 52.8627884019005, -7.24661109679151 52.8622479872779, -7.25952928409517 52.8490556713883, -7.27729838893699 52.8542323843088, -7.29911511655727 52.8636077256775, -7.30187026286591 52.8616636618394, -7.3086168630155 52.8662867504503, -7.31192724287064 52.8659833141201, -7.31967040344965 52.8615677603712, -7.32432532006052 52.8622670950066, -7.32719518379247 52.8600839595402, -7.32955841325217 52.8517073501372, -7.33530108277076 52.8487177621559, -7.33741891881825 52.8440968760726, -7.34024215881157 52.8439383235951, -7.345331693144 52.8389845752252, -7.34273619632944 52.8349149212892, -7.34557625588381 52.8333228261205, -7.34451838084998 52.8296336451117, -7.34995882640251 52.8211679259901, -7.34751250716304 52.8116873637382, -7.34963746449886 52.8129929145617, -7.35512169421227 52.8123855248954, -7.36008431596762 52.813874165212, -7.36128125640055 52.8284102664548, -7.37040762589566 52.8317813901306, -7.37669370327408 52.8288305490833, -7.37815137411679 52.8235912973888, -7.38094142687377 52.8214947753105, -7.38307300244373 52.822731493741, -7.38591116769145 52.8199891474163, -7.3886930636105 52.8200071198512, -7.39265076175386 52.8081189924685, -7.39102962750239 52.8042848043561, -7.39901486608696 52.7956899357834, -7.4038041339805 52.7983368946793, -7.42163943558323 52.8013226129994, -7.42589155873267 52.8040499208604, -7.43908994738654 52.7962829598964, -7.44668767577132 52.7954178983365, -7.44925840068265 52.786990155148, -7.4759990756232 52.7856291952121, -7.48596890943546 52.7916682154395, -7.48957427206589 52.7976086831874, -7.49609318614224 52.7992215407551, -7.49488773880685 52.801059276087, -7.50092460079037 52.8022455961809, -7.50770266329032 52.8001380163265, -7.51679894594631 52.8006623256507, -7.51933878853402 52.8019833269905, -7.516027727779 52.8066180742061, -7.52365192332656 52.808103967273, -7.52905399660499 52.8112426820537, -7.53396189002814 52.8114423586913, -7.53511505347164 52.8101222919968, -7.53508019123757 52.8032415613198, -7.54740147659816 52.8082293720726, -7.55120363089129 52.8064398377722, -7.55951527161674 52.8086581250644, -7.55669107971249 52.8144130125589, -7.56032811972201 52.8153135649571, -7.56163165756983 52.8188354387584, -7.56553909603058 52.8192283887061, -7.56627052201194 52.8218979668698, -7.57315826908927 52.8232746792519, -7.57368156958373 52.825573469448, -7.57858935624932 52.8287194958214, -7.58409628106344 52.8219480903261, -7.59496681000937 52.8164634745811, -7.6001621067923 52.8154713192734, -7.60890793185137 52.8071595765962, -7.61278065397935 52.8105681971911, -7.61675746970752 52.8094303880046, -7.61645727679987 52.8037739886012, -7.61310960537172 52.8016585919325, -7.61451402865595 52.7926556001773, -7.61198158380145 52.7919872721517, -7.61207919788494 52.7900358669989, -7.62561058967336 52.789919561356, -7.635689469836 52.7876801311189, -7.64751842932226 52.789956529366, -7.65289668955 52.7893394874584, -7.66264287870728 52.7840206785744, -7.67408237063264 52.7812937659253, -7.67126369838865 52.7774787017385, -7.66736879198226 52.7609457897699, -7.66987387135023 52.7556585511159, -7.65412637476153 52.7467327100723, -7.64618335395077 52.7350739624923, -7.64782667609943 52.7321310549072, -7.62617444968681 52.733689205436, -7.61110611737078 52.7244216381348, -7.60871164046274 52.7209816308676, -7.60349817634155 52.7196238534716, -7.59461940318709 52.7203480930961, -7.59285733252714 52.7162393039418, -7.58711270602255 52.7132116510982, -7.58094779665514 52.7112736941578, -7.57672035789849 52.7125119235685, -7.56101128133332 52.7057466485802, -7.56055267574195 52.7027542917647, -7.55347895882044 52.702684720891, -7.54768233844646 52.7004139383235, -7.54702910445211 52.6947956962106, -7.54170224463473 52.6933103249844, -7.53616549203293 52.6891245529278, -7.53359315964478 52.683245785219, -7.53858881802989 52.6803375616206, -7.53144128887834 52.6738166666179, -7.52746919468936 52.6728491558975, -7.52671694622864 52.668638954534, -7.51980926543975 52.6617802920555, -7.52120430207791 52.6547506075369, -7.51850302723061 52.6518565890658, -7.50234315605773 52.6353915821963, -7.47596366424491 52.6171190433511, -7.47467416717465 52.6111199782737, -7.48123126205124 52.6028391709117, -7.47995459388399 52.596116613504, -7.47563517087504 52.5907212777507, -7.45136107343544 52.5818728575608, -7.458465554837 52.5740875313789, -7.45526242280936 52.5739672734298, -7.45511961402878 52.57023148481, -7.45759807215029 52.567269768951, -7.45564975686748 52.5635015861518, -7.45941662118036 52.5588513213764, -7.45315797280817 52.5578611186965, -7.45150383385671 52.55419157017, -7.45450379946463 52.5493260017457, -7.45276765593979 52.5455425477317, -7.45630937903936 52.5434036902033, -7.45856698974735 52.5357151895725, -7.45713997539204 52.5295357265034, -7.45882783671533 52.5214214395169, -7.45406460288875 52.5214952810005, -7.45027481403372 52.5163985725524, -7.45323015601151 52.5106610362614, -7.44842444007312 52.5091534092501, -7.44342444721259 52.5103894327979, -7.43244001101755 52.5185609528656, -7.42006549719785 52.5109100221027, -7.42520839275936 52.5044653737408, -7.4295335260625 52.5031461973894, -7.43201424597157 52.4952162398419, -7.44392953452207 52.4913133470234, -7.45952429059651 52.4823149005869, -7.45951094189154 52.4768041370676, -7.4678897101033 52.4722174400085, -7.46276354946207 52.4693377264212, -7.46099234457617 52.4658806178428, -7.44106576129765 52.4659590688287, -7.44105007917504 52.4596192918354, -7.43056883490984 52.4550564620416, -7.42936217380335 52.4531799364071, -7.42294537516756 52.4520733967049, -7.41869434141687 52.4419892066336, -7.40974597850326 52.4380250954552, -7.40836787935107 52.4353978203206, -7.40351890434734 52.434455212959, -7.39993738680163 52.4279511219376, -7.39101691540766 52.4285915544625, -7.38932394755221 52.4255534624887, -7.3846971866837 52.4246617771548, -7.38321278833536 52.4165088283635, -7.3854582604355 52.4156031295585, -7.38547879088437 52.4104046774027, -7.38909931756751 52.4075477989758, -7.39045956505868 52.3999605872782, -7.39453257786364 52.3947936879978, -7.38824260341025 52.3837083725864, -7.39215447950077 52.380457818601, -7.38962602759637 52.3777784229362, -7.39706607420844 52.3640517059004, -7.38876068441032 52.3565359827366, -7.38298389807469 52.3549454390028, -7.37614678219894 52.3502830243943, -7.3772895466179 52.3494384538171, -7.37289966660517 52.3470712590394, -7.3721607311648 52.3430092664724, -7.35859533980264 52.3421756403704, -7.35523447190505 52.3358514382568, -7.32392925997013 52.3308612741476, -7.31797837073579 52.3242379675984, -7.30256116419803 52.3155770201202, -7.29983881595914 52.3110701948969, -7.30116406492595 52.3041430987998, -7.28470064735464 52.2971863505438, -7.28320428798547 52.2889412586348, -7.27629291424708 52.2830611314202, -7.26500024799817 52.2674033146363, -7.25890374634406 52.2645184402278, -7.23976945557889 52.2614565087328, -7.22740900896422 52.2464849333981, -7.21931800001675 52.2431585723256, -7.21245438136566 52.2431049011982, -7.19858951912025 52.2499038490055, -7.19442517706084 52.2547452687185, -7.19428683862948 52.254956119072, -7.19419036431349 52.2550799457847, -7.19402324012692 52.2552960744317, -7.19381461722388 52.2555478306682, -7.19326950275363 52.2561095473066, -7.19301463415345 52.2563712180697, -7.19286566658441 52.2565329700112, -7.19286319664714 52.256535652465, -7.19272818470163 52.256671077932, -7.19260536107589 52.256794277321, -7.19238872712534 52.2569978744166, -7.19235351023751 52.2570327563829, -7.19201176086327 52.2573708215506, -7.1919686996905 52.257413992231, -7.19196331666164 52.2574193891241, -7.19195416884926 52.2574257687946, -7.19115305863938 52.2579844684296, -7.17002216770015 52.2739159111823, -7.17002166037763 52.2739162419996, -7.16993386868397 52.2739682111449, -7.1695373504753 52.2742065098106, -7.16926104505221 52.2743756877488, -7.16889908758824 52.2745757382897, -7.1684702675513 52.2748131813016, -7.16847020390994 52.2748132150109, -7.16821695144682 52.2749357985243, -7.16804594477325 52.275025958628, -7.16509297324119 52.2767650687339, -7.16458338037519 52.2770467994951, -7.16457796435253 52.2770497490534, -7.16416844716758 52.2772544553986, -7.16355215714488 52.277545957715, -7.16353890272094 52.2775522314892, -7.16320172853786 52.2777055159519, -7.1628349956513 52.2778842807749, -7.16283492469188 52.2778843135304, -7.16252365543168 52.2780183729051, -7.16136259562166 52.2784909847871, -7.16112557025454 52.2785872826657, -7.16018312688353 52.2789517815159, -7.16017913802659 52.2789533198943, -7.16016034963183 52.2789605669702, -7.15983955730205 52.2790855942267, -7.15926987640607 52.27925908636, -7.15911184614769 52.2793065536649, -7.15885572666431 52.2793774354394, -7.15878041353465 52.2793982787996, -7.1584513134928 52.2794774263285, -7.15105787547722 52.2792772858459, -7.144993908661 52.2756332894863, -7.1442905813041 52.275231488068, -7.14401374561048 52.2750700650499, -7.14341063770574 52.2747183998485, -7.14340988813896 52.2747179836223, -7.14321501959237 52.2746082816365, -7.14256059864468 52.274239931294, -7.14214831263534 52.2740249715963, -7.14130465691499 52.273608068669, -7.14032075799812 52.2730934370123, -7.13606186218974 52.2711503209475, -7.13606046531445 52.2711498190385, -7.13528014057447 52.2708473869591, -7.13401564631559 52.2698851680246, -7.13382171970594 52.2697148195208, -7.13361851604168 52.2695318182654, -7.13353960371318 52.2694520171157, -7.13344158995785 52.2693834169267, -7.13340427839301 52.2693560993131, -7.13331693893974 52.2692921553685, -7.13322676309274 52.2692221293719, -7.13311947427438 52.2691450418892, -7.13296337108859 52.2690271506495, -7.13166814912898 52.2688129120803, -7.1314830317331 52.2687904699697, -7.13123979593844 52.2687606021619, -7.12454512116305 52.2682588943326, -7.12442950289668 52.2682607022171, -7.12442942082492 52.2682607034063, -7.12434657041878 52.2682620000303, -7.12426991413666 52.2682628769155, -7.12259664430524 52.2680240314572, -7.12199572053797 52.2679306873838, -7.1219950209173 52.267930577012, -7.12185118097738 52.267907887376, -7.12162870316187 52.2678712479902, -7.12119223372275 52.2678056491559, -7.12050463151545 52.2677027443661, -7.11570860654966 52.2670014043748, -7.1120723751838 52.2669017271452, -7.10682782437026 52.2667562540768, -7.10661683488959 52.2667490532835, -7.10646847108287 52.2667456474391, -7.10628117525162 52.266740635255, -7.10627972411831 52.2667405964056, -7.10617227505825 52.2667387052813, -7.10547486890902 52.2667290623308, -7.1052734751721 52.2667269323282, -7.10523205771551 52.2667272503831, -7.1051878418241 52.2667304838712, -7.10517688144621 52.2667327379068, -7.10510203446555 52.2686906743448, -7.10029938749041 52.2703867890728, -7.09904975039814 52.2676090556736, -7.09600771011803 52.2666736516931, -7.10061195305702 52.2663509951963, -7.10019178615036 52.2653448800693, -7.10007937093634 52.2650639145345, -7.1000679696341 52.2650354210671, -7.10005034165463 52.264994422489, -7.09998249449889 52.264836673239, -7.09988736838713 52.2646037840174, -7.09973515898214 52.2642461049873, -7.09970296152726 52.2641699782845, -7.09966607917592 52.2640846607005, -7.09962597826311 52.2639918973623, -7.09958827867304 52.2639008691924, -7.09956919000062 52.2638547833872, -7.09954365803769 52.2637911363547, -7.09949972891626 52.2636817018082, -7.0994995284036 52.2636811861165, -7.09948455143151 52.2636473573945, -7.09941231071467 52.2634842402732, -7.09939238436171 52.2634357713926, -7.09935249833391 52.2633386769595, -7.09918696805679 52.2629560359292, -7.09917464022212 52.2629269788829, -7.09913972615545 52.262843671654, -7.09900711993905 52.2625223994622, -7.09884574845026 52.2621373868985, -7.09877094347813 52.2619762668567, -7.09867270748817 52.2617646374831, -7.09854493596059 52.2614558727435, -7.09853370188016 52.2614140247374, -7.09847100175859 52.2612184805877, -7.09756360127868 52.2592103665899, -7.09748495717181 52.25903728896, -7.09739766305445 52.2588516928709, -7.09736391236597 52.2587604630615, -7.09736366818891 52.2587597915244, -7.0973260653694 52.2586673951603, -7.09732602631295 52.2586672986808, -7.09730665420191 52.2586196677998, -7.09728605440056 52.2585775296108, -7.09721486083673 52.2583930677187, -7.09721484820285 52.2583930406555, -7.09717142890646 52.2582964019588, -7.09715711695795 52.2582599343612, -7.09711825365632 52.2581624945181, -7.09710248774859 52.2581236211606, -7.09707111494863 52.258029033221, -7.09707021971513 52.2580265202793, -7.09702424062098 52.2578983631677, -7.09693905643113 52.2576838045294, -7.09685087941993 52.257517970435, -7.09681713989107 52.2574723698012, -7.09681643133567 52.25747141246, -7.09676477294184 52.2574100269129, -7.09674276511356 52.257390021014, -7.09671660556669 52.257347906695, -7.09670574167468 52.2573294269651, -7.09664181028753 52.2572508758079, -7.09661278541458 52.2572131054317, -7.09658610916317 52.2571876363037, -7.09658601566524 52.2571875519918, -7.0965429287503 52.2571316980609, -7.09640513308887 52.2569970878473, -7.09637219251436 52.2569710277968, -7.0962381326237 52.2568455894489, -7.09622319512244 52.256833253839, -7.09619038549837 52.2567958633748, -7.09615890795537 52.2567699744652, -7.09611282934773 52.2567243564596, -7.09508060715468 52.2556745243583, -7.09508053683882 52.2556744528073, -7.09436822093307 52.2549434515412, -7.09375929976126 52.2543300400339, -7.09212843661217 52.2526889723832, -7.09208096462781 52.2526389078202, -7.09087784702595 52.252202133629, -7.09053741755983 52.2520929888888, -7.0901531054941 52.2519760406043, -7.08967023559957 52.2518631114033, -7.08954131697658 52.2518401762865, -7.08910022950806 52.2517668564518, -7.08877424171529 52.251714588182, -7.08858711385384 52.2516916926033, -7.08811225623969 52.2516466264634, -7.08753914419072 52.2516240928123, -7.0875349194518 52.2516239900455, -7.08740902897142 52.2516272938617, -7.08725138676703 52.2516314091502, -7.08654471989089 52.2516651151481, -7.0864039433092 52.2516824458133, -7.08576879512775 52.2517828794409, -7.08539391824005 52.2518589223995, -7.08485700984063 52.2519883363651, -7.08451860477736 52.2520862065124, -7.08451329642103 52.2520877995261, -7.08405987576073 52.2522360202015, -7.08396274233773 52.2522677775298, -7.08392271516596 52.2522847894086, -7.08376709854903 52.252352108496, -7.08357081527608 52.2524405690599, -7.08347506745774 52.2524844357768, -7.0834625755182 52.2524905510103, -7.08329861479558 52.2525708062179, -7.0832968391714 52.2525716823294, -7.08282985274877 52.2528154822825, -7.08228769443545 52.2530838757204, -7.08207865987241 52.2531983581716, -7.08205446260151 52.2532116102024, -7.0820535337606 52.2532120479298, -7.08195871348638 52.253257301325, -7.08189989179864 52.2532853701075, -7.08189769365599 52.2532864190942, -7.08187166556037 52.2532974671585, -7.08169678274095 52.2533716980519, -7.08113402773075 52.2536439880711, -7.08106411853981 52.2536720034004, -7.08086307468902 52.2537525679385, -7.08055949634621 52.2538829509144, -7.08028064696027 52.2540006087438, -7.08017020162755 52.2540468158482, -7.08016471698864 52.2540489106709, -7.08016452054366 52.2540489900402, -7.07986317854656 52.2541641102568, -7.07952573604749 52.2542965709428, -7.0793045143708 52.2543757395404, -7.07889565119367 52.2545284255113, -7.078889047032 52.2545308917699, -7.07871780813545 52.2545866314009, -7.07864061320475 52.2546117587451, -7.07863654310466 52.2546132281237, -7.0783941442385 52.2547007458106, -7.07836306936667 52.2547119649456, -7.07836247475163 52.254712174239, -7.07803429927503 52.2548243764658, -7.07765856045246 52.2549402251289, -7.07751324963888 52.2549850274594, -7.07743743203444 52.2550081584634, -7.07721552116253 52.2550758614461, -7.07687120800984 52.2551888206154, -7.07654679969658 52.255289391397, -7.07593727294559 52.2554789077855, -7.07515015030455 52.2557271466583, -7.07507350212722 52.2557503712168, -7.07498532018518 52.2557751593114, -7.07397861451329 52.2560721566712, -7.07379319208272 52.2561157957522, -7.07362189081807 52.2561567012661, -7.07318075352451 52.2562630848986, -7.07291548279223 52.2563091690336, -7.07258743436996 52.2563728270954, -7.07230900476229 52.2564215606945, -7.07211190873095 52.2564713392016, -7.07187403875476 52.2565362154728, -7.07187384731558 52.2565362643056, -7.07178020505339 52.2565516137059, -7.07158210704589 52.256584083452, -7.07123607013629 52.2566254459042, -7.07123570295244 52.2566254933533, -7.0708088062796 52.2566859562008, -7.07066457629092 52.2566982746127, -7.07054049061241 52.2567088718662, -7.07050602446735 52.2567118158408, -7.07037627292994 52.2567243063172, -7.06992606213791 52.2567699278224, -7.06609887514843 52.2565373216373, -7.06579377243036 52.256576652143, -7.06470337474921 52.2566961248201, -7.06438512723379 52.2567314409852, -7.06396045094331 52.2567685930075, -7.06349262275335 52.2567885830052, -7.06263199090322 52.2568776176237, -7.0587694701651 52.2568100811066, -7.05855327367549 52.2568060525379, -7.05855215981477 52.2568060130934, -7.05747839339272 52.2567679746887, -7.05440653452136 52.2565290850539, -7.051602982741 52.2563052671851, -7.05139072098035 52.2563017730592, -7.05135101937023 52.2562998836895, -7.05124436410803 52.2562948081403, -7.05094206864657 52.2562765948282, -7.05092754805531 52.2562757221328, -7.0507267909265 52.2562619272351, -7.05066932332744 52.2562579783521, -7.05053514492724 52.2562468883969, -7.04996293710242 52.256197221129, -7.04958916485914 52.2561695831715, -7.04941316429943 52.2561530558503, -7.04924480334538 52.2561372459791, -7.04893760996525 52.2561141781248, -7.04630770451211 52.2559035846841, -7.04483057826407 52.255777430094, -7.04384410773259 52.2557099131108, -7.04384317032921 52.2557098434954, -7.04294712479919 52.2556404580261, -7.04275468360073 52.2556304158982, -7.0419123250986 52.2557676875386, -7.04035421384483 52.2559999820229, -7.03794025802689 52.2563478467375, -7.03437273902562 52.2622985520166, -7.02620607824084 52.2691483971104, -7.00017208583225 52.2756998453633, -7.00082306423547 52.2783374757405, -7.0182111887618 52.296148598697, -7.0062474710841 52.306166540031, -7.00366002205693 52.3127475089272, -6.98852904858413 52.3189977381463, -6.98651609116327 52.3213655036173, -6.986125858399 52.3237035501409, -6.99357674158319 52.330624292002, -6.99346590663928 52.3397968844092, -6.99710331765196 52.3483756624102, -6.99311177184463 52.3615199703495, -6.98760127488479 52.3678291055553, -6.97038699963337 52.367260552989, -6.96503790395649 52.3683988834947, -6.96523362669462 52.3781608484585, -6.95372198151253 52.3903149919406, -6.95687286582569 52.3918874145601, -6.95566713983771 52.3989154391837, -6.94129749256921 52.4024907083612, -6.94183366406777 52.412214384529, -6.95684272476257 52.4161283259112, -6.96170393505834 52.4194663528682, -6.96134317063198 52.4216871625847, -6.95016139994769 52.4256642785873, -6.9455752854404 52.425060111974, -6.9409711531936 52.4217801747754, -6.9269747989152 52.4201828331375, -6.92539680673511 52.4247852427995, -6.91836195699965 52.4262007079485, -6.91562371356202 52.4284709016655, -6.91579080852248 52.4313105004966, -6.92103839177355 52.4337224887075, -6.92731215410713 52.4417007615607, -6.92339140204757 52.4512003577578, -6.92550383297271 52.4555469578241, -6.91501107666591 52.4605487364313, -6.91716508293663 52.463603846477, -6.92855962217942 52.4669590635331, -6.9325596147839 52.4659462052169, -6.93454882547565 52.4672664891364, -6.93317828562056 52.4691417826493, -6.92308851594385 52.4700800077546, -6.91859937882085 52.4752422879469, -6.91987262037565 52.4773286831775, -6.92757970102679 52.4802154494619, -6.9248444657248 52.4853439315102, -6.93372360817898 52.4892219789271, -6.94053449357389 52.4998570526557, -6.93300992071799 52.5169579427353, -6.93476716370196 52.5274255258983, -6.95255912492834 52.529847685109, -6.95952813697728 52.535916011632, -6.95361066821831 52.5400095439871, -6.94610740574846 52.5410669502601, -6.94543465981317 52.5463383478204, -6.9352109197125 52.5489187444962, -6.93111590366306 52.5541612603355, -6.92459527619031 52.5576805629144, -6.91910267118212 52.5583775264205, -6.91465712053416 52.5620519273372, -6.92237054250936 52.5696337484208, -6.91900645214778 52.5765797198213, -6.92609770125504 52.5872577858407, -6.93895070108753 52.5907167115428, -6.94615558742755 52.5969638972022))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "9": {
    "Question": "Where is Glyfada located?",
    "Query": "select ?geoWKT where {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Glyfada> geo:hasGeometry ?o.     ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "MULTIPOLYGON(((478838 4193957,478841.5 4193975,478848.5 4193999,478860.5 4194021,478873.09375 4194 4066,478883.59375 4194100,478895 4194142,478905.3125 4194184,478915.1875 4194234,478926.40625 4194288,478937.5 4194344,478951.3125 4194394,478968.8125 4194445,478988.40625 4194511,479012 4194573,479036.90625 4194630,479060.8125 4194681,479085.6875 4194737,479111.90625 4194794,479147.90625 4194863,479187.5 4194937,479231.09375 4195003,479278.59375 4195064,479323.90625 4195116,479364.40625 4195155,479403.8125 4195189,479439.6875 4195215,479471.6875 4195243,479509.90625 4195278,479551.8125 4195314,479592.40625 4195348,479639.5 4195382,479687.6875 4195415,479742.3125 4195447,479800.5 4195486,479862.59375 4195523,479922.3125 4195554,479980.6875 4195584,480033 4195607,480085.40625 4195629,480137.59375 4195655,480201.3125 4195679,480266.1875 4195703,480338.6875 4195727,480416.1875 4195751,480487.5 4195771,480553.90625 4195787,480610.5 4195794,480657.09375 4195796,480704.90625 4195799,480752.8125 4195799,480796.8125 4195802,480842.1875 4195803,480888.6875 4195808,480929 4195812,480974.3125 4195816,481027.09375 4195819,481086.1875 4195824,481150.3125 4195833,481217 4195836,481277.5 4195837,481343.09375 4195837,481408.59375 4195839,481471.5 4195844,481536.90625 4195851,481602.3125 4195855,481659.09375 4195854,481707.09375 4195852,481750 4195851,481787.8125 4195852,481823.09375 4195851,481860.90625 4195851,481896.3125 4195847,481935.5 4195842,481973.5 4195835,482011.5 4195829,482053.3125 4195821,482090 4195816,482124.1875 4195810,482164.8125 4195804,482209 4195800,482254.5 4195795,482300 4195791,482345.59375 4195785,482387.3125 4195781,482424 4195776,482454.5 4195766,482481.1875 4195757,482493.5 4195753,482477 4195725,482460.3125 4195693,482438.40625 4195661,482420.1875 4195634,482401.90625 4195611,482385 4195586,482361.90625 4195554,482343.6875 4195527,482324.1875 4195502,482321 4195480,482318.09375 4195447,482332 4195400,482346.8125 4195365,482357.6875 4195336,482368.6875 4195302,482377.09375 4195270,482382.6875 4195249,482387.5 4195212,482397.8125 4195159,482409.3125 4195106,482421.8125 4195063,482430 4195038,482438.3125 4195010,482447 4194968,482459.6875 4194921,482472 4194883,482484.59375 4194839,482498.59375 4194787,482513.8125 4194738,482532.90625 4194684,482556 4194622,482577.8125 4194561,482593.90625 4194524,482614.6875 4194501,482641.59375 4194487,482667.09375 4194476,482687.5 4194469,482710.40625 4194459,482738.5 4194446,482762.8125 4194433,482785.90625 4194419,482807.59375 4194408,482830.59375 4194398,482869 4194376,482896.09375 4194353,482920.8125 4194327,482937.8125 4194303,482955 4194272,483000.1875 4194186,483013.8125 4194150,483031.1875 4194112,483051.40625 4194065,483072.8125 4194017,483093.09375 4193968,483109.3125 4193927,483125.40625 4193893,483139.1875 4193847,483155.59375 4193801,483168 4193761,483176.09375 4193742,483177.8125 4193678,483175.90625 4193655,483166.90625 4193615,483158.6875 4193594,483115 4193576,483088.8125 4193566,483061.40625 4193553,483040.3125 4193542,483009.3125 4193524,482971 4193495,482928.8125 4193468,482884.3125 4193436,482843.5 4193407,482801.3125 4193381,482762.90625 4193355,482717 4193327,482668.8125 4193292,482625.5 4193263,482582.1875 4193231,482546.3125 4193205,482516.6875 4193183,482479.59375 4193156,482429.09375 4193112,482381 4193071,482336.59375 4193035,482306.90625 4193015,482287 4193003,482252.40625 4192977,482225.40625 4192952,482190.8125 4192924,482148.90625 4192888,482110.59375 4192859,482072.3125 4192832,482033.90625 4192807,481995.5 4192780,481951.09375 4192745,481901.5 4192712,481853.1875 4192681,481807.3125 4192654,481771.3125 4192632,481746.59375 4192615,481720.6875 4192594,481687.40625 4192563,481653 4192531,481621 4192502,481591.6875 4192468,481559.8125 4192434,481529.1875 4192400,481503.6875 4192365,481490.40625 4192343,481483.40625 4192321,481477.90625 4192290,481473.5 4192270,481470.3125 4192245,481464.90625 4192213,481464.40625 4192186,481467.90625 4192150,481472.59375 4192114,481478.40625 4192088,481482.90625 4192061,481488.5 4192039,481507.90625 4191974,481533.3125 4191920,481553.3125 4191880,481566.8125 4191848,481581.59375 4191815,481596.09375 4191791,481612.09375 4191758,481629.40625 4191725,481647.90625 4191693,481666.59375 4191655,481689.09375 4191613,481709.3125 4191566,481729.1875 4191530,481746.59375 4191494,481761.3125 4191460,481742.6875 4191449,481730.59375 4191432,481713.59375 4191406,481700.1875 4191390,481677.1875 4191355,481652.90625 4191321,481640.8125 4191301,481620.1875 4191270,481603.3125 4191244,481581.59375 4191206,481557.6875 4191159,481538.59375 4191120,481522.90625 4191091,481502.3125 4191063,481480.5 4191030,481458.6875 4190995,481438.3125 4190957,481426.40625 4190929,481414.5 4190905,481401.40625 4190877,481386.09375 4190837,481366 4190785,481346.09375 4190730,481332.1875 4190686,481318 4190649,481305 4190617,481290.8125 4190584,481274 4190551,481252.3125 4190517,481227.90625 4190484,481198.5 4190453,481164 4190424,481130.59375 4190399,481093.5 4190372,481055.09375 4190347,481012.90625 4190322,480968.09375 4190302,480919.40625 4190282,480875.6875 4190268,480829.1875 4190264,480781.3125 4190262,480737.3125 4190256,480697.3125 4190242,480667.59375 4190222,480644.5 4190193,480624.1875 4190150,480603.8125 4190113,480584.40625 4190081,480561.40625 4190046,480525.6875 4190017,480481 4189990,480428.8125 4189961,480376.8125 4189928,480336.1875 4189892,480305.3125 4189865,480281.90625 4189845,480256 4189825,480217.6875 4189797,480175.6875 4189763,480131.3125 4189727,480092.40625 4189674,480058.5 4189623,480033.09375 4189583,480011.40625 4189546,479995.8125 4189514,479982.90625 4189481,479967.5 4189444,479954.6875 4189404,479945.3125 4189379,479914.1875 4189363,479877.8125 4189359,479837.3125 4189360,479790.8125 4189359,479741.6875 4189356,479691.3125 4189353,479645.90625 4189352,479604.40625 4189350,479562.8125 4189350,479517.40625 4189348,479469.40625 4189352,479419 4189352,479362.3125 4189353,479297.8125 4189360,479224.59375 4189363,479153.90625 4189366,479087 4189366,479013.8125 4189368,478939.3125 4189375,478873.6875 4189377,478808 4189381,478744.90625 4189383,478679.3125 4189384,478618.90625 4189381,478563.5 4189376,478513.1875 4189372,478449 4189371,478378.5 4189366,478311.8125 4189363,478253.90625 4189357,478196 4189354,478150.59375 4189353,478112.8125 4189355,478082.40625 4189357,478055.90625 4189360,478016.8125 4189362,477961.5 4189355,477902.3125 4189349,477850.8125 4189343,477818.1875 4189338,477807.8125 4189338,477294.6875 4189338,477290 4189364,477249.40625 4189381,477226.3125 4189445,477215.90625 4189511,477223.3125 4189557,477252.5 4189574,477285.40625 4189586,477324.59375 4189626,477365.1875 4189629,477404.5 4189634,477424.6875 4189653,477424.5 4189694,477409.1875 4189729,477400.1875 4189761,477415.40625 4189769,477424.3125 4189766,477439.6875 4189719,477447.5 4189660,477462.90625 4189620,477488.3125 4189599,477520.09375 4189586,477554.40625 4189576,477597.59375 4189564,477616.6875 4189551,477642 4189568,477677.40625 4189588,477707.8125 4189587,477754 4189608,477772.59375 4189584,477775.40625 4189577,477791.8125 4189603,477808.59375 4189636,477810.8125 4189640,477833.5 4189677,477851.1875 4189715,477861.1875 4189757,477868.6875 4189792,477873.6875 4189819,477878.6875 4189857,477878.59375 4189876,477877.3125 4189892,477867.09375 4189912,477854.3125 4189931,477842.8125 4189944,477839 4189951,477828.8125 4189963,477809.40625 4189952,477783.09375 4189936,477775.40625 4189949,477765.1875 4189941,477754.6875 4189958,477776.09375 4189973,477786.59375 4189957,477808.40625 4189973,477809.5 4189974,477813.5 4189979,477809.5 4189986,477805.8125 4189992,477803.1875 4190002,477805.6875 4190019,477787.90625 4190025,477773.90625 4190027,477774.90625 4190037,477776.8125 4190060,477766.3125 4190061,477754.8125 4190044,477745 4190023,477741.40625 4190003,477727.5 4189992,477719.8125 4189994,477716.5 4190004,477715.59375 4190015,477710.6875 4190035,477703.40625 4190047,477692.09375 4190065,477678.09375 4190086,477666.59375 4190104,477636 4190131,477605.5 4190150,477592.8125 4190157,477576.3125 4190160,477567.8125 4190163,477551.3125 4190182,477544.8125 4190204,477544.8125 4190213,477557.40625 4190226,477571.40625 4190232,477568.8125 4190249,477557.3125 4190259,477539.5 4190261,477507.8125 4190259,477500.3125 4190247,477495.3125 4190236,477492.8125 4190215,477491.59375 4190195,477496.8125 4190175,477510.8125 4190158,477519.6875 4190146,477528.59375 4190129,477519.8125 4190113,477497 4190123,477480.40625 4190148,477468.90625 4190166,477468.8125 4190195,477477.5 4190227,477485 4190252,477488.8125 4190269,477488.8125 4190278,477468.40625 4190299,477442.90625 4190318,477420.09375 4190331,477399.6875 4190337,477385.8125 4190337,477371.90625 4190320,477365.59375 4190310,477345.3125 4190306,477342.8125 4190316,477350.3125 4190327,477356.59375 4190336,477347.6875 4190351,477334.90625 4190367,477333.59375 4190394,477346.1875 4190416,477361.3125 4190432,477370.09375 4190454,477364.90625 4190477,477347.09375 4190499,477328 4190508,477292.59375 4190503,477273.5 4190513,477249.3125 4190523,477234.1875 4190518,477224.09375 4190490,477216.6875 4190443,477223.1875 4190405,477232.1875 4190364,477245.09375 4190321,477256.59375 4190289,477261.6875 4190276,477278.3125 4190267,477294.8125 4190259,477310 4190257,477320.1875 4190244,477314 4190213,477260.8125 4190198,477229.09375 4190189,477201.09375 4190197,477184.40625 4190256,477175.3125 4190307,477167.5 4190369,477164.8125 4190406,477159.59375 4190452,477144.1875 4190491,477122.5 4190528,477099.59375 4190556,477085.5 4190571,477074 4190594,477051.09375 4190633,477015.40625 4190681,476977.1875 4190723,476953 4190747,476919.90625 4190776,476893.1875 4190789,476869.09375 4190793,476852.59375 4190798,476831 4190798,476805.59375 4190805,476779 4190797,476746.09375 4190769,476710.6875 4190746,476677.6875 4190744,476651.09375 4190750,476635.6875 4190794,476646.90625 4190835,476673.40625 4190887,476683.40625 4190911,476674.40625 4190958,476641.3125 4190998,476609.40625 4191028,476577.59375 4191058,476540.8125 4191071,476512.90625 4191067,476465.8125 4191088,476425.1875 4191098,476380.8125 4191111,476338.8125 4191133,476304.5 4191169,476278.90625 4191220,476261 4191253,476258.5 4191259,476269.8125 4191271,476291.3125 4191286,476317.90625 4191295,476342.09375 4191290,476361.09375 4191276,476376.40625 4191262,476387.90625 4191247,476405.6875 4191223,476426.5 4191201,476449.90625 4191183,476475.59375 4191167,476503.1875 4191155,476532 4191147,476561.6875 4191143,476591.59375 4191143,476621.6875 4191146,476635.59375 4191151,476638 4191177,476623.90625 4191210,476602.3125 4191217,476561.6875 4191230,476544 4191230,476523.6875 4191228,476517.3125 4191228,476517.3125 4191249,476597.09375 4191253,476585.59375 4191276,476547.40625 4191317,476525.8125 4191333,476495.3125 4191334,476471.3125 4191327,476453.59375 4191311,476430.8125 4191295,476415.59375 4191292,476395.3125 4191306,476396.40625 4191344,476402.6875 4191365,476405.09375 4191384,476405.09375 4191400,476403.8125 4191408,476398.59375 4191417,476383 4191443,476365.09375 4191467,476345.09375 4191489,476323.1875 4191510,476299.59375 4191528,476274.40625 4191544,476247.8125 4191558,476220.09375 4191570,476210.59375 4191573,477020 4192400,477400 4192860,477818.09375 4193186,477823.5 4193190,477943 4193212,477983.1875 4193218,478025.8125 4193228,478074.8125 4193236,478125.09375 4193241,478172.8125 4193247,478219 4193263,478255 4193284,478288.5 4193304,478318.59375 4193310,478352.6875 4193310,478398.1875 4193304,478446.40625 4193293,478494.6875 4193278,478540.5 4193265,478579.90625 4193253,478616.6875 4193246,478655.8125 4193242,478692.5 4193236,478727.90625 4193235,478765.8125 4193233,478802.1875 4193240,478823.3125 4193248,478835.40625 4193267,478842.1875 4193298,478844.59375 4193348,478848.1875 4193401,478848.1875 4193449,478845.8125 4193491,478845.6875 4193542,478842.90625 4193597,478837.40625 4193661,478832 4193721,478829.5 4193769,478829.59375 4193811,478833.3125 4193861,478833.3125 4193906,478834.90625 4193941,478838 4193957)));http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/2100^^<http://strdf.di.uoa.gr/ontology#WKT><http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((23.7926273345947 37.870433807373,23. .7924175262452 37.8703346252443,23.7922801971437 37.8701820373536,23.7920875549316 37.8699493408203,23.791934967041 37.8698043823243,23.7916736602783 37.8694877624512,23.7913990020753 37.8691787719727,23.7912616729736 37.8689994812013,23.7910289764404 37.8687210083009,23.7908363342286 37.8684844970704,23.7905921936035 37.8681411743165,23.7903213500977 37.8677177429199,23.7901039123536 37.8673667907715,23.7899265289307 37.8671035766602,23.7896938323975 37.8668518066407,23.7894458770753 37.866554260254,23.7891998291016 37.8662376403809,23.788969039917 37.865894317627,23.7888336181641 37.8656425476074,23.7887001037598 37.8654251098633,23.7885513305664 37.8651733398438,23.7883777618409 37.8648147583008,23.7881507873536 37.8643455505371,23.787925720215 37.8638458251953,23.787769317627 37.8634490966797,23.7876091003419 37.8631172180177,23.7874622344971 37.8628273010254,23.7873020172119 37.8625297546388,23.7871112823486 37.862232208252,23.786865234375 37.8619270324708,23.7865886688232 37.861629486084,23.7862548828125 37.8613471984864,23.7858638763428 37.8610877990723,23.7854843139648 37.8608589172363,23.7850646972657 37.8606147766114,23.7846279144288 37.8603897094727,23.7841491699218 37.860164642334,23.7836399078369 37.8599815368653,23.7830867767335 37.8598022460937,23.7825908660889 37.8596725463867,23.7820625305176 37.8596382141114,23.7815170288086 37.8596191406249,23.7810173034668 37.859561920166,23.7805633544922 37.8594360351562,23.7802257537843 37.8592567443848,23.7799644470215 37.8589935302736,23.779733657837 37.8586044311525,23.7795028686524 37.8582725524903,23.7792835235596 37.8579826354982,23.7790241241456 37.8576660156251,23.7786178588867 37.8574028015138,23.7781105041505 37.8571586608887,23.7775192260742 37.8568992614746,23.7769279479981 37.8565979003906,23.7764682769776 37.856273651123,23.7761173248292 37.8560295104982,23.7758522033691 37.8558502197266,23.7755584716796 37.8556671142578,23.7751235961915 37.8554153442382,23.7746467590333 37.8551063537599,23.7741432189941 37.8547821044922,23.77370262146 37.8543014526367,23.7733173370361 37.853843688965,23.7730312347412 37.8534812927246,23.7727851867677 37.8531494140625,23.7726078033447 37.8528594970704,23.7724628448487 37.8525619506835,23.772289276123 37.8522262573242,23.772144317627 37.8518676757813,23.7720375061035 37.8516426086427,23.7716846466065 37.8514976501466,23.7712707519532 37.8514595031739,23.7708110809326 37.8514671325685,23.7702827453614 37.8514595031739,23.7697238922119 37.8514289855958,23.7691516876221 37.851402282715,23.7686367034913 37.8513908386231,23.7681636810303 37.8513717651368,23.7676906585693 37.8513717651368,23.7671756744386 37.8513526916504,23.7666301727295 37.8513870239259,23.7660560607911 37.8513870239259,23.7654113769532 37.8513946533204,23.7646789550782 37.8514556884766,23.7638473510743 37.8514823913575,23.7630424499513 37.851505279541,23.7622833251954 37.851505279541,23.7614498138428 37.8515205383301,23.7606029510499 37.8515815734864,23.7598571777344 37.8516006469726,23.759111404419 37.8516349792481,23.7583942413331 37.8516502380372,23.7576484680176 37.8516578674318,23.7569618225097 37.8516273498536,23.7563323974609 37.8515815734864,23.7557601928711 37.8515472412111,23.7550296783447 37.8515357971191,23.7542285919191 37.8514900207521,23.7534713745117 37.8514595031739,23.7528133392333 37.8514060974122,23.7521553039552 37.851375579834,23.7516384124757 37.8513641357423,23.7512092590333 37.8513832092285,23.7508640289307 37.8513984680176,23.7505626678467 37.8514251708984,23.7501182556152 37.8514442443848,23.7494888305664 37.8513793945314,23.7488174438478 37.8513221740722,23.7482318878174 37.8512687683107,23.747859954834 37.8512229919434,23.7477436065675 37.8512229919434,23.7420806884766 37.8512115478517,23.7420806884766 37.8520889282227,23.7429161071777 37.8520851135253,23.7429161071777 37.8523597717286,23.743190765381 37.8523597717286,23.743190765381 37.8539123535156,23.743190765381 37.8540306091309,23.7429161071777 37.8540267944337,23.7429161071777 37.8545837402344,23.742359161377 37.8545837402344,23.742359161377 37.8548622131348,23.742639541626 37.8548583984375,23.742639541626 37.8551406860352,23.7429199218751 37.8551406860352,23.7429199218751 37.8554191589356,23.7431945800781 37.8554153442382,23.7431945800781 37.8556938171388,23.7434730529785 37.8556938171388,23.7434730529785 37.8559722900392,23.7440280914307 37.8559722900392,23.7440280914307 37.8562507629396,23.7445831298829 37.8562507629396,23.7445831298829 37.856803894043,23.7448616027833 37.8568000793458,23.7448616027833 37.8576393127441,23.7454204559326 37.8576393127441,23.7454166412355 37.8573608398438,23.7456951141358 37.8573608398438,23.7456951141358 37.856803894043,23.7459716796876 37.856803894043,23.7459716796876 37.8562507629396,23.746250152588 37.8562507629396,23.746250152588 37.8559684753419,23.7465286254884 37.8559722900392,23.7465286254884 37.8556938171388,23.74680519104 37.8556938171388,23.74680519104 37.8554153442382,23.747917175293 37.8554153442382,23.747917175293 37.8556938171388,23.7484703063965 37.8556900024415,23.7484703063965 37.8562507629396,23.7490272521973 37.8562507629396,23.7490272521973 37.85652923584,23.7495822906495 37.85652923584,23.7495822906495 37.856803894043,23.7501392364503 37.856803894043,23.7501392364503 37.8570823669434,23.7504196166992 37.8570785522462,23.7504196166992 37.8582000732422,23.7501392364503 37.8582000732422,23.7501392364503 37.8584709167481,23.7495803833009 37.8584709167481,23.7495822906495 37.8587493896485,23.7490291595459 37.8587493896485,23.7490291595459 37.8590316772462,23.7479190826417 37.8590316772462,23.7479190826417 37.8593101501466,23.7476387023926 37.8593063354493,23.7476406097413 37.8598594665528,23.7473602294922 37.8598594665528,23.7473602294922 37.8601417541504,23.746530532837 37.8601417541504,23.746530532837 37.8598594665528,23.7454166412355 37.8598594665528,23.7454166412355 37.8609733581544,23.7451381683351 37.8609733581544,23.7451381683351 37.8618049621581,23.7443046569825 37.8618049621581,23.7443046569825 37.8615264892578,23.744031906128 37.8615303039551,23.744031906128 37.8612518310547,23.7434673309326 37.8612518310547,23.7434673309326 37.860969543457,23.7425117492676 37.860969543457,23.7420806884766 37.860969543457,23.7420825958252 37.8612518310547,23.7418079376222 37.8612518310547,23.7418079376222 37.8617286682129,23.7418079376222 37.8620834350587,23.7415294647218 37.8620834350587,23.7415294647218 37.8623619079591,23.7418098449708 37.8623580932618,23.7418098449708 37.8629188537599,23.7415294647218 37.8629150390625,23.7415294647218 37.8631935119629,23.741247177124 37.8631896972657,23.741247177124 37.8637504577637,23.740972518921 37.8637504577637,23.740972518921 37.8645820617676,23.7406902313233 37.8645782470703,23.7406940460206 37.8651390075684,23.7404193878174 37.8651390075684,23.7404193878174 37.8654212951661,23.740140914917 37.8654212951661,23.740140914917 37.8656997680665,23.7398605346681 37.8656997680665,23.7398605346681 37.8659706115724,23.7393054962159 37.8659706115724,23.7393054962159 37.8662490844728,23.7381992340089 37.8662490844728,23.7381896972656 37.8665313720703,23.7376403808594 37.8665313720703,23.7376403808594 37.8662490844728,23.7373600006104 37.8662490844728,23.7373600006104 37.8659706115724,23.7370796203614 37.8659706115724,23.7370796203614 37.8656997680665,23.7356891632081 37.8656997680665,23.7356891632081 37.8668098449707,23.7359714508057 37.8668060302736,23.7359714508057 37.8673629760743,23.7362499237061 37.8673629760743,23.7362499237061 37.8681945800781,23.7365283966064 37.8681945800781,23.7365283966064 37.8693046569824,23.7362499237061 37.8693046569824,23.7362499237061 37.8695831298828,23.7356948852538 37.8695831298828,23.7356948852538 37.8693046569824,23.7354164123535 37.8693046569824,23.7354164123535 37.869026184082,23.7348594665527 37.8690299987794,23.7348594665527 37.868751525879,23.7345790863038 37.868751525879,23.7345790863038 37.8690299987794,23.7333526611329 37.869026184082,23.732915878296 37.869026184082,23.732915878296 37.8691749572754,23.732915878296 37.8693046569824,23.7323627471924 37.8693046569824,23.7323627471924 37.8695831298828,23.7320823669434 37.8695793151857,23.732084274292 37.8701400756836,23.7318058013916 37.8701400756836,23.7318058013916 37.8709716796876,23.7320823669434 37.8709716796876,23.7320823669434 37.8715286254883,23.7326393127442 37.8715286254883,23.7326393127442 37.8718109130861,23.732915878296 37.8718070983887,23.7329196929932 37.8723602294923,23.7326393127442 37.8723602294923,23.7326393127442 37.8726387023927,23.7323627471924 37.8726387023927,23.7323627471924 37.8731994628906,23.731809616089 37.8731956481935,23.7386913299562 37.8787994384766,23.7429962158203 37.8829574584962,23.7477416992188 37.8859062194824,23.7478027343751 37.8859405517578,23.7491607666016 37.8861427307129,23.7496185302734 37.8861961364747,23.7501029968261 37.886287689209,23.7506599426271 37.886360168457,23.7512302398682 37.8864059448243,23.7517738342286 37.8864631652832,23.7522983551027 37.8866081237792,23.75270652771 37.8867988586425,23.7530879974366 37.8869781494141,23.7534294128419 37.887035369873,23.7538166046144 37.887035369873,23.7543354034424 37.8869819641113,23.7548828125001 37.8868827819825,23.7554340362549 37.8867492675781,23.7559547424318 37.8866348266602,23.7564029693604 37.8865280151367,23.7568206787111 37.8864631652832,23.7572669982911 37.8864288330079,23.7576847076415 37.8863754272461,23.7580871582032 37.8863677978516,23.7585182189941 37.8863525390625,23.7589321136475 37.8864135742188,23.7591705322266 37.8864860534669,23.7593078613282 37.8866577148439,23.7593841552734 37.8869400024414,23.7594108581544 37.8873901367188,23.7594490051269 37.887866973877,23.7594490051269 37.888298034668,23.7594203948975 37.8886795043946,23.7594165802002 37.8891372680665,23.7593841552734 37.889633178711,23.7593193054199 37.8902091979982,23.759256362915 37.8907508850099,23.7592258453369 37.8911819458008,23.7592258453369 37.8915634155274,23.7592678070069 37.8920135498048,23.7592658996582 37.8924179077148,23.759283065796 37.8927345275879,23.7593173980713 37.8928794860841,23.7593574523926 37.8930397033693,23.7594356536866 37.8932571411133,23.7595710754395 37.8934555053712,23.759714126587 37.8938598632813,23.7598323822023 37.8941688537598,23.7599601745607 37.8945465087891,23.7600765228271 37.8949241638184,23.7601871490479 37.895378112793,23.7603130340576 37.8958625793458,23.7604370117189 37.8963699340821,23.7605934143066 37.8968200683594,23.7607917785645 37.8972778320313,23.7610111236573 37.8978729248047,23.7612781524659 37.8984336853027,23.7615604400635 37.8989486694336,23.7618312835693 37.8994102478027,23.7621116638183 37.8999137878419,23.7624092102051 37.9004287719726,23.7628154754639 37.9010505676271,23.7632637023925 37.9017181396486,23.7637577056886 37.902313232422,23.7642974853517 37.9028663635254,23.7648105621338 37.9033355712891,23.7652702331544 37.9036865234375,23.7657165527344 37.903995513916,23.7661247253417 37.9042282104493,23.7664871215821 37.9044837951661,23.7669219970704 37.9048004150392,23.76739692688 37.9051246643066,23.7678585052491 37.9054336547852,23.7683925628663 37.9057388305665,23.7689399719239 37.9060363769532,23.7695598602296 37.9063262939454,23.7702217102051 37.906681060791,23.7709274291993 37.9070167541503,23.7716045379639 37.9072952270507,23.772268295288 37.9075660705568,23.7728633880615 37.9077758789063,23.773458480835 37.9079742431641,23.7740516662598 37.9082107543946,23.7747745513917 37.9084281921387,23.7755126953126 37.9086456298828,23.7763366699219 37.9088630676271,23.7772178649902 37.9090843200685,23.7780284881592 37.9092636108398,23.7787837982178 37.9094085693359,23.779426574707 37.9094734191896,23.779956817627 37.9094924926758,23.7805004119873 37.909523010254,23.7810459136963 37.909523010254,23.7815456390381 37.9095497131348,23.7820625305176 37.9095611572267,23.7825908660889 37.9096069335938,23.7830505371094 37.9096412658693,23.7835655212403 37.9096794128417,23.7841663360597 37.9097099304199,23.7848377227784 37.9097557067872,23.7855663299562 37.9098358154297,23.7863254547119 37.9098663330079,23.7870140075684 37.9098739624024,23.7877597808839 37.9098777770996,23.7885055541993 37.909896850586,23.7892208099366 37.9099426269532,23.7899646759033 37.9100074768068,23.7907085418702 37.9100456237794,23.7913551330566 37.9100379943849,23.7919006347657 37.9100189208984,23.7923889160156 37.9100112915039,23.792818069458 37.9100227355958,23.7932205200196 37.9100112915039,23.793649673462 37.9100151062013,23.7940521240236 37.9099769592286,23.7944984436036 37.9099349975587,23.7949314117432 37.909870147705,23.7953643798829 37.9098167419435,23.7958393096924 37.9097480773926,23.796257019043 37.9097023010254,23.7966461181641 37.9096488952638,23.7971076965333 37.909595489502,23.7976112365723 37.9095611572267,23.7981281280518 37.9095153808594,23.79864692688 37.9094810485841,23.7991657257081 37.9094276428223,23.7996406555177 37.9093933105468,23.8000583648682 37.9093475341798,23.8004055023194 37.9092597961427,23.800708770752 37.9091796875001,23.8008480072023 37.9091415405274,23.8006610870361 37.9088897705078,23.8004722595215 37.9085998535157,23.8002243041992 37.9083137512208,23.8000183105469 37.9080696105958,23.799810409546 37.9078598022462,23.799617767334 37.9076347351074,23.7993564605713 37.9073448181153,23.799150466919 37.9071044921874,23.7989292144775 37.9068756103517,23.7988929748536 37.9066772460939,23.7988605499269 37.906379699707,23.799020767212 37.9059562683106,23.7991905212403 37.9056434631349,23.7993144989015 37.9053802490236,23.7994403839112 37.9050750732422,23.7995357513429 37.9047889709473,23.7996006011964 37.904598236084,23.7996559143068 37.9042663574219,23.799774169922 37.9037857055665,23.7999076843262 37.9033088684083,23.8000507354736 37.9029235839844,23.8001441955567 37.9026985168458,23.8002395629883 37.9024467468262,23.8003387451173 37.9020652770996,23.8004837036133 37.9016418457031,23.8006248474122 37.9013023376465,23.8007698059083 37.9009056091308,23.8009300231934 37.9004364013671,23.801103591919 37.8999938964845,23.8013229370117 37.8995094299317,23.8015880584718 37.8989486694336,23.801836013794 37.8983993530273,23.8020210266113 37.8980674743652,23.8022575378419 37.8978614807128,23.8025646209718 37.8977355957032,23.8028545379639 37.8976364135742,23.8030872344971 37.8975753784179,23.8033466339112 37.8974838256837,23.8036670684814 37.8973693847657,23.8039436340332 37.8972511291505,23.8042068481445 37.8971252441407,23.8044548034667 37.8970260620117,23.8047161102295 37.8969383239746,23.8051528930664 37.8967399597168,23.8054618835449 37.8965339660645,23.8057441711427 37.8962974548341,23.8059368133545 37.8960838317872,23.8061332702638 37.8958015441895,23.8066501617433 37.8950309753418,23.8068046569824 37.8947067260742,23.8070049285889 37.8943634033203,23.8072357177734 37.8939399719239,23.8074798583984 37.8935089111329,23.807710647583 37.8930664062501,23.8078975677491 37.8926963806153,23.8080806732179 37.892391204834,23.8082389831544 37.8919754028321,23.8084259033203 37.8915634155274,23.8085689544678 37.8912010192871,23.8086605072023 37.8910293579103,23.8086814880371 37.890453338623,23.8086605072023 37.8902473449707,23.8085594177247 37.8898849487306,23.8084659576416 37.8896980285645,23.8079700469971 37.8895339965821,23.8076725006104 37.8894424438477,23.8073616027832 37.8893241882324,23.8071212768555 37.8892250061036,23.8067684173585 37.8890609741212,23.8063335418702 37.888801574707,23.8058547973634 37.8885574340821,23.8053493499756 37.8882675170898,23.8048858642579 37.8880043029785,23.8044071197509 37.8877716064454,23.8039703369142 37.8875350952149,23.8034496307374 37.8872833251953,23.8029022216797 37.8869667053224,23.8024101257324 37.8867034912109,23.8019180297852 37.8864135742188,23.8015117645264 37.8861770629883,23.8011741638185 37.8859786987305,23.8007545471192 37.8857345581056,23.8001804351808 37.88533782959,23.7996349334717 37.8849678039551,23.7991313934327 37.8846435546875,23.7987937927246 37.8844604492188,23.7985668182374 37.8843536376954,23.7981739044189 37.8841171264649,23.7978687286378 37.8838920593263,23.7974758148193 37.8836402893067,23.7969989776611 37.8833122253419,23.796564102173 37.8830528259278,23.7961292266846 37.8828086853027,23.7956943511963 37.8825798034669,23.7952575683594 37.8823356628419,23.7947540283204 37.882022857666,23.7941913604737 37.8817214965821,23.7936420440674 37.8814430236818,23.7931213378906 37.8811988830567,23.7927131652833 37.8810005187989,23.7924308776857 37.8808441162109,23.7921371459962 37.880657196045,23.7917594909669 37.8803749084473,23.7913703918458 37.8800849914552,23.7910060882568 37.8798255920411,23.7906742095947 37.8795166015625,23.7903118133545 37.8792114257814,23.7899646759033 37.8789024353028,23.7896766662598 37.8785858154297,23.7895259857178 37.8783874511719,23.7894458770753 37.8781890869141,23.7893848419189 37.8779106140137,23.7893352508545 37.8777313232421,23.7892990112304 37.8775062561035,23.7892379760743 37.8772163391114,23.789234161377 37.8769721984864,23.7892742156982 37.8766479492188,23.7893295288086 37.8763236999512,23.7893962860109 37.876091003418,23.7894477844238 37.875846862793,23.7895107269288 37.8756484985352,23.7897338867188 37.8750648498536,23.7900238037111 37.8745765686036,23.7902526855468 37.8742179870605,23.7904071807862 37.8739280700684,23.7905750274659 37.8736305236816,23.7907409667969 37.8734169006349,23.7909240722657 37.873119354248,23.7911224365235 37.8728218078614,23.791332244873 37.8725318908691,23.7915458679199 37.8721923828126,23.7918033599855 37.8718147277833,23.79203414917 37.8713912963868,23.7922611236572 37.8710670471192,23.792459487915 37.8707427978516,23.7926273345947 37.870433807373))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "10": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Regional unit of Hmathia ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?pop WHERE{ <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gagentity_201> y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?pop }",
    "Answer": "pop 125717^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "11": {
    "Question": "What is location of the county Cambridge?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?geoWKT where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cambridge> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "geoWKT <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((0.408932 52.0593605,0.39305601 52.05... more  <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-0.121026797610404 52.0195117567867,... more"
  },
  "12": {
    "Question": "What is the total area of Glengarra Wood forest?",
    "Query": "select distinct (strdf:area(?geoWKT) as ?area) where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Glengarra_Wood_3300941> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "area 7.642593700438738E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "13": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Piraeus?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population WHERE {         yago:Piraeus y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population     }",
    "Answer": "175697^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "14": {
    "Question": "What is the total area of Cambridge?",
    "Query": "SELECT (strdf:area(?WKT) AS ?totalArea) WHERE {         yago:Cambridge geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT    }",
    "Answer": "0.6051532626152039^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> 0.40279582142829895^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "15": {
    "Question": "Where is Dublin located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?WKT WHERE {         yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT }",
    "Answer": "MULTIPOLYGON (((-6.16321572721054 53.3411099322235, -6.16412004567249 53.3411312746422, -6.1650334 45201099 53.3410907265272, -6.16321572721054 53.3411099322235)), ((-6.16321572721054 53.3411099322235, -6.15963574670632 53.3410253748237, -6.15119224978705 53.3422217066927, -6.16321572721054 53.3411099322235)), ((-6.17041344373788 53.3675229764706, -6.17827038382959 53.3602001552808, -6.18946440069435 53.3559136072047, -6.18745838923483 53.3541031722344, -6.18337674671535 53.3545386312336, -6.16634985360809 53.3498471271997, -6.16436793564919 53.3516617934563, -6.15916858246556 53.3494803691844, -6.15368346134789 53.3543741090555, -6.16294312713314 53.3549997046466, -6.15359142697036 53.3544548015359, -6.14264528398378 53.3634342217828, -6.1221583984524 53.3720170532807, -6.12822831187499 53.375710451491, -6.11683514529695 53.3796924072723, -6.11311239825096 53.3828505206845, -6.13495797727933 53.3798013985404, -6.14346377253376 53.3851508380182, -6.15742495433882 53.3903242423601, -6.1504631190924 53.3976457603725, -6.14879781023651 53.4044189959273, -6.15038497653722 53.407408406266, -6.16502209319504 53.4093002852306, -6.1729329970132 53.4066259483848, -6.18621040949124 53.4061191397722, -6.2256949812171 53.4109918296153, -6.23689653391978 53.3970352023947, -6.24412097484046 53.3985417395989, -6.245045754894 53.3973239917349, -6.2685336309519 53.4022198969062, -6.27160327817637 53.4054651472848, -6.29168848233545 53.4066143356411, -6.29132167760266 53.3980298747266, -6.30279119862263 53.4002375748968, -6.30853203446628 53.4028533563497, -6.31419629924155 53.3993039730599, -6.31836172890629 53.4004189596646, -6.32203659134997 53.3796714709888, -6.33342355536386 53.3778760573717, -6.33181204273828 53.3721099480959, -6.33379457883054 53.3708309345967, -6.3492893856226 53.369641132392, -6.35633723810139 53.3582027181906, -6.3511660252043 53.3548669154391, -6.3568486236254 53.3522909019486, -6.35970327183145 53.3531222168612, -6.36287959978728 53.3452921848745, -6.36907260693226 53.3462678787283, -6.37048539262051 53.3436249003126, -6.37988885462401 53.3451322256696, -6.38352854267161 53.3427687658537, -6.38674532653159 53.3435696478271, -6.38701076512148 53.3400504981189, -6.37729043944229 53.3285406728533, -6.35065997106317 53.3317793809526, -6.35014649802516 53.3295969030476, -6.34527394344138 53.3275522994227, -6.34216784069831 53.321631070428, -6.34533310529079 53.3218990024953, -6.34513567499905 53.3206042334556, -6.34283890153932 53.3191734559991, -6.33548674527311 53.316838029604, -6.31704714785954 53.3163366956003, -6.29968948877873 53.3120250158386, -6.30276292028061 53.3099515355784, -6.29954663615957 53.3041082797501, -6.2919148977212 53.2988821203321, -6.28659501489505 53.3014015871036, -6.28486417869894 53.3049206771456, -6.268712135239 53.3037700463531, -6.2656614664389 53.3067061236014, -6.25994863419561 53.3061975686615, -6.25881306245672 53.3083997154029, -6.24917112574513 53.3082691717412, -6.24600255498122 53.312424570659, -6.23674047021921 53.3145255796481, -6.23342217002302 53.3148146126359, -6.23231068094223 53.3133266677678, -6.22982532197956 53.3142254602117, -6.22685463717355 53.3111630565816, -6.21761171430418 53.3099276191171, -6.21352928318048 53.3122095427016, -6.21084653053486 53.3107023043915, -6.20523254542793 53.3122549351324, -6.20055377335711 53.3118135700862, -6.18968672733358 53.3190630926537, -6.1967366200062 53.3245503092682, -6.19728498525843 53.3300591050368, -6.19420901098183 53.331459198916, -6.19639289843991 53.3296628025195, -6.19223163772431 53.3214421051712, -6.17995230990366 53.3180120119239, -6.17579225851181 53.3204826371879, -6.17142416316546 53.3274952522626, -6.17815987396583 53.3317254729205, -6.18942153640342 53.3343780037119, -6.19096456977451 53.3330274640265, -6.18967810415486 53.3343420707214, -6.19325749246267 53.3371800247016, -6.18875394290528 53.3343942937554, -6.17700035693118 53.3321510229062, -6.17074364596285 53.3281064285063, -6.16959502965894 53.3366039905007, -6.16503345201099 53.3410907265272, -6.19069856594654 53.3416382374073, -6.19338397650449 53.3397747445364, -6.19527737088337 53.3419124405653, -6.1986722766792 53.3406558475703, -6.20347496583396 53.3411445649411, -6.19890527086146 53.3406885590595, -6.1979401772816 53.3423651161471, -6.22711942335298 53.3449343084951, -6.22724244046334 53.3465015513396, -6.21633927379998 53.3457365234387, -6.22410117129159 53.3469674659425, -6.22278146625649 53.3494788628835, -6.22150992138244 53.3479739923839, -6.21885268150443 53.3477980920623, -6.22180373058997 53.3489160897889, -6.21592764837077 53.3486076632186, -6.21242379006433 53.3454470973279, -6.20033226445548 53.3451130817964, -6.19864285614728 53.3481191797157, -6.19758978825765 53.3449635441806, -6.19289025761119 53.3451560502879, -6.19332573349425 53.3482846642112, -6.18978354764911 53.3464779383633, -6.18929138343653 53.3504881009102, -6.19564287154825 53.3504060876906, -6.19593697922293 53.3532095133425, -6.20882743703341 53.3535657064037, -6.20643207061887 53.355004323704, -6.21299922610205 53.3577863567905, -6.20476761630561 53.3543286559716, -6.20351000869351 53.3557099971636, -6.20389772999153 53.3568382051062, -6.2061831574571 53.358212273416, -6.21229856714057 53.3585180150934, -6.20663137885824 53.3590823148611, -6.20308577100279 53.3568324246357, -6.20087744403396 53.3539285014026, -6.19820590897604 53.3572741476641, -6.18865720021646 53.3569749057778, -6.18356485021809 53.3597642802404, -6.17846045406249 53.3602948256801, -6.17041344373788 53.3675229764706), (-6.17041344373788 53.3675229764706, -6.170361077344 53.3676385682246, -6.16561816119442 53.3700144526787, -6.1668075002651 53.3711437977211, -6.16542932037061 53.3700460914443, -6.16197959749741 53.3727905640888, -6.163462685728 53.3708944938672, -6.16157296355717 53.3714505164353, -6.16136707929847 53.3715255923797, -6.16134183602492 53.3715185198131, -6.16117783248932 53.3715667717984, -6.1590813502135 53.3708851312543, -6.16134183602492 53.3715185198131, -6.16157296355717 53.3714505164353, -6.170361077344 53.3676385682246, -6.17035328257851 53.3675722271681, -6.17041344373788 53.3675229764706)))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "16": {
    "Question": "Where is Aghaboy located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?geoWKT WHERE {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Aghabog_2967065> geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . }",
    "Answer": "POLYGON ((-7.08559212234739 54.1496676183327, -7.09670697090401 54.1511959079075, -7.0974267311534 45 54.1507882250245, -7.09837393595031 54.1447837332511, -7.0922329905441 54.145577014771, -7.08559212234739 54.1496676183327))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>  <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-7.27688738926288 54.2036879084467,- -7.27627362786556 54.2037291464241,-7.27558590086369 54.2036126997171,-7.27448180202921 54.2032014609377,-7.271377754306 54.2032273754169,-7.27038039822205 54.2032887234427,-7.26995823702083 54.2033310899594,-7.26861729173939 54.2033226838109,-7.26762032690629 54.2033615488625,-7.26716534119165 54.203415745335,-7.26723487470194 54.2032865159732,-7.26846264417847 54.201001921907,-7.26866932079926 54.200149158282,-7.2704707309739 54.2000926975415,-7.27330363393619 54.2001996767336,-7.27523604795589 54.1992225298776,-7.27563037176248 54.1987965002187,-7.27618624172058 54.1992936553067,-7.27655871356345 54.1998354396752,-7.27709443721312 54.2006481098097,-7.27769204793511 54.2014428196138,-7.27722295354507 54.2019161171286,-7.27751067767895 54.2020798418689,-7.27764683020949 54.2021797630361,-7.2782354822587 54.2026420630349,-7.27887027723271 54.2031046373099,-7.27912620877985 54.2032874849604,-7.27856601801397 54.2034610443648,-7.27838466715637 54.2035171916671,-7.27769327083863 54.2036253582391,-7.27688738926288 54.2036879084467))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "17": {
    "Question": "Where is Taghsheenod located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?geoWKT WHERE {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Taghsheenod_2961290> geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . }",
    "Answer": "POLYGON ((-7.71864376801813 53.6101345619359, -7.71414138067621 53.6079945810103, -7.7116119752556 69 53.6105526306587, -7.71298061638008 53.6152330099318, -7.71619357918323 53.6156283603318, -7.71520730731685 53.6134317259667, -7.71864376801813 53.6101345619359))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "18": {
    "Question": "What are the coordinates  Of Dimos Petroupoli?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?dimos_geoWKT WHERE {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Petroupoli> geo:hasGeometry ?dimos_geo .  ?dimos_geo geo:asWKT ?dimos_geoWKT . }",
    "Answer": "MULTIPOLYGON(((471709.90625 4212317,471922.59375 4212114,472023 4211962,472075.40625 4211797,47207 74 4211471,472107.6875 4211354,472369.5 4211112,472481.09375 4210901,472698.6875 4210645,473035 4210380,473102.8125 4210275,473029.8125 4210044,472820.1875 4209801,472692.1875 4209727,472569.59375 4209427,472459.1875 4209330,472312.6875 4209061,472201.59375 4209004,472092.3125 4208948,471999 4209002,471899.90625 4209180,471760.1875 4209310,471278.59375 4209285,470839.8125 4209376,470704 4209405,470271.90625 4209441,469867.8125 4209528,469669.8125 4209632,469666.3125 4209647,469592.8125 4209952,469600.59375 4210291,469626.3125 4210400,469660.3125 4210445,469818.3125 4210652,469893.1875 4211023,470431.8125 4211362,470834.5 4211564,470985.6875 4211739,471454.8125 4212075,471709.90625 4212317)));http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/2100^^<http://strdf.di.uoa.gr/ontology#WKT> <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((23.6832580566406 38.0283164978027,23 3.6820144653321 38.0278053283691,23.680950164795 38.0282897949219,23.6798133850098 38.0298919677736,23.6782169342042 38.0310592651368,23.6727294921876 38.030818939209,23.6677265167237 38.0316238403321,23.6661777496338 38.0318832397461,23.661252975464 38.0321922302246,23.6566448211671 38.0329627990723,23.6543846130371 38.0338935852051,23.6543445587158 38.0340309143068,23.6534938812256 38.0367736816407,23.6535682678224 38.0398292541504,23.6538562774659 38.040813446045,23.6542415618896 38.0412216186523,23.6560344696045 38.0430908203126,23.6568717956543 38.0464363098144,23.6629962921143 38.0495109558105,23.6675777435303 38.0513458251953,23.6692943572998 38.0529251098633,23.6746273040771 38.0559692382813,23.6775245666504 38.0581588745118,23.6799583435059 38.0563354492188,23.6811084747315 38.0549697875977,23.6817111968995 38.0534820556641,23.6817092895509 38.0505447387695,23.6820964813232 38.0494918823243,23.6850910186768 38.0473175048828,23.6863708496094 38.0454216003419,23.6888599395752 38.0431213378906,23.6927032470704 38.0407409667969,23.693479537964 38.0397987365723,23.6926555633545 38.0377120971681,23.6902770996095 38.0355186462403,23.6888198852539 38.0348472595215,23.6874351501465 38.0321388244628,23.6861801147462 38.0312614440919,23.6845226287843 38.0288314819336,23.6832580566406 38.0283164978027))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "19": {
    "Question": "What is the total area of river Garw?",
    "Query": "select distinct (strdf:area(?geoWKT)as ?totalArea) where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Garw> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "totalArea 0.004007779527455568^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "20": {
    "Question": "Where is Muckross Village located?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?geoWKT where {  yago:geoentity_Muckross_Village_9884064 geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "geoWKT POLYGON ((-9.51561710474964 52.01751320378, -9.51393828426444 52.0175673272649, -9.51448639392698   52.0150688717966, -9.5072134679328 52.016802531233, -9.50686492468953 52.0146467819321, -9.51214633155784 52.0141561584216, -9.50913163343043 52.0123882230444, -9.50502478284021 52.0113119331347, -9.50034614183345 52.0154741019022, -9.49657102563317 52.0148886596357, -9.49490230888728 52.0231799519888, -9.48938867868276 52.0257987452833, -9.48827753893454 52.0273700968048, -9.48915804232796 52.029982532993, -9.49401553476616 52.0311195951466, -9.49929695859042 52.0261923513232, -9.50900949760151 52.0229710502579, -9.50824523262543 52.022110185999, -9.5124940269628 52.0223956801751, -9.51513525730401 52.0251391689195, -9.52399592696954 52.0223567836027, -9.52612611314268 52.0202148045705, -9.52853372672496 52.0218477638521, -9.5315920787922 52.0198005062831, -9.53472441019019 52.0222920076346, -9.53366236020877 52.0204825798867, -9.53638504574622 52.0210733862437, -9.54344414213538 52.0164234202263, -9.54445174918551 52.0177701360036, -9.54745761137205 52.0166452445975, -9.54734189280379 52.0152572644199, -9.53925634356655 52.0157135090519, -9.54145663496924 52.0167791997684, -9.53876261817003 52.0174924488289, -9.5293524020452 52.0159913708047, -9.52974402316705 52.0146302293656, -9.52659224819567 52.0154551420202, -9.52113229571546 52.0140716472139, -9.51804961694613 52.0156146788032, -9.518918791409 52.0169255555911, -9.51561710474964 52.01751320378))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "21": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Dimos Thessaloniki?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population WHERE{         yago:geoentity_Dimos_Thessaloniki_8133841 y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population . }",
    "Answer": "population 375276^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "22": {
    "Question": "Where Anafi is located ?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?geoWKT where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Anafi> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "geoWKT <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> MULTIPOLYGON (((25.7926387786866 36.3451385498...   more                  MULTIPOLYGON(((669335.6875 4014969,669329.125 4014976,669323.875 4014980,669321.3125 4014984,66931...   more <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> MULTIPOLYGON (((25.7926387786866 36.3451385498...   more"
  },
  "23": {
    "Question": "Where Southampton is located?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?geoWKT where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Southampton> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "geoWKT <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> MULTIPOLYGON (((-1.47651124 50.91125107,-1.476...   More <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> MULTIPOLYGON (((-1.47651124 50.91125107,-1.476...   more <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> MULTIPOLYGON (((-1.47651124 50.91125107,-1.476...   more"
  },
  "24": {
    "Question": "Where the city of Cork is located?",
    "Query": "select distinct  ?geoWKT where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cork_City_7778678> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "geoWKT MULTIPOLYGON (((-9.88553190386653 51.6455212468997, -9.88555563831235 51.6455346123881, -9.8855515...   more"
  },
  "25": {
    "Question": "What is the population of the municipality of Athens?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876> y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population  }",
    "Answer": "population 657701^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "26": {
    "Question": "Where is Oxford district located ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?gWKT  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oxford> geo:hasGeometry ?g .  ?g geo:asWKT ?gWKT }",
    "Answer": "gWKT <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-1.30368765335028 51.7726313487459,- -1.30371817328995 51.7727214156925,-1.3038751904235 51.773156585654,-1.3040986565148 51.7739878277706,-1.30415664479278 51.7743666817804,-1.30419765366075 51.7748084455203,-1.30421616781215 51.7750188887965,-1.3042472325809 51.7753535391645,-1.30424490998843 51.7755046241387,-1.3042355638434 51.7762058609863,-1.30421651301985 51.7765977419684,-1.30418934977582 51.7768565433744,-1.30411576277226 51.7772121471671,-1.3040589420515 51.7774177401921,-1.30395067571502 51.7777668466077,-1.30362056419325 51.7787781792366,-1.30346431810538 51.7792313588685,-1.30334149977221 51.7795857716237,-1.30306339243287 51.780229686274,-1.30283943891876 51.7806473182831,-1.3029958398343 51.7806581327213,-1.30283762016683 51.7809593022663,-1.30269676643175 51.7809710513286,-1.30251540069169 51.781269386619,-1.30255459059867 51.7812624281276,-1.30260969758177 51.7812618560323,-1.30268329028667 51.7812793707359,-1.30265944089404 51.7813223746752,-1.30260021162889 51.7813112371547,-1.3024182740348 51.7813596854687,-1.30207324317011 51.7819240110243,-1.30169257297028 51.7824504616606,-1.30130562524749 51.7829184477775,-1.30112682176446 51.7831349098463,-1.30089109104051 51.7833843810244,-1.30031449040251 51.7839186509799,-1.30014342519283 51.7840129124811,-1.30021089543472 51.7840555603924,-1.30023385897097 51.7840700787912,-1.30020730420423 51.7841022797944,-1.30018134717744 51.7840958333279,-1.30015096809261 51.7840893605436,-1.29962343065823 51.7845493135567,-1.29904953885113 51.7850071003426,-1.2981916794348 51.7856313671406,-1.29761267681617 51.7860469598282,-1.29759503148072 51.7860594385049,-1.2972732192842 51.7862462770116,-1.29728504506999 51.7863237395744,-1.2972821486422 51.7863255199912,-1.2972858371425 51.7863650919001,-1.29722580681984 51.7864051819687,-1.29715334115325 51.7863993558022,-1.29701439990705 51.7863868402757,-1.29698809287416 51.786402862535,-1.29606862026532 51.7869809036485,-1.29583793580351 51.7870873861092,-1.29547130674191 51.7872650526487,-1.29483873438891 51.7875714587552,-1.29385717419734 51.7880420560337,-1.29335278860394 51.7883060783473,-1.29313078835692 51.7884144053962,-1.29292336077354 51.7885157186315,-1.29264422480695 51.7886542625402,-1.29256964717435 51.7886915661647,-1.2922320797243 51.7888667008178,-1.29222734782946 51.788886447277,-1.29221312398639 51.7889627648343,-1.29234075193847 51.7890570142594,-1.29230122328496 51.7890774502257,-1.29217263046391 51.7891441808752,-1.2918203503385 51.7893272256639,-1.29178236101931 51.7893485695844,-1.29175020756136 51.7893636566091,-1.29135116501288 51.7895707775291,-1.29124739106962 51.7896249827598,-1.2910675737874 51.7897182794587,-1.29038456132094 51.7900963563217,-1.29021331102875 51.7901995908641,-1.28962622182408 51.7905583773084,-1.2896031172865 51.7905528446061,-1.28944703850811 51.7905195428746,-1.28923270453347 51.7905038661375,-1.28878718412803 51.7908068755695,-1.28854392120362 51.7909734913254,-1.28821715994038 51.7911891285379,-1.28784800035127 51.7914323728215,-1.28740817087672 51.7917372091989,-1.28702311836224 51.7919794557466,-1.28670806657754 51.7921869801086,-1.2866596694659 51.7922236297714,-1.28643373809638 51.7923894474031,-1.28627302846883 51.792558446838,-1.28615311186672 51.7927105253929,-1.28605316588076 51.7928924773142,-1.28590704760472 51.7931441700595,-1.28580698718341 51.7934240968278,-1.28569759607001 51.7936437432095,-1.28548710411796 51.7937548222957,-1.28525097002146 51.793831678396,-1.28494637144532 51.7939287017428,-1.28465990690872 51.793982689298,-1.28454624652669 51.7942903969309,-1.28447263186993 51.7946361001695,-1.28439929305105 51.7946922822086,-1.28450666222971 51.794774821504,-1.28456352325774 51.7948533681818,-1.28458204844331 51.7949595463355,-1.28455719207582 51.7950646516597,-1.28416441272816 51.7956034655936,-1.28366816279884 51.7962657806659,-1.28365663791745 51.7962612161821,-1.28343331358673 51.7961699699672,-1.2832578855893 51.7960817117596,-1.28287831988917 51.7958761661208,-1.28285367916249 51.7958769147557,-1.28102797378641 51.7959710262693,-1.28099236270361 51.79611282848,-1.28094461552713 51.7961080423138,-1.27971692605059 51.795984578155,-1.27987551586799 51.7954029080375,-1.27993510638491 51.7951218397223,-1.28004810909205 51.7951279245848,-1.28006047744742 51.7950794618363,-1.27995180705499 51.7950716057851,-1.27995825138131 51.7950347919654,-1.27907436522762 51.7949906371517,-1.27882489706612 51.7949953999401,-1.2787263645083 51.7949965935128,-1.27843256363695 51.7950524085395,-1.27723636291892 51.7952275331603,-1.27723223169292 51.7952167214522,-1.2770439914375 51.7947417753598,-1.27701587033772 51.7946012904118,-1.27640575631492 51.7946703464924,-1.27640420226067 51.7946703369324,-1.27379505536392 51.7949825213055,-1.27283201520404 51.7950880304333,-1.27261260650576 51.7951118419383,-1.27155345878391 51.7952383189025,-1.2715809968227 51.7949760221504,-1.2715730033332 51.7947448755853,-1.27148457441065 51.7947497210994,-1.27125819685433 51.7947609028655,-1.27091646772896 51.7948154134395,-1.27062918394869 51.7949187991117,-1.27029816609052 51.7950354855802,-1.27002133086 51.7951209573746,-1.26937662273622 51.7953543437087,-1.2690626143196 51.7954908174039,-1.26888761625776 51.7955553466551,-1.26866312791117 51.7956268487254,-1.26866031696884 51.795623235806,-1.26811384243464 51.7948905911552,-1.26790409148495 51.794413698609,-1.26768257110458 51.7937631623164,-1.26764916123012 51.7937665497499,-1.26649904100961 51.7938789318111,-1.26627666859707 51.7932823191101,-1.2661766874621 51.7930119471757,-1.26610717586928 51.7928236515084,-1.26501935829212 51.793024496173,-1.26397381199178 51.7932131011357,-1.26395536370945 51.7931860198584,-1.26392135327708 51.7931381673844,-1.2638804758327 51.7929760266597,-1.26386520450613 51.7927611032416,-1.26382123512225 51.7924290583422,-1.2636935004937 51.7923517657075,-1.26325569636773 51.7924336071483,-1.26312775571512 51.7924570749673,-1.26252412126074 51.7925764358501,-1.26237270892464 51.7926096431587,-1.26203154097026 51.7927253438951,-1.26183751015088 51.7927987318824,-1.26175505657813 51.7927892257907,-1.26169582260832 51.7927780676665,-1.26161285688611 51.7927047391006,-1.26145867165815 51.7925562679331,-1.2614149548465 51.7925685774927,-1.26141353508297 51.7925676697162,-1.26041004120157 51.792845494346,-1.26012302365006 51.7929245868236,-1.25934226017453 51.7931498714822,-1.25872332915929 51.7933114529368,-1.25865921565989 51.7933281272373,-1.25823362998663 51.7934656665402,-1.25811260557221 51.793504453171,-1.25795000198958 51.7934324174157,-1.2577175286833 51.7932834474171,-1.25730205608835 51.7929724253807,-1.2570915753137 51.7927221115095,-1.25683127146863 51.7924192585987,-1.25663524635333 51.7921698441841,-1.25646164599118 51.7920617823678,-1.25637876434676 51.7918966768208,-1.25631695730765 51.7917731419877,-1.25623969741366 51.7916224536656,-1.25607874532888 51.791363372566,-1.25598073610411 51.7912387097058,-1.25570080781914 51.7909815720006,-1.25550906664223 51.7908212599498,-1.25499555566621 51.7903971613154,-1.25475216434186 51.790215847012,-1.25430327297537 51.7899117932508,-1.25400579357836 51.7896689219321,-1.25377974230941 51.7894804347668,-1.25356828866137 51.7892912308202,-1.25332115557394 51.7890693510545,-1.25320054934821 51.7889094867111,-1.2531401553894 51.7888821373637,-1.2530489557116 51.7888743673269,-1.25304535096257 51.7888248171163,-1.25301695206017 51.7884380360291,-1.25302070837467 51.7882105577913,-1.25303926693432 51.787962589599,-1.25300562963329 51.7878930736706,-1.25296649127489 51.7878092308778,-1.2529782556439 51.7874442775003,-1.25297873057358 51.787415516913,-1.25296873976583 51.7873183762944,-1.25294214159107 51.7872641857118,-1.25257239676475 51.7870919516133,-1.25249943738152 51.7870294664256,-1.25249209491823 51.7869457356432,-1.25252303328065 51.786918067522,-1.25263045869735 51.7868261673213,-1.25267309363651 51.7867850905424,-1.25269228976391 51.786766336394,-1.25273513318724 51.7867198677407,-1.25273715372217 51.7865975453582,-1.25273727248939 51.7865903552108,-1.25273898880851 51.7865732877228,-1.25272286011036 51.7864931864641,-1.25304873446792 51.7865132337128,-1.25328789489297 51.786514752314,-1.2535107333441 51.7864550441714,-1.25361302164869 51.7864062558806,-1.25370073067615 51.7863644760091,-1.25387639633859 51.7862586258446,-1.25400435711398 51.7861461808138,-1.25378870195047 51.7860386571015,-1.25374757469327 51.7860681485221,-1.25372412108293 51.7860841792411,-1.25241594454815 51.7855067115818,-1.25194676112332 51.7852986977907,-1.25143372934871 51.78502478604,-1.25063093728597 51.7847382398445,-1.25031044763988 51.7845744020709,-1.24938736050252 51.7841117122597,-1.24894727565119 51.7839021642445,-1.24875693452635 51.7838407247717,-1.24869537095491 51.7837908041535,-1.24803876547463 51.7835277353142,-1.24748902734015 51.7832859305595,-1.24741428711166 51.7833312943714,-1.24735244005291 51.7833057304277,-1.24740982129261 51.7832548623969,-1.24579316271034 51.7825719766983,-1.24484200081645 51.782149519664,-1.24398133241521 51.781784354912,-1.24304700478286 51.7813935415561,-1.24279228825861 51.7812876336736,-1.24261508450838 51.7812207856932,-1.24213492812312 51.7810666834456,-1.24199959494244 51.7810118794516,-1.24172752713339 51.780900374342,-1.24162914614808 51.7808871559066,-1.24156833404508 51.7808786739859,-1.2415811462792 51.7808059486103,-1.24158279023156 51.7808005660265,-1.24078055822382 51.7804887874416,-1.23999836606276 51.7801942112624,-1.23902193383668 51.7798165765223,-1.23613147144051 51.7786190673461,-1.23528800993491 51.7782692308578,-1.23436357710961 51.7779026815881,-1.23262148165649 51.7772116055841,-1.23171697898205 51.7768703336006,-1.23120820395991 51.7767033254443,-1.23109854975934 51.7766720471565,-1.23091530823164 51.7766250068499,-1.23080123044436 51.7766008902777,-1.23066234121377 51.7765811056143,-1.23045405693156 51.7765590689906,-1.23010631833656 51.776550500996,-1.22914706852341 51.7766188232352,-1.22874382963729 51.7766341567819,-1.22873383812099 51.7766313946606,-1.22810793702791 51.7764447286848,-1.22801269829311 51.7764162387212,-1.22799973487525 51.7764125581632,-1.22800686257176 51.7763379991152,-1.2278733242153 51.7761798209843,-1.22782094647136 51.7761047813617,-1.22776296977567 51.776021705046,-1.22774357633747 51.7759676457648,-1.22771532981546 51.7758371247683,-1.2277104086341 51.7757893626883,-1.22771217242008 51.7756860047254,-1.22771991714937 51.7755683041864,-1.22778052482722 51.7754131085259,-1.22793710270673 51.7752433520821,-1.22795038776262 51.7752281585809,-1.22773064040926 51.7751079756064,-1.22771061537065 51.7750979565827,-1.22732546917303 51.7749012717322,-1.22660720709922 51.7746106212006,-1.22653234760412 51.7745786685722,-1.22559720745184 51.7741759348286,-1.22557193181748 51.7742144196233,-1.22556885236368 51.7742197925403,-1.22554584101922 51.7742097534788,-1.22472418275028 51.7738662761723,-1.22475223420379 51.7738332030512,-1.22444615957045 51.7737655677416,-1.22443885552464 51.773766418439,-1.22428616451657 51.7737995682819,-1.22426455669524 51.7737913359576,-1.22412633776249 51.7737400876425,-1.22394818747518 51.7736481266886,-1.22381653734645 51.7736319771322,-1.22378469634602 51.7736281715091,-1.2237617165298 51.7736163345715,-1.22369274786313 51.7735825313842,-1.2233981961118 51.7732613992494,-1.22332088394516 51.7732960343463,-1.22262291232538 51.7730027966692,-1.22090629585321 51.7722828603763,-1.22083440035994 51.7722527214565,-1.22017550011088 51.772301387148,-1.21958630148936 51.7723479050093,-1.21892745602838 51.772400159541,-1.21851523462299 51.7724324767311,-1.21744986310437 51.7725260652677,-1.21730396721071 51.7725808240658,-1.21716164874886 51.7726014495664,-1.2167539242841 51.7727120818043,-1.21655459683732 51.7727538996621,-1.216227671522 51.7728011589135,-1.21574048164321 51.7728149893841,-1.21527866858452 51.7727849427064,-1.21499386252688 51.7727461883735,-1.21475459516601 51.7727481864337,-1.21381762746404 51.7725413891466,-1.21323536275355 51.7724359231729,-1.21274575059509 51.772341860996,-1.21225645368105 51.7723053263668,-1.21102072835895 51.7722790649803,-1.21097528621444 51.7723084227077,-1.21072318564384 51.7722995400489,-1.21067880909833 51.7722677818593,-1.21049944926368 51.7722539038417,-1.2103640302099 51.7722008603432,-1.21035976023786 51.7721990339377,-1.21000553363524 51.7720645214312,-1.20987257896393 51.7720483474664,-1.20983541919079 51.7720139408419,-1.20969005528571 51.7718735497452,-1.20931341727614 51.7717020309658,-1.20926556856344 51.7716981137714,-1.20907021525102 51.7716833170429,-1.20899507465515 51.7716684297728,-1.20872514435846 51.7715245029235,-1.2085700283976 51.7715252568386,-1.20831817473439 51.7714273828149,-1.20802655004508 51.7712806116938,-1.20792404041381 51.7712592473424,-1.20779690887518 51.7712314249664,-1.20756618996666 51.7711687475167,-1.20724649611239 51.7710488412028,-1.20698212957787 51.7710039131165,-1.20621699409155 51.7708350671922,-1.20614086349143 51.7707950031188,-1.20593581680442 51.7707540685734,-1.20568997778084 51.7706408588597,-1.20538489834061 51.7706010453708,-1.20518861338777 51.770551180045,-1.20446029770989 51.7702666175683,-1.20435646896188 51.7702389490948,-1.20416163624093 51.7701881930021,-1.20412712158143 51.7701735775362,-1.20382655122302 51.7700474992092,-1.20328852315783 51.7699844401664,-1.20313747624619 51.769998697483,-1.20298842552625 51.7699877998389,-1.20283132554486 51.7700200829786,-1.20277904428945 51.7700305149728,-1.20266770748431 51.7700153782512,-1.20241324661805 51.76997850694,-1.20228957652951 51.7700055329939,-1.2022226383792 51.770020449541,-1.20207440363715 51.7700446121158,-1.20195529637671 51.7700635789689,-1.20183234632756 51.7701310584782,-1.20166137656011 51.7701298979232,-1.20146482827458 51.7700953053242,-1.20120660452228 51.7700279342297,-1.20118642058473 51.7700206061827,-1.20088320742838 51.769875536239,-1.20076879248155 51.7697911639735,-1.20067748199097 51.76979234109,-1.20064271482307 51.7697921047659,-1.20056856432291 51.7697214890111,-1.2005125608036 51.7696923445067,-1.20031411052667 51.7696100071571,-1.20019758833949 51.769557080375,-1.20014788416966 51.7695028102363,-1.20012934078812 51.7694838078814,-1.19990748589968 51.7694885907194,-1.19919093294294 51.7693659615748,-1.19899322818099 51.7693159863066,-1.19824187392565 51.7691886199632,-1.1981294573425 51.7691536964718,-1.19807908737102 51.7691371733673,-1.19811317739213 51.7690069800714,-1.19821110463595 51.7689627043957,-1.19823794559467 51.7689179439942,-1.19824749485263 51.7688712679581,-1.19825064872242 51.7688551098345,-1.19812347355679 51.7687562660715,-1.19779094451124 51.7686280666608,-1.19752999481325 51.7685534778958,-1.1971138926142 51.7684823236753,-1.19690426889632 51.7684512296125,-1.19645869828695 51.7684113322023,-1.19623613441469 51.7683755642943,-1.19597254189349 51.7683692679872,-1.19593480505042 51.7683681110947,-1.19590026252665 51.7683552907443,-1.19576934840759 51.7683058566014,-1.19571401690019 51.7683198600679,-1.19548837360447 51.7683767430062,-1.19535663747462 51.7683668529869,-1.19520219737994 51.7684108294276,-1.19501583542699 51.7684625870797,-1.19493970280896 51.7684234145545,-1.19489377964736 51.7683988307057,-1.19472792777668 51.7684327509546,-1.19454943585999 51.768371214458,-1.1944013709752 51.768379188892,-1.19424646522859 51.7683754309771,-1.1940400793748 51.7683236800114,-1.19387661254236 51.7683108742483,-1.193782670306 51.7682922528552,-1.19372246806045 51.7682576830959,-1.19349041560639 51.7682650804955,-1.19347307636178 51.7682658604428,-1.19346449913025 51.7682577117988,-1.19341324271804 51.7682106190775,-1.19316952173442 51.7682224301496,-1.19264590488583 51.7681640053867,-1.19254774995053 51.7681471518183,-1.19236891659472 51.768098283699,-1.1922195380786 51.7681062463618,-1.19204167963316 51.7681634509304,-1.19191599721636 51.7682228115234,-1.19181822594069 51.7682580943583,-1.19156207592489 51.7682365585412,-1.19129778992508 51.7681888990246,-1.1908586203086 51.7681121707719,-1.19017966842685 51.7679941497241,-1.18901403533948 51.767697489929,-1.18883973397498 51.767636063514,-1.18861883772188 51.7675077990543,-1.18848467541738 51.7673935259078,-1.18840933983308 51.7673103100525,-1.18830631809811 51.7671 85890081,-1.18826199693551 51.7670449356992,-1.18826763675756 51.7668103698381,-1.18828274402622 51.7662943435463,-1.18828883353087 51.7661946111177,-1.18829642931452 51.766097495805,-1.18832714843662 51.7656769472258,-1.18823892338379 51.7655864513057,-1.18822460670963 51.7655719705668,-1.18817530724734 51.7655761245692,-1.18776888426874 51.7656137671154,-1.18770224149127 51.7655324085524,-1.18739122782137 51.7655796975172,-1.18700084456219 51.7656156505121,-1.18636966343856 51.7657407221311,-1.18613756458896 51.7657579922281,-1.18445438354676 51.7658821498167,-1.18442311065198 51.7659268763857,-1.18192701555761 51.7659697619542,-1.18070796092232 51.7659900385675,-1.18070648699314 51.7659064334368,-1.18022773990287 51.765859951138,-1.18005872279804 51.7647887583516,-1.17999336449335 51.7644790015279,-1.17990765832373 51.7639273067628,-1.17975034609301 51.7630944852101,-1.17974637131292 51.7630764800843,-1.17968391748737 51.7628440460686,-1.17971002399478 51.7628406327101,-1.18113260591298 51.7626203474204,-1.18180983001114 51.7625109051059,-1.18268548146377 51.7624019394019,-1.18273981423817 51.7623636656339,-1.1829393754159 51.7622220422587,-1.18308180553527 51.7621214595534,-1.18317496708871 51.7620168490723,-1.18342787942742 51.7616526757103,-1.1836814433224 51.7613316520769,-1.18370921757253 51.7612356657978,-1.18413334749634 51.7605382098132,-1.18427714901724 51.7602748497858,-1.18428686567317 51.760139996782,-1.18429468781448 51.7600240967929,-1.18430770770543 51.760024187113,-1.18509476794098 51.7600089703281,-1.18555715680797 51.759998690878,-1.18595866541295 51.7599924825023,-1.18595913398193 51.7599664185131,-1.18597723092219 51.7592787283522,-1.18601222848029 51.7587008172851,-1.1860246330382 51.7584958708388,-1.18608918210343 51.7573238311002,-1.18613345073312 51.7568746123689,-1.18615704209586 51.7568514050238,-1.18615707439946 51.7568496075063,-1.18620872478614 51.7568005271111,-1.18696957835673 51.7560594583047,-1.18706729464701 51.7560259768506,-1.18724605655571 51.7559094605827,-1.18733260618895 51.755852531084,-1.18733135034453 51.7558426348269,-1.1873286869638 51.7558246390056,-1.1872599162585 51.7557828156207,-1.18730724342725 51.7557282217464,-1.18741082074935 51.7556875895519,-1.18742387821057 51.7556921741432,-1.18757076751369 51.7557408293155,-1.18766195315573 51.755745054812,-1.18766126148736 51.7557037019832,-1.18766019903037 51.7556830206176,-1.18782123802156 51.7555088533073,-1.18784153565257 51.7555027014147,-1.18794645515688 51.7554737633389,-1.18805470489405 51.7557387788715,-1.18826783889289 51.7557303628779,-1.18865314234347 51.7558131115945,-1.18878738538398 51.755921003435,-1.18931354379187 51.7559093515091,-1.18938207528965 51.7559646550949,-1.18957624426438 51.7560414986777,-1.18974822373658 51.7560633579318,-1.19000208050933 51.7560489273098,-1.19023609867424 51.7560082922726,-1.19024797343398 51.7559921943828,-1.19029824248342 51.7559332151092,-1.19033291857798 51.7559379482467,-1.19046005361041 51.75595590217,-1.19047969595564 51.7559128916213,-1.19048876835665 51.7558931789316,-1.19057691686447 51.7558200783933,-1.1911543741642 51.7554508411277,-1.19143874627826 51.7552658319252,-1.19146169226256 51.7552785739016,-1.19146604010347 51.7552759071876,-1.19149187573706 51.7552940622516,-1.19177607594692 51.7554398354012,-1.19196871294646 51.7556093380477,-1.1919912423367 51.755645447688,-1.19205449170431 51.7557492524153,-1.19230706876457 51.7558868070128,-1.19235610085403 51.7558970313888,-1.1926347275877 51.7559537759815,-1.19263914679549 51.7559538063256,-1.19264198126354 51.7559556235288,-1.19268492799899 51.7559855811307,-1.192901815365 51.7561687317724,-1.19322769215485 51.7564163597716,-1.19340939338301 51.7565498301603,-1.19396523610676 51.7569042910716,-1.19409987894248 51.7569906066408,-1.19430463719171 51.7571242336479,-1.19430922489667 51.7571080854216,-1.19431241879595 51.7570964219951,-1.19440419132854 51.7566582223913,-1.19450736666218 51.7560690906026,-1.19454619936174 51.7558401447003,-1.19461935924491 51.7553937275137,-1.19466157781052 51.7551422430953,-1.19471988600393 51.7547919931002,-1.19479874191178 51.7541056163147,-1.19486368075779 51.7538794557403,-1.19493246820759 51.7535912994031,-1.19491044833471 51.7532845438588,-1.19490879284886 51.7528871417943,-1.19491602211395 51.7526417096979,-1.19494445854882 51.752426175421,-1.19502580966835 51.752089565964,-1.19506613036491 51.7519378429462,-1.19512558430705 51.7516100721963,-1.19504815845825 51.7515645986084,-1.19508093403195 51.7513534984368,-1.1950923948849 51.7512798694787,-1.1951639634939 51.7504315555083,-1.19512631372861 51.7492903606192,-1.19512407877973 51.749248098371,-1.1951390199877 51.7487365631141,-1.1951389198326 51.747680118863,-1.19516069952883 51.7470256198165,-1.19516911368823 51.7463099958162,-1.19522078174435 51.7455191625802,-1.19526134292345 51.7451921609814,-1.19526642392462 51.7451481510381,-1.19477214447893 51.7453353276621,-1.19467884319522 51.7453706434927,-1.19441721688221 51.7450128079944,-1.19372067618862 51.74402979087,-1.19292278580274 51.7428787935454,-1.19222698289837 51.7418580194663,-1.19256159317586 51.74128126431,-1.19287779928601 51.7407718871557,-1.19327927238926 51.740181206942,-1.19338660227254 51.7400146631618,-1.19340757536119 51.7390779119318,-1.19342359449759 51.7385871473387,-1.19344016728805 51.7380585439479,-1.19348086200032 51.7377243524696,-1.19356882177778 51.7371764634929,-1.19386560645191 51.7367766127391,-1.19401715267677 51.7366409331899,-1.1940136699355 51.7365950667789,-1.19400763410424 51.7365249132868,-1.1936201292151 51.7364134923,-1.1931839613416 51.73626569125,-1.19170137807483 51.7362447206018,-1.18829802730601 51.7361754289768,-1.18697046092826 51.7361527722161,-1.18572822621139 51.7362187811456,-1.18359505745746 51.7363820536145,-1.18273887606619 51.7363994754706,-1.18211228739168 51.7363780392921,-1.18133371517406 51.7363492493784,-1.18126419430684 51.7363442708632,-1.181183163684 51.7363419087635,-1.18033563032494 51.7362838679307,-1.17947892842794 51.73625092546,-1.17924876361626 51.7362421278006,-1.17908331476585 51.7357059627507,-1.17883398411969 51.7353976154525,-1.17881984813669 51.7353804381013,-1.17835075563505 51.7355371600731,-1.17807076947088 51.7356422587849,-1.17798913713709 51.7356731486168,-1.1774112275406 51.7351215121149,-1.17666625974312 51.7344338716342,-1.17662389988665 51.7344587434406,-1.17631207534419 51.7340033465109,-1.17609381716324 51.7337474355586,-1.17581338969801 51.7334766164565,-1.17581356947584 51.7334667300959,-1.17582468817386 51.7333345835876,-1.17583275757489 51.7329696071532,-1.17583511092389 51.7328401856929,-1.17589305396092 51.7326805023119,-1.17593116948386 51.7325738034097,-1.17654255851818 51.7323182229287,-1.17738554664555 51.7319842602835,-1.18025906061961 51.7308264474153,-1.18126105742877 51.730430644489,-1.18322833385573 51.7296530500666,-1.18336965024454 51.7296018971096,-1.18358270649696 51.7298362754363,-1.18362936155629 51.7298177230753,-1.18469539870599 51.7293962682811,-1.18640047989079 51.7287012963497,-1.18750422621503 51.7282710883643,-1.18767926164717 51.7282030846661,-1.18937370322115 51.7275305579228,-1.19015980921606 51.7272095947047,-1.1902495034058 51.7271337183397,-1.19033221960221 51.7270408051093,-1.1903487758797 51.7270094585231,-1.1903685910831 51.7269493703845,-1.19033689598184 51.726859174709,-1.1901377870863 51.7262571749136,-1.18998793570646 51.7260520978064,-1.18903465081167 51.7243083589423,-1.18777309748453 51.7237719190652,-1.18729319390006 51.7234880630581,-1.18679250685065 51.7232319264264,-1.18654270662083 51.7231169397011,-1.18629974774719 51.7230198874227,-1.18594969836455 51.7229239806978,-1.18568068948955 51.7228286343637,-1.18544784650163 51.7227334481396,-1.18529166420249 51.7226433770659,-1.18516454284447 51.7225436196004,-1.18504597929203 51.7224592022143,-1.18492037357858 51.72235487072,-1.18485444499027 51.7222375596901,-1.18475828459631 51.7221154546864,-1.1846407187262 51.7219690213625,-1.18453017521037 51.7218370186473,-1.18435158968412 51.7217053526939,-1.18417310060142 51.7215683837644,-1.18443602961852 51.7214370847799,-1.18462429430879 51.7213556942579,-1.18477910900909 51.7212758692059,-1.18506366409895 51.7210701120917,-1.18543179827818 51.7208029110549,-1.18575191594941 51.7205506571536,-1.18592360550306 51.7204215093032,-1.1861762852603 51.7202155287316,-1.18645541974419 51.7199918430798,-1.18663791187324 51.7198258251409,-1.18684550289458 51.7196312165129,-1.18704447525181 51.7194312445394,-1.18719212189631 51.7192712768676,-1.18730889908598 51.7191354551294,-1.18744237740653 51.7189601082851,-1.1875704562701 51.7187596453203,-1.18767340430778 51.7185894804454,-1.18771405428361 51.7184989748603,-1.1877645487062 51.7184319080697,-1.18786022917683 51.7184208837968,-1.18801802984773 51.7181000863735,-1.18821663273817 51.7171933233362,-1.18832589843245 51.7167498531526,-1.18847284752957 51.7163813396601,-1.18864362684156 51.7159815297817,-1.18880731931829 51.7157308842508,-1.18908587396672 51.7153704691444,-1.18953798164288 51.7148547557353,-1.18947078043217 51.7147284496082,-1.18949132251341 51.7146341193123,-1.18960560496455 51.7145567050221,-1.18980941348308 51.7144915931458,-1.19045025777894 51.7144330872907,-1.19045836397229 51.714380109393,-1.19078354311175 51.7143283260785,-1.19157416171473 51.7142294968132,-1.19260395193749 51.7141098334593,-1.19283447115601 51.7140925402869,-1.19315434950801 51.7140902421233,-1.19329327899657 51.7140893979603,-1.19346266902642 51.7140869648982,-1.19377303502946 51.7140558357258,-1.19410376021349 51.7140139689189,-1.19443319493713 51.7139640923363,-1.19469501892669 51.7138975718483,-1.19520553095696 51.7137581470484,-1.19598718597061 51.7135108222287,-1.19628386449363 51.7134301545944,-1.1968876332059 51.7132535174337,-1.19754148950008 51.7130313764371,-1.19802767238209 51.7128764923981,-1.19825309902212 51.712816007789,-1.19876740903716 51.7127034698625,-1.19919929379079 51.7125886602835,-1.19942024730329 51.7125380306061,-1.19964584646006 51.7124675669753,-1.19976686918107 51.7124126606425,-1.19983768734619 51.7123421315191,-1.19991449395972 51.7122500700781,-1.19999633864571 51.7122038855836,-1.20008686362041 51.7121594679721,-1.20022184016812 51.7121388134445,-1.20036683227656 51.7121254179126,-1.20046217220583 51.7121395496353,-1.20060474187479 51.7121755755433,-1.20074700191713 51.7122359587267,-1.20091946968749 51.7123090414896,-1.20104446923752 51.7123602283108,-1.2016147071108 51.7126086873365,-1.2023947811228 51.7129367699174,-1.20306993507562 51.7132326752823,-1.20419970818503 51.7136826667845,-1.20475898833878 51.7138977778034,-1.20531950104097 51.7141245798604,-1.2056874495269 51.714273583732,-1.20646982498816 51.7145621040299,-1.20664789721087 51.7146433060283,-1.20683877269662 51.7147362795366,-1.20703810707549 51.7148437816982,-1.20738167979275 51.7149746382542,-1.20787285895712 51.7151137695184,-1.20842880543578 51.7152757169077,-1.2088824704228 51.7154038047803,-1.20918621037579 51.7154993317729,-1.20960224467219 51.7156297704085,-1.21016226335432 51.7158053099534,-1.21031130412489 51.7158135023534,-1.21054402272438 51.7158276498545,-1.21087375333673 51.7158496392298,-1.21136627287304 51.7159059783872,-1.21154265144573 51.7159206447668,-1.21240504531999 51.715941707264,-1.21240636806358 51.7159480082549,-1.21242834270819 51.7160983575716,-1.21273144626897 51.7160662307918,-1.21344360664632 51.715982818792,-1.21376267355109 51.7159454029228,-1.21391278007308 51.7158852833545,-1.21399962442165 51.7158049653257,-1.21414691519844 51.7156593435836,-1.21417079831419 51.7155345595789,-1.21430114541591 51.7155264421844,-1.21435380698297 51.7155798278284,-1.21445381247237 51.7156560017433,-1.21450550935927 51.71568241461,-1.21465125599195 51.7157085569972,-1.21476085013753 51.7157272666917,-1.21501072123322 51.7157640816985,-1.21520586685314 51.7157770701578,-1.21547221776229 51.7157788481866,-1.21571726077033 51.7157498317942,-1.2160429016986 51.7156702064663,-1.21659238586646 51.7155381398183,-1.21713647104292 51.7153798773772,-1.21739286218797 51.7152809106946,-1.21755779926789 51.7152047054676,-1.2176196242349 51.7151421957305,-1.21768311040425 51.7150733150025,-1.2177599064182 51.7148139612537,-1.21785460755074 51.7143605695126,-1.21792751462411 51.7141605155277,-1.21804815075095 51.7139608689099,-1.21813303585869 51.7138274112551,-1.21830587815617 51.7136245161203,-1.2185563766087 51.7133681146153,-1.2186867710868 51.7132737006376,-1.2187761267793 51.7132130811436,-1.21883058654056 51.7131622071886,-1.21884850796215 51.7131263712715,-1.21886108867031 51.7130680279709,-1.21879706678308 51.7130019845703,-1.21895774545358 51.7129229625587,-1.21903845793113 51.7129414763658,-1.2191383333642 51.7129421399141,-1.21921512598402 51.7129318635417,-1.21991357131409 51.7126361867062,-1.22015803762037 51.7125632022454,-1.22037589222843 51.7125179059108,-1.22054024702021 51.7124677600272,-1.2206472191806 51.7123956604388,-1.22071953525612 51.7123124545972,-1.22088134156532 51.7120771229763,-1.22104856237879 51.7118669056394,-1.22119848404696 51.7116493824354,-1.22128953297153 51.7114827948115,-1.22138500167205 51.7114897193924,-1.22145837503055 51.7114281829971,-1.22149215935616 51.7113996427479,-1.22176009235158 51.7112242486764,-1.22202297641763 51.7110856744779,-1.22229827771262 51.7109814290151,-1.22230703432976 51.7109787903263,-1.22270691379273 51.711459817038,-1.22302413527945 51.7117855994892,-1.22330576413261 51.7120715953474,-1.22374982234192 51.7125105732611,-1.22398043392046 51.7127378036154,-1.22384785316623 51.7127863663678,-1.2236726505625 51.7128777934874,-1.22404197660366 51.7132003216946,-1.22429198475468 51.7133962188128,-1.22464598656166 51.7136871833098,-1.22506227432702 51.7140558606298,-1.22522602028916 51.7142160409516,-1.22548388955712 51.7143715379145,-1.2257038153096 51.7144637732261,-1.22615421892876 51.7147014355818,-1.22653295646037 51.7149008718841,-1.22772007948335 51.715825709503,-1.22813431842622 51.7160649242917,-1.22870381535738 51.7164525718874,-1.22900004148938 51.7166559530421,-1.23041175617683 51.7174825507104,-1.23038534398685 51.7175057485149,-1.23106621883 51.7179013046429,-1.23113358677151 51.7179403969033,-1.23118927228158 51.7179857048356,-1.23133774652675 51.7181054171112,-1.23141042951144 51.7181760045611,-1.23186381056435 51.7186716410392,-1.23197573139306 51.7187299901804,-1.23212634381193 51.7188082773123,-1.23260481024626 51.7192753107446,-1.2328854154773 51.7195504898479,-1.2334176758261 51.7202606567137,-1.23360344458936 51.7205756648421,-1.23379249338019 51.7209510084524,-1.23391128918287 51.7209490861019,-1.23392143367623 51.7209491522147,-1.23397060958616 51.7210339668039,-1.23400721498759 51.7210998231132,-1.23404088235104 51.721162963645,-1.23403924119343 51.7212601211817,-1.23400428825409 51.7213578706368,-1.23392928818091 51.7214238985279,-1.23376702283709 51.7219497605763,-1.23380786665762 51.7220120490699,-1.2338636812994 51.7220501655392,-1.23413857550214 51.7221490351675,-1.23448103078321 51.7222691081158,-1.23499216386811 51.7224378283125,-1.23598632301042 51.7228076185284,-1.23695972594394 51.723205939594,-1.23716770378546 51.7233169519277,-1.23782629542841 51.7236691776302,-1.23910600338791 51.7242825891054,-1.24104589423161 51.7252365188813,-1.24107002667688 51.7251854389443,-1.241125499996 51.725066247009,-1.24132814339438 51.7251547456468,-1.24185375008698 51.7254108097051,-1.24173151043306 51.7255394589245,-1.24367151756569 51.7264070538978,-1.2450754590643 51.7270463673412,-1.24593171303903 51.7274429621489,-1.24614472535867 51.7272608685396,-1.24668616967972 51.7275224055591,-1.24684181812332 51.7276529303122,-1.24701646303086 51.7277753967981,-1.2476635873909 51.7283019643295,-1.24829238098215 51.7282790205887,-1.2484806790208 51.7280967647491,-1.2486887922588 51.7280369717011,-1.24892483851628 51.7280348845478,-1.24979447679889 51.727979314159,-1.25118380210181 51.7279288465181,-1.25170199959871 51.7279375394042,-1.25290931161368 51.7279497125342,-1.25352728588928 51.7279671212612,-1.25315113548369 51.7282128207293,-1.25315112067703 51.7282137195068,-1.25307941577666 51.7282618928949,-1.25400660595831 51.7292792802883,-1.25388109769743 51.72933960704,-1.25382924229654 51.7294147831104,-1.25381882956875 51.7294308967029,-1.25370337831129 51.729496680327,-1.2530192 991573 51.7298889176813,-1.25296373665739 51.7299209239845,-1.25331160633176 51.7306900509603,-1.25446333489418 51.7317997359898,-1.2558242822385 51.7331282606461,-1.25605050723658 51.7332896914129,-1.25675447704268 51.7334479408337,-1.25703284685263 51.7340485279365,-1.25739466259979 51.7343223627014,-1.25763209657188 51.7345072317958,-1.25789470665086 51.7348244831513,-1.25868247598606 51.7358031992633,-1.25872893035863 51.7357954023422,-1.25876090952054 51.7357893118798,-1.25884653560567 51.7357736720467,-1.25891654773836 51.7357417540663,-1.25912668824005 51.7356468994015,-1.25932333607047 51.7356616215168,-1.25946010749655 51.7357164153175,-1.25948163026245 51.7357291350676,-1.25952946660608 51.735812132418,-1.25957671432432 51.7359311707312,-1.25962904179605 51.7360097019715,-1.25998668808669 51.736365299506,-1.26044787952378 51.736770985156,-1.26088610967361 51.7370695590871,-1.26116636745661 51.7372880381704,-1.2613214318459 51.7374589888207,-1.26133764708274 51.7375336968915,-1.26152802862567 51.7376697233382,-1.2615724366623 51.7376996649678,-1.26171766530558 51.7377635878035,-1.26183154512943 51.7377948644383,-1.26204648175131 51.7378456515822,-1.26213724379759 51.7378740862024,-1.26236825194986 51.738008568498,-1.26275048521025 51.7383670981658,-1.26295355488675 51.7386191560006,-1.26299381184898 51.7388163506773,-1.26310349927271 51.7391056652104,-1.26314602452603 51.739251548589,-1.26321016114318 51.7393167590244,-1.2632925031688 51.7393271625814,-1.26341731097023 51.7393108660564,-1.26364931915338 51.7392007696779,-1.26379723086771 51.7391882129273,-1.26391258027214 51.7392248899447,-1.26407900716506 51.7393222007104,-1.26423514160619 51.7394283456332,-1.26432178519126 51.7395268645825,-1.26438558978654 51.7396126563982,-1.26444163425897 51.7398234323465,-1.26454520890924 51.7402178749132,-1.26464091093931 51.7403911463028,-1.26472728287502 51.7405139326991,-1.26478849688721 51.7405755284956,-1.26508126004926 51.7408353343091,-1.26522672687424 51.7409738603614,-1.26548070882881 51.7412101420712,-1.26556371557784 51.7412681882347,-1.26558946830742 51.7412854276122,-1.26575184236677 51.7413682388423,-1.26613240515402 51.7414793780148,-1.26642098154414 51.7415486839635,-1.26679787131078 51.7416139557391,-1.26694637958302 51.7416535331296,-1.26711633175114 51.7417184123314,-1.26750530899506 51.7418412847825,-1.26769625794733 51.7420331243393,-1.26769144584678 51.7421535427845,-1.26775210285625 51.742257380368,-1.26775747114239 51.7422798855206,-1.26775984301554 51.7423104618301,-1.26776249703294 51.7425083193679,-1.26787392905562 51.7426033945179,-1.26787533287075 51.7426052009968,-1.26791441056846 51.7426108375371,-1.2679089760805 51.7426737245071,-1.26785924383161 51.7427066729726,-1.26797717757668 51.7427541484669,-1.26825285133642 51.7428170774629,-1.26843866354473 51.7427875823384,-1.2687902063745 51.7427223540138,-1.26907722087148 51.7427115544895,-1.26930770962061 51.7426959086416,-1.2694041049596 51.7427387544998,-1.26947161221877 51.7428624088503,-1.26961252510558 51.7431068776869,-1.26968773738798 51.7432045125801,-1.26978907012644 51.7432078385692,-1.27003143320062 51.7431742876741,-1.27085825583067 51.7432800914173,-1.271297496969 51.743345735352,-1.2715294644578 51.7433273977023,-1.27165477163559 51.7432805339889,-1.27167647216314 51.7431934781786,-1.27168572337863 51.7431602773534,-1.27189623058518 51.7430356496814,-1.27191531339757 51.7430222848274,-1.27192696800525 51.7430178626562,-1.27203957633258 51.7429511447894,-1.27207571302745 51.7429540651292,-1.27218139123927 51.7429619103025,-1.27254316045304 51.7430702156733,-1.27285352959887 51.7431296631565,-1.27314766066054 51.743218761977,-1.27346984468268 51.7432638989728,-1.2737969371835 51.7432785038781,-1.27397288883399 51.743417117366,-1.27405679314607 51.7434275229976,-1.27432072809406 51.7434039840032,-1.27453477627686 51.743423282291,-1.27476725799308 51.7434697498271,-1.27513945093992 51.7434720450179,-1.27586813549686 51.7436446235124,-1.27626952129427 51.7438080821966,-1.27648289770728 51.743869619595,-1.27650891451206 51.7440576431219,-1.27661569550003 51.7441761417434,-1.27695953361581 51.7444065691784,-1.27713118479544 51.7445461401877,-1.27743595272056 51.7446882369314,-1.27752830012871 51.7447085795089,-1.27764727145677 51.7446994229439,-1.27772080939073 51.7447160543373,-1.27780993153992 51.7447589384648,-1.2779676549764 51.744865973555,-1.27818795995982 51.7449428311314,-1.27821810918418 51.7449618924409,-1.27826932786336 51.7450152400552,-1.27829716948567 51.7450892080045,-1.2782641984263 51.745157319575,-1.27817977929338 51.7451864639841,-1.27804193019898 51.7452035949871,-1.27809766743715 51.7452506783443,-1.27844331047943 51.745368753969,-1.27877287664247 51.7455065949326,-1.2788435790059 51.7455214104881,-1.27888106533303 51.7455297302127,-1.27959288922349 51.7454963413287,-1.27988012814236 51.7454648428097,-1.28062116217488 51.7454118515104,-1.28063419242876 51.7454110323655,-1.28100326864279 51.7453323019012,-1.2810713765493 51.7453300217646,-1.28108846849979 51.7453516990966,-1.28116240465922 51.7454412289317,-1.28138008747865 51.7455935693477,-1.2815825154056 51.7457063558572,-1.28196431621333 51.7458345295552,-1.28211318476298 51.7458606068761,-1.28232609480127 51.7459526922523,-1.2825314128694 51.7459737203797,-1.28287158693681 51.7459856831912,-1.28308518035572 51.7460347156012,-1.28331828294589 51.7460433276159,-1.28351193341504 51.746069676114,-1.28368495679923 51.7461165725803,-1.28416004823189 51.7463046326734,-1.28429212145258 51.7463810314315,-1.28454377504057 51.7464931236753,-1.28466267844909 51.7465792395279,-1.28484803897329 51.7467602304423,-1.28495389888081 51.7468480643928,-1.28506259683542 51.7469377132369,-1.28516208000653 51.747058856196,-1.28518341686081 51.7470841541964,-1.28528434928142 51.7472043171042,-1.28531160263794 51.7472179657704,-1.28543811993912 51.7472834531545,-1.28576354387397 51.7474059684746,-1.28591942298675 51.7474347801373,-1.28601557508759 51.7474946892749,-1.28639016012732 51.7476201979618,-1.28671614237512 51.7477075683123,-1.28719782509776 51.747941588097,-1.28741304175523 51.7480705317087,-1.28836936955621 51.7486913282794,-1.28859235623929 51.7488887204891,-1.28862236483016 51.7489095759835,-1.2888051103123 51.7489924783427,-1.28934518362534 51.7496476018747,-1.289668352038 51.7499157090289,-1.29020314690672 51.7503603719309,-1.29055919772519 51.7505657544201,-1.29066402446223 51.750629307498,-1.29075544716406 51.7507098580929,-1.29085416586039 51.7508813280103,-1.2908635975753 51.751018911449,-1.29086199559888 51.7510296881841,-1.29084582681491 51.7511393422534,-1.29083065067409 51.7514602358913,-1.29082524469514 51.7516148082896,-1.29086971328376 51.7519252752256,-1.29092940055847 51.7521792053311,-1.29093237034103 51.7522718064569,-1.29088135544506 51.7523794526406,-1.29088053934947 51.7524315819564,-1.29078648142444 51.7525191035684,-1.29077033552457 51.7528103286953,-1.2907429022407 51.7529909251967,-1.2907407147571 51.7533136948022,-1.29232933334437 51.753443714376,-1.29234169077711 51.7533943511194,-1.2927251307941 51.753423624091,-1.29309291100328 51.7534384198133,-1.29324602654347 51.7534699016552,-1.29324543752622 51.7535076504823,-1.29324673049655 51.7535166469126,-1.29325675188863 51.7541757555765,-1.29323521012739 51.7549974590323,-1.29328680580749 51.755219878838,-1.29331855860774 51.7553207426193,-1.29336233188029 51.7553938137932,-1.29344212721859 51.7554778877889,-1.29390310064513 51.755829506464,-1.29508937888831 51.7564048865429,-1.2951624602777 51.7564601554058,-1.29521251493484 51.7564982976562,-1.29524806259917 51.7565398585156,-1.29527214384566 51.7565813506449,-1.29526981855957 51.7570992628901,-1.29529410915624 51.7572117666188,-1.29541105128104 51.7581718261623,-1.29551426520435 51.7588935140806,-1.29555849207596 51.7591221806159,-1.29565371674042 51.7594284549786,-1.29573971959165 51.7595826759718,-1.29582125368076 51.759747746401,-1.29590878361134 51.7601726245886,-1.29594455105762 51.7602924776387,-1.29606952871715 51.7606447718242,-1.29619546448809 51.7609278590097,-1.29631796255437 51.7611631957626,-1.29670248658733 51.7618731721503,-1.29672802557608 51.7619056840083,-1.29680889517277 51.7620140313504,-1.29680019657023 51.7620202713857,-1.29672265987913 51.7620665486547,-1.29682771370412 51.7622946794633,-1.29685097222961 51.7622894253508,-1.29696593678869 51.7622640456443,-1.2969842729947 51.7622911211959,-1.29698727339003 51.7622902402686,-1.29799900687187 51.7637573880897,-1.29915231610061 51.7653602000948,-1.30009534992942 51.7666893033466,-1.30019327698758 51.7669164896278,-1.30102473633188 51.7680623617999,-1.30102184122625 51.7680641423193,-1.30098241273659 51.7680872784119,-1.30101214689894 51.7681270950189,-1.30101506434118 51.7681316066758,-1.3010843757054 51.7681464004316,-1.30121759681216 51.7681543830049,-1.30129106160643 51.7682716717337,-1.30124726803971 51.768291186527,-1.30124836339612 51.7683208555236,-1.30124850691429 51.7684044506611,-1.30132959163694 51.7685003018028,-1.30141502929337 51.7686005831736,-1.30249502594813 51.7701768579873,-1.3027917630228 51.7706704753264,-1.3032115518913 51.7714533559255,-1.30321995586781 51.7714740795596,-1.30340217229229 51.771870748467,-1.30359464799243 51.7723619482654,-1.30368765335028 51.7726313487459))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "27": {
    "Question": "What is the area of Donegal County ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?area  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Donegal> geo:hasGeometry ?gy .  ?gy geo:asWKT ?yWKT .  BIND(strdf:area(strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)) AS ?area)     }",
    "Answer": "0.6810451745986938^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "28": {
    "Question": "What is the area of Eretria?",
    "Query": "select (strdf:area(?iWKT) as ?area) where { yago:Eretria geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom. ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT. }",
    "Answer": "0.016864482313394547^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "29": {
    "Question": "Where is Cambridge located?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?geoWKT where { yago:Cambridge geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((0.408932 52.0593605,0.39305601 52.05 5167007,0.40138999 52.04277039,0.4003422 52.04203415,0.39111099 52.03554916,0.36555499 52.04417038,0.325279 52.07416916,0.306945 52.0819397,0.28666499 52.08499908,0.255833 52.07693863,0.206668 52.08166885,0.19388901 52.07638931,0.193611 52.05693817,0.176943 52.04804993,0.139167 52.04193878,0.115557 52.05582809,0.10639 52.05498886,0.108332 52.02750015,0.080556 52.002491,0.05139 52.04333115,0.0 52.04938889,-0.011388 52.05167007,-0.029444 52.03998947,-0.06722 52.03387833,-0.109168 52.0194397,-0.117222 52.02389145,-0.11861 52.03499985,-0.135556 52.04360962,-0.130833 52.05860901,-0.133609 52.06583023,-0.14611 52.06972122,-0.14524646 52.07259369,-0.15345195 52.0850029,-0.14191496 52.09906769,-0.15136185 52.13162231,-0.15390269 52.14036942,-0.21117117 52.15160751,-0.21945255 52.15367889,-0.246944 52.16054916,-0.248888 52.16360092,-0.233889 52.17277908,-0.235833 52.17943954,-0.253057 52.19194031,-0.29194301 52.20277023,-0.29225734 52.20760345,-0.29333401 52.22415924,-0.331669 52.22916031,-0.345833 52.22415924,-0.35527799 52.22721863,-0.36833301 52.24193954,-0.37111101 52.2677803,-0.41888899 52.27804947,-0.42944399 52.29748917,-0.45872799 52.30881882,-0.45879796 52.30920792,-0.48031938 52.31797409,-0.46881431 52.32131958,-0.50395745 52.36005783,-0.40238786 52.40266037,-0.35685602 52.46180344,-0.38123184 52.51247025,-0.39219683 52.53522491,-0.39076346 52.53781891,-0.39576155 52.5426178,-0.42875737 52.56967163,-0.43676245 52.56948853,-0.43771484 52.57337952,-0.42719987 52.57584,-0.40699765 52.57608032,-0.40124905 52.57614899,-0.37640256 52.57581329,-0.36618713 52.55986786,-0.34468895 52.55693436,-0.3276377 52.55076981,-0.3171688 52.54206085,-0.31321797 52.53877258,-0.27747706 52.55480194,-0.26808059 52.52754593,-0.2520147 52.53688049,-0.22828846 52.54131317,-0.19463731 52.54080582,-0.1942926 52.540802,-0.19344136 52.56152725,-0.04559393 52.5894928,-0.02587615 52.59362411,-0.04720359 52.6662674,-0.0470437 52.66631699,-0.0436792 52.66889572,-0.03366309 52.66449356,0.04007199 52.68536758,0.05374882 52.69400406,0.06713299 52.7024498,0.07225339 52.70635605,0.09166618 52.7211647,0.16612147 52.73897171,0.16975088 52.7403183,0.23579009 52.76480103,0.25303814 52.79319382,0.28427088 52.81489182,0.288432 52.82236099,0.29305601 52.82236099,0.29305601 52.82208252,0.29527801 52.82208252,0.29527801 52.82180405,0.29750001 52.82180405,0.29750001 52.82152939,0.299723 52.82152939,0.299723 52.82125092,0.30805501 52.82125092,0.30805501 52.82097244,0.30861101 52.82097244,0.30861101 52.82069397,0.309167 52.82069397,0.309167 52.8204155,0.30972099 52.8204155,0.30972099 52.82013702,0.31027699 52.82013702,0.31027699 52.81986237,0.31083301 52.81986237,0.31083301 52.81958389,0.31249899 52.81958389,0.31249899 52.81986237,0.31361201 52.81986237,0.31361201 52.82013702,0.31416801 52.82013702,0.31416801 52.8204155,0.32249999 52.8204155,0.32249999 52.82013702,0.32472199 52.82013702,0.32472199 52.81986237,0.32694501 52.81986237,0.32694501 52.81930542,0.33138901 52.81930542,0.33138901 52.81902695,0.332499 52.81902695,0.332499 52.81874847,0.33305499 52.81874847,0.33305499 52.81847382,0.334167 52.81847382,0.334167 52.81819534,0.334721 52.81819534,0.334721 52.8176384,0.33527699 52.8176384,0.33527699 52.81708527,0.334723 52.81708527,0.334721 52.81735992,0.334167 52.81735992,0.334167 52.8176384,0.331945 52.8176384,0.331945 52.81791687,0.32805499 52.81791687,0.32805499 52.8176384,0.327501 52.8176384,0.327501 52.81735992,0.32583201 52.81735992,0.32583201 52.81708527,0.325279 52.81708145,0.325279 52.81680679,0.32472199 52.81680679,0.32472199 52.81652832,0.324166 52.81652832,0.324166 52.81624985,0.32472199 52.81624985,0.32472199 52.81597137,0.325279 52.81597137,0.325279 52.8156929,0.32583201 52.8156929,0.32583201 52.81541824,0.32694501 52.81541824,0.32694501 52.81458282,0.327501 52.81458282,0.327501 52.81430435,0.32805499 52.81430435,0.32805499 52.81402588,0.32861099 52.81402588,0.32861099 52.81375122,0.32916701 52.81375122,0.32916701 52.81347275,0.329723 52.81347275,0.329723 52.81319427,0.330277 52.81319427,0.33027899 52.8129158,0.33083299 52.8129158,0.33083299 52.81263733,0.33138901 52.81263733,0.33138901 52.81236267,0.331945 52.81236267,0.331945 52.8120842,0.332499 52.8120842,0.332499 52.81180573,0.33305499 52.81180573,0.33305499 52.81152725,0.33749899 52.81152725,0.33749899 52.81124878,0.33805501 52.81124878,0.33805501 52.81097412,0.33861199 52.81097031,0.33861199 52.81041718,0.33916801 52.81041718,0.33916801 52.80986023,0.33972099 52.80986023,0.33972099 52.80902863,0.340278 52.80902863,0.340278 52.80847168,0.34083399 52.80847168,0.34083399 52.80791855,0.34139001 52.80791473,0.34139001 52.80764008,0.34194401 52.80764008,0.34194401 52.8073616,0.3425 52.8073616,0.3425 52.80708313,0.34305599 52.80708313,0.34305599 52.80680466,0.34361199 52.80680466,0.34361199 52.80652618,0.34416601 52.80652618,0.34416601 52.80625153,0.34527799 52.80625153,0.34527799 52.80597305,0.34583399 52.80597305,0.34583399 52.80569458,0.346944 52.80569458,0.346944 52.80541611,0.34805599 52.80541611,0.34805599 52.80513763,0.34916601 52.80513763,0.34916601 52.80486298,0.351944 52.80486298,0.351944 52.80541611,0.352501 52.80541611,0.352501 52.80597305,0.353057 52.80597305,0.353057 52.80652618,0.35361099 52.80652618,0.35361099 52.80764008,0.35416701 52.80764008,0.35416701 52.80819321,0.35472301 52.80819321,0.35472301 52.80875015,0.355279 52.80875015,0.355279 52.8093071,0.35583299 52.8093071,0.35583299 52.80986023,0.35638899 52.80986023,0.35638899 52.81041718,0.35694501 52.81041718,0.35694501 52.81097031,0.358055 52.81097412,0.358055 52.8120842,0.357501 52.8120842,0.357501 52.81375122,0.358055 52.81375122,0.358055 52.81458282,0.35861099 52.81458282,0.35861099 52.81430435,0.35916701 52.81430435,0.35916701 52.81402588,0.359723 52.81402588,0.359723 52.81347275,0.360277 52.81347275,0.360277 52.8129158,0.36083299 52.8129158,0.36083299 52.81263733,0.36138901 52.81263733,0.36138901 52.81236267,0.361945 52.81236267,0.361945 52.8120842,0.362499 52.8120842,0.362499 52.81180573,0.36305499 52.81180573,0.36305499 52.81152725,0.364167 52.81152725,0.364167 52.8120842,0.364721 52.8120842,0.364721 52.81263733,0.36750001 52.81263733,0.36750001 52.81319427,0.36694601 52.81319427,0.36694601 52.81458282,0.36750001 52.81458282,0.36750001 52.8148613,0.368056 52.8148613,0.368056 52.81513977,0.36861199 52.81513977,0.36861199 52.81541824,0.36916599 52.81541824,0.36916599 52.8156929,0.36972201 52.8156929,0.36972201 52.81597137,0.370278 52.81597137,0.370278 52.81624985,0.37083399 52.81624985,0.37083399 52.81652832,0.37138799 52.81652832,0.37138799 52.81708145,0.37194401 52.81708145,0.37194401 52.81791687,0.3725 52.81791687,0.3725 52.81874847,0.37361199 52.81874847,0.37361199 52.81930542,0.37416601 52.81930542,0.37416601 52.81986237,0.374722 52.81986237,0.374722 52.8204155,0.375278 52.8204155,0.375278 52.82069397,0.37638801 52.82069397,0.37638801 52.82097244,0.37694401 52.82097244,0.37694401 52.82125092,0.3775 52.82125092,0.3775 52.82152939,0.378057 52.82152939,0.378057 52.82180405,0.37860999 52.82180405,0.37860999 52.82208252,0.37916601 52.82208252,0.37916601 52.82236099,0.37972301 52.82236099,0.37972301 52.82291794,0.380279 52.82291794,0.380279 52.82347107,0.380833 52.82347107,0.380833 52.82374954,0.38194501 52.82374954,0.38194501 52.82402802,0.38250101 52.82402802,0.38250101 52.82430649,0.38361099 52.82430649,0.38361099 52.82458496,0.38416699 52.82458496,0.38416699 52.82485962,0.385277 52.82485962,0.385277 52.82513809,0.385833 52.82513809,0.385833 52.82597351,0.38638899 52.82597351,0.38638899 52.82680511,0.388055 52.82680511,0.388055 52.82736206,0.38861099 52.82736206,0.38861099 52.82764053,0.38916701 52.82764053,0.38916701 52.82819366,0.389723 52.82819366,0.389723 52.82875061,0.390277 52.82875061,0.390277 52.82902908,0.39138901 52.82902908,0.39138901 52.82930374,0.39194599 52.82930374,0.39194599 52.83013916,0.392499 52.83013916,0.392499 52.83124924,0.39305601 52.83124924,0.39305601 52.83152771,0.393612 52.83152771,0.393612 52.83180618,0.39416501 52.83180618,0.39416501 52.83208466,0.395834 52.83208466,0.395834 52.83235931,0.39694399 52.83235931,0.39694399 52.83263779,0.39750001 52.83263779,0.39750001 52.83319473,0.398056 52.83319473,0.398056 52.83375168,0.39861199 52.83375168,0.39861199 52.83402634,0.39916599 52.83402634,0.39916599 52.83430481,0.400278 52.83430481,0.400278 52.83458328,0.40083399 52.83458328,0.40083399 52.83486176,0.40138799 52.83486176,0.40138799 52.83514023,0.40194401 52.83514023,0.40194401 52.83541489,0.4025 52.83541489,0.4025 52.83597183,0.403056 52.83597183,0.403056 52.83625031,0.40360999 52.83625031,0.40360999 52.83652878,0.40416601 52.83652878,0.40416601 52.83708191,0.40472201 52.83708191,0.40472201 52.83763885,0.40527901 52.83763885,0.40527901 52.8381958,0.40583199 52.8381958,0.40583199 52.83874893,0.40694499 52.83874893,0.40694499 52.8390274,0.408611 52.8390274,0.408611 52.83930588,0.40972301 52.83930588,0.40972301 52.83958435,0.410833 52.83958435,0.410833 52.83986282,0.41638899 52.83986282,0.41638899 52.84013748,0.425834 52.84013748,0.425834 52.84041595,0.426388 52.84041595,0.42638999 52.84069443,0.42694399 52.84069443,0.42694399 52.84125137,0.42750001 52.84125137,0.42750001 52.84236145,0.428056 52.84236145,0.428056 52.84375,0.42861199 52.84375,0.42861199 52.84430695,0.42916599 52.84430695,0.42916599 52.84597397,0.42972201 52.84597397,0.42972201 52.84736252,0.430278 52.84736252,0.430278 52.84763718,0.430832 52.84763718,0.430832 52.84819412,0.43138799 52.84819412,0.43138799 52.84791565,0.43250099 52.84791565,0.43250099 52.84763718,0.433054 52.84763718,0.433054 52.84708405,0.43360999 52.84708405,0.43360999 52.84680557,0.434167 52.84680557,0.434167 52.8465271,0.43527901 52.8465271,0.43527901 52.84624863,0.43583301 52.84624863,0.43583301 52.84597397,0.43694499 52.84597397,0.43694499 52.8456955,0.43757799 52.8456955,0.440833 52.8456955,0.440833 52.84763718,0.44138899 52.84763718,0.44138899 52.84819412,0.44194499 52.84819412,0.44194499 52.84875107,0.44249901 52.84875107,0.44249901 52.8493042,0.443055 52.8493042,0.443055 52.84958267,0.443611 52.84958267,0.443611 52.84986115,0.44416699 52.84986115,0.44416699 52.85013962,0.44472101 52.85013962,0.44472101 52.85430527,0.44527701 52.85430527,0.44527701 52.85597229,0.445833 52.85597229,0.445833 52.85652924,0.44639 52.85652924,0.44639 52.85708237,0.44694301 52.85708237,0.44694301 52.85763931,0.44749999 52.85763931,0.44749999 52.85791779,0.44805601 52.85791779,0.44805601 52.85847092,0.44749999 52.85847092,0.44749999 52.85930634,0.44694301 52.85930634,0.44694301 52.86041641,0.44639 52.86041641,0.44639 52.86152649,0.445833 52.86152649,0.445833 52.86180496,0.44527701 52.86180496,0.44527701 52.86208344,0.44472101 52.86208344,0.44472101 52.86236191,0.44416699 52.86236191,0.44416699 52.86458588,0.44416699 52.86513901,0.443611 52.86513901,0.443611 52.86652756,0.443055 52.86652756,0.443055 52.86763763,0.443611 52.86763763,0.443611 52.86847305,0.44416699 52.86847305,0.44416699 52.86902618,0.44472101 52.86902618,0.44472101 52.87097168,0.44527701 52.87097168,0.44527701 52.87374878,0.445833 52.87374878,0.445833 52.87513733,0.44639 52.87513733,0.44639 52.87569427,0.44694301 52.87569427,0.44694301 52.87625122,0.44749999 52.87625122,0.44749999 52.87708282,0.44805601 52.87708282,0.44805601 52.87791824,0.448612 52.87791824,0.448612 52.87847137,0.449166 52.87847137,0.449168 52.87902832,0.44972199 52.87902832,0.44972199 52.87958145,0.45027801 52.87958145,0.45027801 52.8801384,0.45083401 52.8801384,0.45083401 52.88152695,0.45139 52.88152695,0.45139 52.88375092,0.45083401 52.88375092,0.45083401 52.88458252,0.45249999 52.88458252,0.45249999 52.88486099,0.45305601 52.88486099,0.45305601 52.88513947,0.453612 52.88513947,0.453612 52.88541794,0.454166 52.88541794,0.454166 52.8856926,0.45472199 52.8856926,0.45472199 52.88624954,0.45527801 52.88624954,0.45527801 52.88652802,0.455834 52.88652802,0.455834 52.88680649,0.456388 52.88680649,0.456388 52.88735962,0.45694399 52.88735962,0.45694399 52.88791656,0.45750001 52.88791656,0.45750001 52.88847351,0.458056 52.88847351,0.458056 52.88902664,0.45861 52.88902664,0.45861 52.88930511,0.45916599 52.88930511,0.45916599 52.88986206,0.459723 52.88986206,0.459723 52.89041519,0.46027899 52.89041519,0.46027899 52.89125061,0.460832 52.89125061,0.460832 52.89180374,0.46138901 52.89180374,0.46138901 52.89263916,0.461945 52.89263916,0.461945 52.89319611,0.46250099 52.89319611,0.46250099 52.89402771,0.46305501 52.89402771,0.46305501 52.89513779,0.46361101 52.89513779,0.46361101 52.89625168,0.464167 52.89625168,0.464167 52.89708328,0.46472299 52.89708328,0.46472299 52.89764023,0.46527699 52.89764023,0.46527699 52.89819336,0.46583301 52.89819336,0.46583301 52.89875031,0.466389 52.89875031,0.466389 52.89930725,0.46694499 52.89930725,0.46694499 52.90041733,0.46749899 52.90041733,0.46749899 52.90180588,0.46805501 52.90180588,0.46805501 52.90263748,0.468611 52.90263748,0.468611 52.90319443,0.46916699 52.90319443,0.46916699 52.90375137,0.46972099 52.90375137,0.46972099 52.90458298,0.47027701 52.90458298,0.47027701 52.90569305,0.470833 52.90569305,0.470833 52.90652847,0.471389 52.90652847,0.471389 52.90763855,0.471946 52.90763855,0.471946 52.91236115,0.47249901 52.91236115,0.47249901 52.91347122,0.47305501 52.91347122,0.47305501 52.91458511,0.47361201 52.91458511,0.47361201 52.91513824,0.474168 52.91513824,0.474168 52.91569519,0.474722 52.91569519,0.474722 52.91680527,0.47527799 52.91680527,0.47527799 52.92180634,0.47583401 52.92180634,0.47583401 52.92347336,0.47639 52.92347336,0.47639 52.92458344,0.476944 52.92458344,0.476944 52.92597198,0.47749999 52.92597198,0.47749999 52.92708206,0.47805601 52.92708206,0.47805601 52.92763901,0.47861201 52.92763901,0.47861201 52.92847061,0.479166 52.92847061,0.479166 52.93208313,0.47972199 52.93208313,0.47972199 52.93264008,0.48027799 52.93264008,0.48027799 52.93347168,0.48083401 52.93347168,0.48083401 52.93375015,0.481388 52.93375015,0.481388 52.93458176,0.48194399 52.93458176,0.48194399 52.93569565,0.48249999 52.93569565,0.48249999 52.93652725,0.48305601 52.93652725,0.48305601 52.9370842,0.48361 52.9370842,0.48361 52.93763733,0.484166 52.93763733,0.484166 52.93819427,0.48472199 52.93819427,0.48472199 52.93875122,0.48527801 52.93875122,0.48527801 52.93958282,0.48583201 52.93958282,0.48583201 52.94124985,0.48527801 52.94124985,0.48527801 52.94347382,0.48583201 52.94347382,0.48583201 52.94458389,0.486388 52.94458389,0.486388 52.94569397,0.486945 52.94569397,0.486945 52.94652939,0.487501 52.94652939,0.487501 52.94763947,0.48805699 52.94763947,0.48805699 52.94847107,0.48861101 52.94847107,0.48861101 52.94874954,0.489167 52.94874954,0.489167 52.94902802,0.489723 52.94902802,0.489723 52.94958496,0.49027899 52.94958496,0.49027899 52.94985962,0.49083301 52.94985962,0.49083301 52.95013809,0.49138901 52.95013809,0.49138901 52.95041656,0.491945 52.95041656,0.491945 52.95069504,0.49250099 52.95069504,0.49250099 52.95097351,0.49305499 52.95097351,0.49305499 52.95124817,0.49361101 52.95124817,0.49361101 52.95152664,0.494167 52.95152664,0.494167 52.95208359,0.49472299 52.95208359,0.49472299 52.95236206,0.49527699 52.95236206,0.49527699 52.95264053,0.49583301 52.95264053,0.49583301 52.95319366,0.496389 52.95319366,0.496389 52.95430374,0.49583301 52.95430374,0.49583301 52.95569611,0.496389 52.95569611,0.496389 52.95624924,0.49749899 52.95624924,0.49749899 52.95652771,0.49805501 52.95652771,0.49805501 52.95680618,0.49916801 52.95680618,0.49916801 52.95708466,0.49972099 52.95708466,0.49972099 52.95735931,0.50083399 52.95735931,0.50083399 52.95763779,0.50138998 52.95763779,0.50138998 52.95791626,0.50194401 52.95791626,0.50194401 52.95819473,0.5025 52.95819473,0.5025 52.95875168,0.50305599 52.95875168,0.50305599 52.95958328,0.50361198 52.95958328,0.50361198 52.95986176,0.50416601 52.95986176,0.50416601 52.96014023,0.504722 52.96014023,0.504722 52.96041489,0.50527799 52.96041489,0.50527799 52.96097183,0.50583398 52.96097183,0.50583398 52.96125031,0.50638801 52.96125031,0.50638801 52.96152878,0.506944 52.96152878,0.506944 52.96208191,0.50749999 52.96208191,0.50749999 52.96236038,0.50861001 52.96236038,0.50861198 52.96263885,0.509166 52.96263885,0.509166 52.96291733,0.50972199 52.96291733,0.50972199 52.9631958,0.51027799 52.9631958,0.51027799 52.96347046,0.51083398 52.96347046,0.51083398 52.96374893,0.511388 52.96374893,0.511388 52.96430588,0.511944 52.96430588,0.511944 52.96486282,0.51249999 52.96486282,0.51249999 52.96513748,0.51305699 52.96513748,0.51305699 52.96569443,0.51361001 52.96569443,0.51361001 52.96625137,0.51416701 52.96625137,0.51416701 52.9668045,0.514723 52.9668045,0.514723 52.96736145,0.515279 52.96736145,0.515279 52.96763992,0.51583302 52.96763992,0.51583302 52.96819305,0.51638901 52.96819305,0.51638901 52.96875,0.516945 52.96875,0.516945 52.96930695,0.517501 52.96930695,0.517501 52.96986008,0.51805502 52.96986008,0.51805502 52.97013855,0.51861101 52.97013855,0.51861101 52.97041702,0.51916701 52.97041702,0.51916701 52.9706955,0.519723 52.9706955,0.519723 52.97097397,0.52027702 52.97097397,0.52027702 52.97124863,0.52138901 52.97124863,0.52138901 52.9715271,0.521945 52.9715271,0.521945 52.97180557,0.52305502 52.97180557,0.52305502 52.97208405,0.52361101 52.97208405,0.52361101 52.97236252,0.524167 52.97236252,0.524167 52.97263718,0.52472103 52.97263718,0.52472299 52.97291565,0.52527702 52.97291565,0.52527702 52.97319412,0.52583301 52.97319412,0.52583301 52.9734726,0.52639002 52.9734726,0.52639002 52.97402954,0.52694601 52.97402954,0.52694601 52.9743042,0.52749902 52.9743042,0.52749902 52.97458267,0.52805603 52.97458267,0.52805603 52.97486115,0.52861202 52.97486115,0.52861202 52.97513962,0.53027803 52.97513962,0.53027803 52.97541809,0.53139001 52.97541809,0.53139001 52.97569275,0.53305602 52.97569275,0.53305602 52.97597122,0.53527802 52.97597122,0.53527802 52.97624969,0.53750002 52.97624969,0.53750002 52.97652817,0.53916597 52.97652817,0.53916597 52.97513962,0.53860998 52.97513962,0.53860998 52.97486115,0.53750002 52.97486115,0.53750002 52.97458267,0.53305602 52.97458267,0.53305602 52.9743042,0.53027803 52.9743042,0.53027803 52.97402954,0.53138798 52.97402954,0.53139001 52.97375107,0.53305602 52.97375107,0.53305602 52.9734726,0.53361201 52.9734726,0.53361201 52.97319412,0.53472197 52.97319412,0.53472197 52.97291565,0.53583401 52.97291565,0.53583401 52.97263718,0.53805602 52.97263718,0.53805602 52.97291565,0.53860998 52.97291565,0.53860998 52.97319412,0.53916597 52.97319412,0.53916597 52.9734726,0.53972203 52.9734726,0.53972203 52.97375107,0.54027897 52.97375107,0.54027897 52.97402954,0.54138899 52.97402954,0.54138899 52.9743042,0.54250097 52.9743042,0.54250097 52.97458267,0.54361099 52.97458267,0.54361099 52.97486115,0.54472297 52.97486115,0.54472297 52.97541809,0.555278 52.97541809,0.555278 52.97569275,0.555834 52.97569275,0.555834 52.97513962,0.55638999 52.97513962,0.55638999 52.97486115,0.55861199 52.97486115,0.55861199 52.97513962,0.56138802 52.97513962,0.56138802 52.97486115,0.5625 52.97486115,0.5625 52.97458267,0.56305599 52.97458267,0.56305599 52.97486115,0.56583202 52.97486115,0.56583202 52.97458267,0.566944 52.97458267,0.566944 52.9743042,0.56861103 52.9743042,0.56861103 52.97402954,0.56916702 52.97402954,0.56916702 52.97375107,0.570279 52.97375107,0.570279 52.97124863,0.57083303 52.97124863,0.57083303 52.97097397,0.57194501 52.97097397,0.57194501 52.97124863,0.572501 52.97124863,0.572501 52.97180557,0.57527697 52.97180557,0.57527697 52.97208405,0.57583302 52.97208405,0.57583302 52.97236252,0.57638901 52.97236252,0.57638901 52.97263718,0.57749897 52.97263718,0.57749897 52.97291565,0.57805502 52.97291565,0.57805502 52.97319412,0.57861102 52.97319412,0.57861102 52.97375107,0.57916701 52.97375107,0.57916701 52.97402954,0.57972097 52.97402954,0.57972097 52.9743042,0.58083397 52.9743042,0.58083397 52.97458267,0.58249998 52.97458267,0.58249998 52.97486115,0.58583403 52.97486115,0.58583403 52.97458267,0.58749998 52.97458267,0.58749998 52.9743042,0.58805603 52.9743042,0.58805603 52.97458267,0.58861202 52.97458267,0.58861202 52.97597122,0.58916599 52.97597122,0.58916599 52.97624969,0.590832 52.97624969,0.590832 52.97597122,0.59194398 52.97597122,0.59194398 52.97569275,0.59472299 52.97569275,0.59472299 52.97541809,0.59750098 52.97541809,0.59750098 52.97513962,0.59805501 52.97513962,0.59805501 52.97486115,0.59916699 52.97486115,0.59916699 52.97458267,0.60027701 52.97458267,0.60027701 52.9743042,0.60138899 52.9743042,0.60138899 52.97402954,0.60472101 52.97402954,0.60472101 52.97375107,0.60638899 52.97375107,0.60638899 52.9734726,0.61416602 52.9734726,0.61416602 52.97375107,0.61472201 52.97375107,0.61472201 52.97402954,0.61527801 52.97402954,0.61527801 52.9743042,0.615834 52.9743042,0.615834 52.97458267,0.61694402 52.97458267,0.61694402 52.97513962,0.618056 52.97513962,0.618056 52.97458267,0.61861002 52.97458267,0.61861002 52.9743042,0.61972201 52.9743042,0.61972201 52.97402954,0.62194502 52.97402954,0.62194502 52.97375107,0.62250102 52.97375107,0.62250102 52.9734726,0.62527901 52.9734726,0.62527901 52.97375107,0.62583297 52.97375107,0.62583297 52.97402954,0.62805498 52.97402954,0.62805498 52.97375107,0.62972301 52.97375107,0.62972301 52.97402954,0.63194501 52.97402954,0.63194501 52.97458267,0.63416803 52.97458267,0.63416803 52.97486115,0.63749999 52.97486115,0.63749999 52.97513962,0.639166 52.97513962,0.639166 52.97541809,0.64083397 52.97541809,0.64083397 52.97569275,0.64249998 52.97569275,0.64249998 52.97597122,0.64416599 52.97597122,0.64416599 52.97624969,0.64583403 52.97624969,0.64583403 52.97652817,0.64694399 52.97652817,0.64694399 52.97680664,0.64861 52.97680664,0.64861 52.97708511,0.65027899 52.97708511,0.65027899 52.97958374,0.65083301 52.97958374,0.65083301 52.98014069,0.65250099 52.98014069,0.65250099 52.97986221,0.65305501 52.97986221,0.65305501 52.97958374,0.653611 52.97958374,0.653611 52.97930527,0.654167 52.97930527,0.654167 52.97902679,0.65472299 52.97902679,0.65472299 52.97847366,0.65527701 52.97847366,0.65527701 52.97791672,0.65916699 52.97791672,0.65916699 52.97819519,0.66139001 52.97819519,0.66139001 52.97847366,0.66361201 52.97847366,0.66361201 52.97874832,0.66515499 52.97874832,0.66527802 52.97874832,0.66527802 52.97864151,0.66527802 52.97847366,0.665474 52.97847366,0.66638798 52.97847366,0.66638798 52.97819519,0.66805601 52.97819519,0.66805601 52.97791672,0.66916603 52.97791672,0.66916603 52.97763824,0.67027801 52.97763824,0.67027801 52.97735977,0.670834 52.97735977,0.670834 52.97708511,0.67194402 52.97708511,0.67194402 52.97680664,0.67250001 52.97680664,0.67250001 52.97652817,0.67360997 52.97652817,0.67360997 52.97597122,0.67416602 52.97597122,0.67416602 52.97513962,0.67472303 52.97513962,0.67472303 52.9743042,0.67527902 52.9743042,0.67527902 52.9734726,0.67583197 52.9734726,0.67583197 52.97291565,0.67527902 52.97291565,0.67527902 52.97263718,0.67472303 52.97263718,0.67472303 52.97236252,0.67360997 52.97236252,0.67360997 52.97208405,0.67305601 52.97208405,0.67305601 52.9715271,0.67250001 52.9715271,0.67250001 52.97097397,0.67194402 52.97097397,0.67194402 52.97041702,0.66983402 52.97041702,0.66916603 52.97041702,0.66916603 52.97013855,0.668612 52.97013855,0.668612 52.96986008,0.66805601 52.96986008,0.66805601 52.9695816,0.66750002 52.9695816,0.66750002 52.96946335,0.66750002 52.96930695,0.66694403 52.96930695,0.66694403 52.96819305,0.668612 52.96819305,0.668612 52.96847153,0.66916603 52.96847153,0.66916603 52.96875,0.670834 52.96875,0.670834 52.96902847,0.67194402 52.96902847,0.67194402 52.96930695,0.67250001 52.96930695,0.67250001 52.9695816,0.67305601 52.9695816,0.67305601 52.96986008,0.67360997 52.96986008,0.67360997 52.97041702,0.67416602 52.97041702,0.67416602 52.97097397,0.67472303 52.97097397,0.67472303 52.97180557,0.67638898 52.97180557,0.67638898 52.97208405,0.67750102 52.97208405,0.67750102 52.97236252,0.67861098 52.97236252,0.67861098 52.97375107,0.67972302 52.97375107,0.67972302 52.97402954,0.68305498 52.97402954,0.68305498 52.9743042,0.68416703 52.9743042,0.68416703 52.97458267,0.68472302 52.97458267,0.68472302 52.97486115,0.68583298 52.97486115,0.68583298 52.97513962,0.68694299 52.97513962,0.68694299 52.97541809,0.68805498 52.97541809,0.68805498 52.97569275,0.68916798 52.97569275,0.68916798 52.97624969,0.68972099 52.97624969,0.68972099 52.97708511,0.69027799 52.97708511,0.69027799 52.97791672,0.69083399 52.97791672,0.69083399 52.97847366,0.69138998 52.97847366,0.69138998 52.97902679,0.69287598 52.97902679,0.69305599 52.97902679,0.69305599 52.97930527,0.69805598 52.97930527,0.69805598 52.97958374,0.69972199 52.97958374,0.69972199 52.97986221,0.699166 52.97986221,0.699166 52.98014069,0.69805598 52.98014069,0.69805598 52.98041534,0.69361198 52.98041534,0.69361198 52.98069382,0.69027799 52.98069382,0.69027799 52.98041534,0.68916798 52.98041534,0.68916798 52.98014069,0.68861198 52.98014069,0.68861198 52.97986221,0.68805498 52.97986221,0.68805498 52.9796524,0.68749899 52.97958374,0.68749899 52.97930527,0.68694299 52.97930527,0.68694299 52.97902679,0.68638903 52.97902679,0.68638903 52.97847366,0.68583298 52.97847366,0.68583298 52.97791672,0.68527699 52.97791672,0.68527699 52.97763824,0.68416703 52.97763824,0.68416703 52.97735977,0.68249899 52.97735977,0.68249899 52.97708511,0.68194503 52.97708511,0.68194503 52.97680664,0.68138897 52.97680664,0.68138897 52.97652817,0.68083298 52.97652817,0.68083298 52.97624969,0.68027699 52.97624969,0.68027699 52.97597122,0.67916697 52.97597122,0.67916697 52.97624969,0.67861098 52.97624969,0.67861098 52.97652817,0.67805499 52.97652817,0.67805499 52.97680664,0.67750102 52.97680664,0.67750102 52.97791672,0.67805499 52.97791672,0.67805499 52.97819519,0.67861098 52.97819519,0.67861098 52.98088074,0.67861098 52.98208237,0.67916697 52.98208237,0.67916697 52.98319626,0.67972302 52.98319626,0.67972302 52.98513794,0.67583197 52.98513794,0.67583197 52.98485947,0.67527902 52.98485947,0.67527902 52.98458481,0.67472303 52.98458481,0.67472303 52.98430634,0.67416602 52.98430634,0.67416602 52.98402786,0.67305601 52.98402786,0.67305601 52.98374939,0.67250001 52.98374939,0.67250001 52.98347092,0.670834 52.98347092,0.670834 52.98319626,0.66916603 52.98319626,0.66916603 52.98291779,0.668612 52.98291779,0.668612 52.98236084,0.66805601 52.98236084,0.66805601 52.98208237,0.66750002 52.98208237,0.66750002 52.98180389,0.66638798 52.98180389,0.66638798 52.98152924,0.66527802 52.98152924,0.66527802 52.98125076,0.66416597 52.98125076,0.66416597 52.98097229,0.660833 52.98097229,0.660833 52.98069382,0.65916699 52.98069382,0.65916699 52.98097229,0.658611 52.98097229,0.658611 52.98152924,0.65805501 52.98152924,0.65805501 52.98180389,0.65749902 52.98180389,0.65749902 52.98208237,0.65694499 52.98208237,0.65694499 52.98236084,0.656389 52.98236084,0.656389 52.98291779,0.65583301 52.98291779,0.65583301 52.98569489,0.656389 52.98569489,0.656389 52.98680496,0.65694499 52.98680496,0.65694499 52.98736191,0.65972102 52.98736191,0.65972102 52.98764038,0.66805601 52.98764038,0.66805601 52.98791504,0.67138797 52.98791504,0.67138797 52.98819351,0.68972099 52.98819351,0.68972099 52.98791504,0.694166 52.98791504,0.694166 52.98764038,0.696944 52.98764038,0.696944 52.98736191,0.70027798 52.98736191,0.70027798 52.98708344,0.701388 52.98708344,0.701388 52.98680496,0.70194501 52.98680496,0.70194501 52.98652649,0.70305401 52.98652649,0.70305401 52.98625183,0.70416701 52.98625183,0.70416701 52.98597336,0.70638901 52.98597336,0.70638901 52.98569489,0.70861101 52.98569489,0.70861101 52.98541641,0.71083301 52.98541641,0.71083301 52.98513794,0.71361101 52.98513794,0.71361101 52.98485947,0.71639001 52.98485947,0.71639001 52.98458481,0.71916598 52.98458481,0.71916598 52.98430634,0.72083402 52.98430634,0.72083402 52.98402786,0.72305602 52.98402786,0.72305602 52.98374939,0.72472203 52.98374939,0.72472203 52.98347092,0.72694403 52.98347092,0.72694403 52.98319626,0.72972298 52.98319626,0.72972298 52.98291779,0.73194498 52.98291779,0.73194498 52.98263931,0.73361099 52.98263931,0.73361099 52.98236084,0.73583299 52.98236084,0.73583299 52.98208237,0.73861098 52.98208237,0.73861098 52.98180389,0.74138999 52.98180389,0.74138999 52.98152924,0.74249899 52.98152924,0.74249899 52.98125076,0.74416798 52.98125076,0.74416798 52.98097229,0.74472201 52.98097229,0.74472201 52.98069382,0.74583399 52.98069382,0.74583399 52.98041534,0.74638999 52.98041534,0.74638999 52.98014069,0.74694401 52.98014069,0.74694401 52.97986221,0.74805599 52.97986221,0.74805599 52.97958374,0.74861199 52.97958374,0.74861199 52.97902679,0.74916601 52.97902679,0.74916601 52.97819519,0.749722 52.97819519,0.749722 52.97763824,0.750278 52.97763824,0.750278 52.97708511,0.749722 52.97708511,0.749722 52.97680664,0.74916601 52.97680664,0.74916601 52.97652817,0.74861199 52.97652817,0.74861199 52.97624969,0.7475 52.97624969,0.7475 52.97569275,0.74694401 52.97569275,0.74694401 52.97486115,0.74638999 52.97486115,0.74638999 52.9743042,0.74694401 52.9743042,0.74694401 52.97402954,0.7475 52.97402954,0.7475 52.97375107,0.750278 52.97375107,0.750278 52.9734726,0.7525 52.9734726,0.7525 52.97291565,0.75305599 52.97291565,0.75305599 52.97236252,0.7525 52.97236252,0.7525 52.97180557,0.75194401 52.97180557,0.75194401 52.97134018,0.75194401 52.97124863,0.75138801 52.97124863,0.75138801 52.9706955,0.750278 52.9706955,0.750278 52.97013855,0.75083399 52.97013855,0.75083399 52.9695816,0.75361001 52.9695816,0.75361001 52.97013855,0.75416601 52.97013855,0.75416601 52.97097397,0.754722 52.9709816,0.754722 52.9734726,0.75416601 52.9734726,0.75416601 52.97458267,0.75361001 52.97458267,0.75361001 52.97486115,0.75138801 52.97486115,0.75138801 52.97652817,0.75194401 52.97652817,0.75194401 52.97708511,0.7525 52.97708511,0.7525 52.97763824,0.75305599 52.97763824,0.75305599 52.97791672,0.75416601 52.97791672,0.75416601 52.97819519,0.754722 52.97819519,0.754722 52.97847366,0.75694501 52.97847366,0.75694501 52.97874832,0.75861102 52.97874832,0.75861102 52.97902679,0.76027697 52.97902679,0.76027697 52.97930527,0.76305503 52.97930527,0.76305503 52.97902679,0.76527703 52.97902679,0.76527703 52.97874832,0.76972097 52.97874832,0.76972097 52.97902679,0.77083403 52.97902679,0.77083403 52.97930527,0.77139002 52.97930527,0.77139002 52.97958374,0.77194399 52.97958374,0.77194399 52.98014069,0.77249998 52.98014069,0.77249998 52.98069382,0.77305597 52.98069382,0.77305597 52.98041534,0.77416599 52.98041534,0.77416599 52.97930527,0.77472198 52.97930527,0.77472198 52.97902679,0.77527797 52.97902679,0.77527797 52.97874832,0.78083199 52.97874832,0.78083199 52.97847366,0.78305697 52.97847366,0.78305697 52.97819519,0.785833 52.97819519,0.785833 52.97791672,0.788055 52.97791672,0.788055 52.97763824,0.790833 52.97763824,0.790833 52.97735977,0.79361099 52.97735977,0.79361099 52.97708511,0.79521525 52.97708511,0.78424901 52.90484619,0.81730157 52.86837387,0.80006588 52.84498596,0.73623049 52.82981873,0.74982077 52.79619217,0.71668321 52.7684021,0.71617287 52.76789093,0.69577366 52.74746323,0.69024718 52.72141647,0.69616807 52.69034958,0.62058157 52.67062759,0.61404079 52.69218826,0.53779751 52.66053391,0.56822824 52.64560318,0.56879258 52.5884819,0.53367436 52.58924103,0.53969175 52.55817795,0.5743674 52.55028915,0.60790306 52.52338028,0.56162471 52.44611359,0.55833203 52.44638824,0.491943 52.43138885,0.45615086 52.43205261,0.44722101 52.43222046,0.44406089 52.43082047,0.42036125 52.4283905,0.37057853 52.40243149,0.37551475 52.38841248,0.43273211 52.34287643,0.42661935 52.3090744,0.46319178 52.30309677,0.48372531 52.28961563,0.46721914 52.27343369,0.43576095 52.25477219,0.430554 52.25387955,0.39117706 52.27288818,0.38277701 52.27693939,0.38253367 52.27913284,0.36750001 52.28998947,0.349722 52.25777054,0.35467723 52.25397873,0.34865892 52.23060989,0.36541224 52.22592545,0.38191175 52.23311615,0.4016833 52.24172211,0.41031864 52.24415588,0.44860899 52.23416138,0.50179708 52.20745087,0.49649718 52.20380783,0.48706958 52.19732285,0.47250882 52.16456985,0.46410865 52.16322708,0.461667 52.16389084,0.45806089 52.16226196,0.43397325 52.15840912,0.4333787 52.15780258,0.39805156 52.12173462,0.40350971 52.10902405,0.398056 52.10443878,0.408932 52.0593605))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "30": {
    "Question": "What is type of Dublin?",
    "Query": "select ?e where { yago:Dublin rdf:type ?e }",
    "Answer": "http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_City_Council"
  },
  "31": {
    "Question": "Where is Galatsi located?",
    "Query": "select ?geoWKT where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Galatsi> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((23.7519416809083 38.0242614746094,23 3.7522201538087 38.0245323181152,23.7525787353516 38.0250396728516,23.7527503967286 38.0252113342286,23.7538738250733 38.0265808105469,23.7541370391846 38.0265846252443,23.7545261383057 38.0265579223633,23.7548446655274 38.02645111084,23.7553043365479 38.0263328552247,23.755542755127 38.0263061523439,23.7560214996338 38.0262794494629,23.7562580108643 38.0262985229493,23.7565135955811 38.0262451171876,23.7567405700685 38.0262184143066,23.7570877075195 38.0261917114258,23.7573204040528 38.0262031555177,23.7575397491455 38.0262641906738,23.7577743530275 38.0264015197755,23.7580242156982 38.0266265869141,23.7582321166992 38.0268707275392,23.7584075927734 38.0270080566407,23.7588138580323 38.026969909668,23.7592887878418 38.0267295837403,23.7594604492188 38.0265922546388,23.7596893310548 38.026439666748,23.760124206543 38.0263442993164,23.7603855133057 38.0263900756837,23.7605762481689 38.0264968872071,23.7607269287109 38.0268936157226,23.7607784271241 38.0273551940919,23.7607536315919 38.0276145935059,23.7607707977296 38.0278778076172,23.7609519958497 38.0282363891602,23.761323928833 38.0288238525391,23.761573791504 38.0291023254395,23.7618923187256 38.0290870666503,23.7620925903321 38.0288887023925,23.7624206542969 38.0284652709961,23.7627067565918 38.0281410217285,23.7629489898682 38.0279426574706,23.7632503509523 38.0277366638185,23.7636890411378 38.0278816223146,23.763879776001 38.0280380249023,23.7646350860596 38.029109954834,23.7650947570801 38.0296783447266,23.7652721405029 38.0298500061035,23.7659606933594 38.0303916931153,23.766315460205 38.030689239502,23.7668266296388 38.0310249328613,23.7675876617433 38.0313415527344,23.7685661315919 38.0317153930664,23.7688694000245 38.0316772460938,23.7691593170166 38.0315895080566,23.7696342468262 38.0313377380372,23.7700538635254 38.031219482422,23.7699337005616 38.0310134887696,23.7698268890381 38.0307426452638,23.7696723937989 38.030101776123,23.7695064544678 38.0296173095703,23.7694282531738 38.0293006896973,23.7694110870362 38.0290832519532,23.7692413330079 38.0284805297852,23.768581390381 38.0270462036134,23.7682971954346 38.0265045166015,23.7681770324708 38.0261802673341,23.767427444458 38.0246276855469,23.7672157287599 38.0239944458009,23.7666053771973 38.0220222473144,23.7664394378663 38.021598815918,23.7662887573243 38.0212821960449,23.766227722168 38.0210647583008,23.7661952972412 38.0208473205568,23.7661609649659 38.0205154418946,23.7661724090576 38.020263671875,23.7663383483887 38.0197677612305,23.7664070129395 38.0194969177247,23.7664318084717 38.0191650390626,23.7663803100587 38.0187568664552,23.7662582397461 38.0183067321778,23.7660961151124 38.0180435180665,23.7659187316896 38.0178375244141,23.7658500671387 38.0177917480469,23.7654495239257 38.0175666809083,23.7649955749512 38.0173416137696,23.7647895812988 38.0171127319337,23.764711380005 38.016716003418,23.7647190093995 38.0163383483887,23.7649288177491 38.0157432556152,23.7649688720704 38.0155029296875,23.7646884918214 38.0152130126954,23.7643795013428 38.0149765014649,23.7641296386719 38.0147323608398,23.7639217376709 38.0144462585449,23.7638320922852 38.0142745971681,23.7635955810547 38.0139198303223,23.7634315490724 38.0137062072754,23.7631511688232 38.0133895874023,23.7629890441895 38.0131645202637,23.7628402709961 38.0129203796387,23.7627506256104 38.0127372741699,23.7627029418946 38.0125389099121,23.7626991271973 38.0122718811036,23.7626667022705 38.0119895935059,23.7621841430665 38.0097618103028,23.7619705200196 38.0091972351075,23.7618045806885 38.0086708068847,23.7616806030273 38.0082588195802,23.7616500854492 38.0080604553224,23.7615661621094 38.0073394775391,23.761547088623 38.0069847106934,23.7615528106689 38.0064620971681,23.7615032196045 38.0060386657715,23.761344909668 38.0051727294922,23.7613258361818 38.0048866271973,23.7613563537597 38.0039749145509,23.7612857818605 38.0031738281251,23.7612819671631 38.0029678344727,23.7612266540527 38.0026054382324,23.7609748840331 38.002758026123,23.7607021331787 38.0029907226564,23.7602005004883 38.0033683776855,23.7599849700928 38.0035667419434,23.7595138549806 38.0039253234863,23.7593421936036 38.0041236877441,23.758939743042 38.004493713379,23.7587699890137 38.0046920776368,23.7583427429199 38.005241394043,23.7581844329834 38.0053825378419,23.7577114105225 38.005672454834,23.7572345733643 38.0058860778809,23.7566432952881 38.006046295166,23.756425857544 38.006145477295,23.7560806274415 38.0062522888184,23.7558345794679 38.0062904357911,23.7555294036865 38.0062713623048,23.7550773620605 38.0062065124512,23.7543659210206 38.0061416625977,23.7540912628174 38.0061340332031,23.7534656524659 38.0061759948732,23.7531204223633 38.0062408447267,23.752685546875 38.0063362121583,23.752281188965 38.0064620971681,23.7519359588624 38.0066070556641,23.7516021728516 38.0066413879395,23.7512531280518 38.0066032409668,23.7502937316894 38.0064239501954,23.749740600586 38.0063591003419,23.7493915557862 38.0062942504882,23.7485313415528 38.0060958862304,23.7480392456056 38.0060653686525,23.747932434082 38.0060386657715,23.7477741241455 38.0060920715333,23.7477378845215 38.0061111450195,23.7475738525391 38.0061836242677,23.747329711914 38.0062446594238,23.7469692230225 38.0063247680664,23.7467117309571 38.0063781738282,23.7464084625245 38.0063972473145,23.7461338043213 38.0063781738282,23.7458610534669 38.0063133239747,23.7453842163087 38.0062675476075,23.7451400756837 38.0062561035157,23.744592666626 38.006275177002,23.7442035675049 38.0063209533692,23.7439594268799 38.0063438415528,23.7435398101808 38.0064086914063,23.7432670593262 38.0064506530762,23.7429084777832 38.0065231323242,23.7426490783693 38.0066146850587,23.7423610687256 38.0067291259766,23.7421169281007 38.0068283081056,23.7418880462648 38.0069465637208,23.7416152954101 38.0070991516114,23.7414016723634 38.007251739502,23.7412300109864 38.0074119567872,23.7410430908203 38.0076179504395,23.7409591674805 38.0077896118165,23.7408885955811 38.0080337524414,23.7409057617188 38.0084037780762,23.7409801483155 38.0086555480958,23.7410259246826 38.0089454650879,23.7411289215088 38.0092048645021,23.7412910461427 38.0094757080079,23.7414512634278 38.0097389221192,23.7416400909425 38.0099983215333,23.741771697998 38.0102424621582,23.7419052124024 38.0104789733887,23.7420635223389 38.0107040405273,23.7422103881836 38.0108757019044,23.7423267364503 38.0110359191895,23.7425174713135 38.0113983154298,23.7427654266357 38.0118675231935,23.7429714202881 38.0122833251954,23.7430877685548 38.0125427246095,23.7431926727295 38.0127449035645,23.7432518005371 38.0130233764648,23.7432689666749 38.013256072998,23.743169784546 38.0136070251466,23.7430572509766 38.013858795166,23.7429714202881 38.0140686035157,23.7428874969484 38.0142745971681,23.7428035736085 38.014591217041,23.7427768707277 38.0149040222169,23.7427806854249 38.0153541564941,23.7427558898926 38.0157775878907,23.7426872253418 38.0160598754883,23.7425880432129 38.0162925720216,23.7425460815431 38.0164833068849,23.7425193786621 38.0167541503907,23.7424640655518 38.0169944763184,23.7423667907715 38.0173645019531,23.7422981262207 38.0176544189454,23.7423133850098 38.017906188965,23.7424011230469 38.018123626709,23.7425174713135 38.0183219909669,23.7426929473878 38.0185356140138,23.742811203003 38.0187263488771,23.7429847717286 38.0188636779786,23.7432899475098 38.0190887451172,23.7436218261719 38.019287109375,23.7438526153565 38.019386291504,23.7442016601563 38.0195312500001,23.7444171905518 38.01961517334,23.7447948455812 38.019760131836,23.7450389862061 38.0198211669923,23.7454147338868 38.0198936462403,23.7456455230714 38.0199317932128,23.745876312256 38.0199775695801,23.7464065551758 38.0201568603517,23.7469921112061 38.0204849243165,23.7476711273193 38.0209617614747,23.7477378845215 38.0210075378419,23.7481708526611 38.0213088989259,23.7490024566651 38.0218238830568,23.7494068145753 38.0220489501954,23.7497520446777 38.0222663879395,23.7501106262207 38.022518157959,23.7508125305177 38.0230979919434,23.7512741088868 38.0235404968263,23.7515544891358 38.0238647460938,23.7518119812011 38.0241355895996,23.7519416809083 38.0242614746094))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>MULTIPOLYGON(((478228.3125 4208536,478252.8125 4208566,478284.40625 4208622,478299.5 4208641,47839 98.5 4208793,478421.6875 4208793,478455.8125 4208790,478483.8125 4208778,478524.09375 4208765,478545 4208762,478586.90625 4208759,478607.8125 4208761,478630.09375 4208755,478650.09375 4208752,478680.59375 4208749,478701 4208750,478720.1875 4208757,478740.8125 4208772,478762.8125 4208797,478781.09375 4208824,478796.59375 4208839,478832.1875 4208835,478873.8125 4208808,478888.90625 4208793,478909 4208776,478947.09375 4208765,478970.09375 4208770,478986.8125 4208782,479000.1875 4208826,479004.8125 4208877,479002.59375 4208906,479004.3125 4208935,479020.1875 4208975,479053 4209040,479075.09375 4209071,479103.09375 4209069,479120.59375 4209047,479149.1875 4209000,479174.1875 4208964,479195.5 4208942,479221.90625 4208919,479260.3125 4208935,479277.1875 4208952,479343.8125 4209071,479384.3125 4209134,479399.8125 4209153,479460.5 4209213,479491.59375 4209246,479536.6875 4209283,479603.5 4209318,479689.40625 4209359,479716.09375 4209355,479741.40625 4209345,479783.09375 4209317,479819.90625 4209304,479809.3125 4209281,479799.90625 4209251,479786.1875 4209180,479771.40625 4209126,479764.5 4209091,479762.90625 4209067,479747.90625 4209000,479689.59375 4208841,479664.5 4208781,479653.8125 4208745,479587.59375 4208573,479568.8125 4208503,479514.6875 4208284,479500 4208237,479486.6875 4208202,479481.3125 4208178,479478.40625 4208154,479475.3125 4208117,479476.1875 4208089,479490.6875 4208034,479496.59375 4208004,479498.59375 4207967,479494.09375 4207922,479483.1875 4207872,479468.8125 4207843,479453.1875 4207820,479447.1875 4207815,479412 4207790,479372.09375 4207765,479353.90625 4207740,479346.90625 4207696,479347.59375 4207654,479365.8125 4207588,479369.1875 4207561,479344.5 4207529,479317.40625 4207503,479295.3125 4207476,479277 4207444,479269.09375 4207425,479248.1875 4207386,479233.8125 4207362,479209.09375 4207327,479194.8125 4207302,479181.59375 4207275,479173.6875 4207255,479169.5 4207233,479169.09375 4207203,479166.09375 4207172,479123.09375 4206925,479104.3125 4206862,479089.5 4206804,479078.59375 4206758,479075.8125 4206736,479068.1875 4206656,479066.40625 4206617,479066.8125 4206559,479062.3125 4206512,479048.1875 4206416,479046.5 4206384,479048.8125 4206283,479042.40625 4206194,479042.09375 4206171,479037.09375 4206131,479015 4206148,478991.1875 4206174,478947.1875 4206216,478928.40625 4206238,478887 4206278,478872 4206300,478836.90625 4206341,478822 4206363,478784.59375 4206424,478770.8125 4206440,478729.3125 4206472,478687.59375 4206496,478635.59375 4206514,478616.6875 4206525,478586.3125 4206537,478564.6875 4206541,478537.90625 4206539,478498.3125 4206532,478435.8125 4206525,478411.59375 4206524,478356.8125 4206529,478326.40625 4206536,478288.3125 4206547,478252.90625 4206561,478222.5 4206577,478193.3125 4206581,478162.6875 4206577,478078.3125 4206557,478029.8125 4206550,477999.09375 4206543,477923.59375 4206521,477880.3125 4206518,477870.90625 4206515,477857.09375 4206521,477853.8125 4206523,477839.5 4206531,477818.09375 4206538,477786.5 4206547,477763.8125 4206553,477737.3125 4206555,477713.1875 4206553,477689.09375 4206546,477647.3125 4206541,477625.8125 4206540,477577.8125 4206542,477543.59375 4206547,477522.1875 4206550,477485.5 4206557,477461.5 4206562,477430 4206570,477407.3125 4206580,477382.09375 4206593,477360.6875 4206604,477340.59375 4206617,477316.6875 4206634,477297.90625 4206651,477282.90625 4206669,477266.6875 4206692,477259.3125 4206711,477253.1875 4206738,477254.8125 4206779,477261.40625 4206807,477265.5 4206839,477274.6875 4206868,477288.90625 4206898,477303.09375 4206927,477319.8125 4206956,477331.40625 4206983,477343.09375 4207009,477357.1875 4207034,477370.09375 4207053,477380.3125 4207071,477397.1875 4207111,477419.1875 4207163,477437.3125 4207209,477447.6875 4207238,477456.8125 4207260,477462.09375 4207291,477463.6875 4207317,477455.1875 4207356,477445.3125 4207384,477437.90625 4207407,477430.59375 4207430,477423.3125 4207465,477421.09375 4207500,477421.59375 4207550,477419.5 4207597,477413.5 4207628,477404.90625 4207654,477401.3125 4207675,477399 4207705,477394.1875 4207732,477385.8125 4207773,477379.8125 4207805,477381.3125 4207833,477389.09375 4207857,477399.40625 4207879,477414.8125 4207903,477425.1875 4207924,477440.5 4207939,477467.3125 4207964,477496.59375 4207986,477516.90625 4207997,477547.5 4208013,477566.5 4208022,477599.59375 4208038,477621.09375 4208045,477654.09375 4208053,477674.40625 4208057,477694.6875 4208062,477741.3125 4208082,477792.8125 4208118,477852.5 4208171,477858.3125 4208176,477896.5 4208209,477969.59375 4208266,478005.09375 4208291,478035.5 4208315,478067 4208343,478128.90625 4208407,478169.5 4208456,478194.1875 4208492,478216.8125 4208522,478228.3125 4208536)));http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/2100^^<http://strdf.di.uoa.gr/ontology#WKT>"
  },
  "32": {
    "Question": "Where is Mitchelstown located?",
    "Query": "select ?geoWKT where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mitchelstown> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "POLYGON ((-8.50432735919634 52.2786332031176, -8.48043414146394 52.2406907990896, -8.4775433914442 21 52.2406359135451, -8.47518667088797 52.2376758655678, -8.47661762250425 52.2344175462321, -8.46790972920174 52.2284222252233, -8.46401138762603 52.2305196671629, -8.46140459634734 52.2293012201604, -8.4539097457013 52.2307909062027, -8.45218772347309 52.2275853412429, -8.44968964298776 52.225669109186, -8.44747844755739 52.2263700563974, -8.43738734273309 52.2171924265554, -8.44359453977039 52.2154304113149, -8.43613460777722 52.2108551546802, -8.43613459335548 52.208601915447, -8.43239040287308 52.2097718942003, -8.41434130382197 52.2132076613167, -8.41300486399609 52.2114478702373, -8.41462612548342 52.2097126215051, -8.40903644724806 52.2096946173607, -8.40837517156633 52.2080569609664, -8.41052021188004 52.207397908682, -8.40713202782 52.2010450818066, -8.40085996488577 52.198981950748, -8.39838743967006 52.2045006007507, -8.38619128103325 52.2122008635579, -8.38003021421684 52.2124219228433, -8.37471288364187 52.2145604650846, -8.3681062961019 52.2128623281259, -8.36060754889737 52.2148664521837, -8.35325950790265 52.214089103152, -8.34927764315231 52.2052677410392, -8.33877453154031 52.2050359424784, -8.33989240631344 52.2068883385928, -8.33321864540639 52.209728877844, -8.33634250730919 52.2104055576407, -8.33505705313257 52.2111626915158, -8.32767986299582 52.209457134812, -8.32604236977445 52.2053163159592, -8.31541158102156 52.211405546964, -8.31979701319673 52.21791618735, -8.3252684269627 52.218426021839, -8.32640963777548 52.2215616012883, -8.30828179221329 52.2170848566566, -8.28764672675831 52.2174734505995, -8.2795029248204 52.2119899692199, -8.26581440378601 52.2203121694334, -8.25147179220492 52.2244264821984, -8.24949021476221 52.2223201952891, -8.20332886485187 52.2272799151731, -8.20208629941527 52.2254561401466, -8.19378358538558 52.2267239703058, -8.1792326257453 52.2262137822932, -8.16058631007099 52.2295681179437, -8.16095220667625 52.2419284834569, -8.16149136731433 52.253044167586, -8.16558248927631 52.2599651041468, -8.16263896428942 52.2656030524177, -8.16931178046423 52.266461349856, -8.16434075367955 52.2728600504013, -8.16513932722271 52.2776170436779, -8.17657978755122 52.2766807362349, -8.18320596724645 52.2876758031396, -8.1956049549727 52.2871538445356, -8.2073831478804 52.2944553368723, -8.22088613460165 52.2936480164157, -8.22537387886041 52.2960832365995, -8.2438186847749 52.2958242067118, -8.24640940558026 52.2971401735112, -8.24929048664296 52.2970286923785, -8.25246964283061 52.2941837779148, -8.2560003218632 52.2943861417186, -8.26502240128592 52.2914514337066, -8.27386232838976 52.2911990472598, -8.28071592792243 52.2873954992405, -8.28120709278641 52.2853787343208, -8.28787654259055 52.290285137805, -8.290928098545 52.2907272954169, -8.29704360663037 52.294801203034, -8.29951925078152 52.3029424091974, -8.31140079672661 52.3169354842541, -8.31095300041189 52.3240682831858, -8.3143995372967 52.3238392210454, -8.32146767510903 52.3197570914781, -8.33050219583311 52.3195306749877, -8.33355441437014 52.3201709873109, -8.3318294438715 52.322500862366, -8.33350380535649 52.3273327446569, -8.34102737203107 52.3292766695288, -8.35231051093366 52.3223827483166, -8.35724516000226 52.3225974156882, -8.3625854596595 52.3199371248091, -8.36357903016835 52.3088852993121, -8.38133628064655 52.3042311304085, -8.38470367943873 52.3009025669043, -8.38641558573574 52.2946270884236, -8.44138338039686 52.2925607428369, -8.45194634799502 52.2872961410901, -8.48229943458205 52.2854095883781, -8.50460355356512 52.2805065143662, -8.50432735919634 52.2786332031176))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "33": {
    "Question": "Where is Loch Ness located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?geoWKT WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Loch_Ness> geo:hasGeometry ?o.   ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-4.4536369 57.330310700000005, -4.453...   more"
  },
  "34": {
    "Question": "Where is the location of Lake Kerkini?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?geoWKT WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lake_Kerkini> geo:hasGeometry ?o.   ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((23.176795600000002 41.247251000000006...   more"
  },
  "35": {
    "Question": "Where is Lough Derg located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?geoWKT WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lough_Derg_(Shannon)> geo:hasGeometry ?o.   ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-8.504264000000001 52.908957, -8.5041...   more"
  },
  "36": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Santorini?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population WHERE{         yago:geoentity_Dimos_Santorini_8133832 y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population }",
    "Answer": "population 11051^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "37": {
    "Question": "What is the area of West Sussex?",
    "Query": "SELECT (strdf:area(?geoWKT) AS ?area) ?g WHERE{         yago:West_Sussex geo:hasGeometry ?g.         ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "0.25089719891548157^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "38": {
    "Question": "What is the area of Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT (strdf:area(?geoWKT) AS ?area) WHERE{         yago:Republic_of_Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?g.         ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "9.458364486694336^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "39": {
    "Question": "Where is Crete located?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?xWKT WHERE {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Crete> geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.  }",
    "Answer": "too big to fit here"
  },
  "40": {
    "Question": "Where is London located?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?xWKT WHERE {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_City_of_London_2643744> geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.  }",
    "Answer": "too big to fit here"
  },
  "41": {
    "Question": "Where is Lough Derg located?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?xWKT WHERE {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lough_Derg_(Shannon)> geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.  }",
    "Answer": "too big to fit here"
  },
  "42": {
    "Question": "Is Crete an island?",
    "Query": "ASK {  yago:Crete rdf:type   y2geoo:OSM_island. }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "43": {
    "Question": "What is population of Kalithea?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population {            yago:Kallithea  y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population . }",
    "Answer": "109609^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "44": {
    "Question": "What is the national level of Plymouth?",
    "Query": "select ?nationalLevel  where {   yago:Plymouth y2geoo:hasGADM_NationalLevel  ?nationalLevel . }",
    "Answer": "3rdOrder"
  },
  "45": {
    "Question": "Where is Lough Ree located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?x1WKT  WHERE {      yago:Lough_Ree geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo. ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.  }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-8.0711086 53.5819525, -8.07120960000 00001 53.582033200000005, -8.071197900000001 53.582141500000006, ….............."
  },
  "46": {
    "Question": "What is the total area of Liverpool?",
    "Query": "select distinct (strdf:area(?geoWKT)as ?totalArea) where { yago:Liverpool geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "totalArea                                                                                                                                                                                                                 0.018048301339149475^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "47": {
    "Question": "Where is Dublin located?",
    "Query": "select ?geoWKT where { yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "geoWKT MULTIPOLYGON (((-6.16321572721054 53.3411099322235, -6.16412004567249 53.3411312746422, -6.1650334...   More"
  },
  "48": {
    "Question": "What population does Megara have?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population WHERE{ yago:Megara  y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population . }",
    "Answer": "population 28943^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "49": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Vironas?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population WHERE {   yago:geoentity_Dimos_Vyronas_8133859    y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population . }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "50": {
    "Question": "Where is Dublin located?",
    "Query": "SELECT  ?xWKT WHERE {   yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT . }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "51": {
    "Question": "What is the total area of Manchester?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct (strdf:area(?xWKT)as ?totalArea) WHERE {   yago:Manchester geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT . }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "52": {
    "Question": "Where is Nafpaktia located?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?geoWKT where {     yago:Nafpaktia geo:hasGeometry ?o.     ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((21.6654205322267 38.3518104553222,21...   more  MULTIPOLYGON(((323671.3125 4292854,323710.90625 4292847,323750.6875 4292851,323829 4292866,323982....   more"
  },
  "53": {
    "Question": "What is the population of region Crete?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?pop WHERE { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Crete>   <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/hasGAG_Population>  ?pop. }",
    "Answer": "pop 564267^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "54": {
    "Question": "Where is York located?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?geoWKT where {         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/York> geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.}",
    "Answer": "geoWKT <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-0.94001359 53.89125061,-0.95081896 ...   more <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-1.01753094913679 53.8887116828545,-...   more"
  },
  "55": {
    "Question": "How many citizens does Astypalaia have?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?p  WHERE {        <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Astypalaia> y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?p  }",
    "Answer": "1238^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "56": {
    "Question": "Where is the Isle of Portland located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?geoWKT  WHERE {        yago:Isle_of_Portland geo:hasGeometry ?g.     ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-2.44996817590899 50.5556823289207,- -2.4499645375593 50.555752468155,-2.44995078014518 50.5557866848822,-2.44983116179091 50.5558267050238,-2.44980593578041 50.5558421761073,-2.44978919150107 50.5558683129921,-2.44975198027395 50.5559574618026,-2.44970601584249 50.5560196732024,-2.44964275915927 50.5560504849666,-2.4495251448166 50.5561544188325,-2.44952806645921 50.556167893157,-2.44957381538469 50.5562297502574,-2.44956130875556 50.556248678415,-2.44954171098994 50.5562685329996,-2.44942935327693 50.5563256064506,-2.44936205996213 50.5563726163756,-2.44929798825291 50.5564646557544,-2.44927721594232 50.5565078898801,-2.44922928635817 50.5566573155953,-2.44918734814582 50.5567024294731,-2.44908481697176 50.5567648589055,-2.44904710033045 50.5568010559431,-2.44896214270809 50.5569245522149,-2.44894109646566 50.5569390180401,-2.44884842877099 50.5569861255295,-2.44881642577602 50.557035696159,-2.44872781970909 50.5570693022838,-2.44863510431969 50.5571236920128,-2.44847326898214 50.5571800561862,-2.44838629803993 50.5572388288794,-2.448311860344 50.5574163164619,-2.44823293339282 50.557734071563,-2.44823603392621 50.5577664250726,-2.44827122985446 50.5580531732711,-2.44832843394856 50.5582795110806,-2.44842307708626 50.5585750206191,-2.4486045567878 50.5589565032705,-2.44878553544246 50.5592849441871,-2.44924399071873 50.5599900907898,-2.44951998604937 50.5603577215103,-2.44985241361487 50.5607224363546,-2.44996080430978 50.5608343973778,-2.45015995959484 50.5609919482439,-2.45056170158405 50.5613734747032,-2.45070269232547 50.5614979852932,-2.45100570010561 50.5617422494816,-2.45254270024394 50.5628694335844,-2.45288942653043 50.5631064204468,-2.45321221038994 50.5633470057496,-2.45428843477785 50.5641108598664,-2.4554751334981 50.5649191338163,-2.45621581610788 50.5654432500518,-2.45683695199316 50.5658707345514,-2.45831846266229 50.566926046705,-2.45924114444379 50.5675788884928,-2.45955679712336 50.5677979972083,-2.46015114470284 50.5682299749831,-2.46164246183511 50.5692609318019,-2.46187157233321 50.569438122561,-2.46416375406509 50.5710612100101,-2.46571489176417 50.5721306244269,-2.466806496052 50.5728429656087,-2.4682126110375 50.5738004583501,-2.46821261995392 50.5738013573525,-2.46949765826493 50.5746496387529,-2.47072198045857 50.575488172115,-2.47132454302455 50.5758716011908,-2.47169565037929 50.5761173335427,-2.47279615467849 50.5768629365827,-2.47414398045543 50.5777549643282,-2.47419801188437 50.5777898067267,-2.4748475967502 50.5782115946736,-2.4760792103051 50.5790501316191,-2.47699756475127 50.5796417151491,-2.47716654065488 50.5797345225862,-2.47756050946093 50.5800009102304,-2.47859687691573 50.580673809349,-2.47885126324473 50.5808282967637,-2.48021926869184 50.5817354545325,-2.48146452110882 50.5825226328928,-2.482301658024 50.5830281128089,-2.48266701710981 50.5832586401385,-2.48333521816308 50.583686686537,-2.48333955462976 50.5836893656449,-2.48389694479806 50.5840539472641,-2.48414014417552 50.5842156618798,-2.48457697708727 50.5845205060234,-2.48473895622881 50.5846206137627,-2.485135405196 50.5848482168535,-2.4858635821318 50.5853281428975,-2.48692556919496 50.5859891732127,-2.4871402104091 50.5861240298703,-2.48751523768646 50.5863275303754,-2.48808962039046 50.5866848284018,-2.49035692741802 50.5881897283625,-2.491203077104 50.5887365517034,-2.49201382413566 50.5892708420745,-2.49224421516288 50.5894165010733,-2.49293803990557 50.5898388997088,-2.49320405606183 50.5900158722392,-2.49360062028311 50.5902462329496,-2.493815036461 50.5903559051972,-2.49397309070439 50.590466715229,-2.49404269855546 50.5905068765156,-2.49451721252326 50.5907611772852,-2.49468067288991 50.5908540725685,-2.49494680409662 50.5910408401117,-2.49581034676143 50.5916145270076,-2.49591936718635 50.591647327035,-2.49698225275597 50.5923666988557,-2.49756388665236 50.5927240089449,-2.49928412525206 50.5937499069467,-2.49994792627261 50.5941301377455,-2.50030169159387 50.5943166065806,-2.50065681836966 50.5944993824378,-2.50167650719895 50.5949887438244,-2.50252225769439 50.5954742620368,-2.50293035598621 50.5957180266516,-2.50333569162534 50.5959644988826,-2.50413232759462 50.5964727834774,-2.50400048399095 50.5965623587898,-2.50257446634411 50.5975865007557,-2.50116827640659 50.5986186309743,-2.50016394925165 50.5975744046209,-2.49931833235427 50.5967065989732,-2.49867717493756 50.5960690536482,-2.49830217587298 50.5957478154566,-2.49792603083236 50.5954499558761,-2.49761704562257 50.5952238208195,-2.49706242047934 50.5948789823056,-2.49620028819121 50.594446537425,-2.49583835924658 50.5942798697139,-2.49556723523876 50.5941632503275,-2.49518971269185 50.5939976359089,-2.49443590180505 50.5936500357039,-2.49376361633317 50.5934002596267,-2.49285031067626 50.592936450769,-2.49254933484952 50.5927929796336,-2.49214560226282 50.5925581505435,-2.49137986692343 50.5920118939792,-2.49081856706163 50.5917004080704,-2.49017433784705 50.5912876775395,-2.48990454349625 50.5911502716231,-2.4895212923822 50.5909783696598,-2.48921886595944 50.5908276138079,-2.4886299025864 50.5905639723876,-2.48821423874554 50.5903993045334,-2.4873283178223 50.590106244251,-2.48700706483382 50.5900599395606,-2.48682587529298 50.590019341661,-2.48646462908517 50.5899236657994,-2.48629028977095 50.5898695529008,-2.48604970623834 50.589682658946,-2.48565842175161 50.5892822427734,-2.48537566211125 50.5889803567842,-2.48486209814674 50.5884897348476,-2.48464510656317 50.5882738806413,-2.48434119637345 50.5881115207063,-2.48348784867399 50.587830882188,-2.48295740298845 50.587474278351,-2.48272936689866 50.587281841322,-2.48233277938542 50.5870415542836,-2.48216641526786 50.5869343590069,-2.48200144946195 50.5868271577026,-2.48154483780146 50.586513395458,-2.48118174975259 50.5862334083075,-2.48051977238209 50.5855832619568,-2.4802932876957 50.5852667466405,-2.48008934352356 50.5850706088589,-2.47978211851126 50.584865006985,-2.47951780839582 50.584710562552,-2.47854503274582 50.584197439158,-2.47834616860385 50.5840876748731,-2.47800482306963 50.5838579344863,-2.47785992069051 50.583774918906,-2.47771226029386 50.5836955106099,-2.47749949924687 50.5836045917716,-2.47735048975606 50.5835413712155,-2.47684640168176 50.5834211679779,-2.47662737446234 50.5834013870391,-2.47640534683013 50.5833843150777,-2.47591366262937 50.5833619621757,-2.47542099207014 50.5833919351789,-2.47496320357365 50.583520567953,-2.47485071263033 50.5835677767542,-2.47452294929242 50.5837022605354,-2.47381612020606 50.584070238269,-2.47308857137562 50.5843358056841,-2.47268581563264 50.5844606096738,-2.4724055420468 50.5845354683071,-2.47159599643503 50.5846620083686,-2.47134735892064 50.5846630152865,-2.47103652372033 50.5846516868291,-2.47068386069601 50.5845568263451,-2.47015092411857 50.5843692830401,-2.47020621284104 50.5839688085992,-2.47017304084264 50.5839006157792,-2.47017667792392 50.5838448608107,-2.47019943082033 50.5837089244596,-2.4701904817067 50.5836640087635,-2.47017301345974 50.5836173293986,-2.4701125734734 50.5835006986913,-2.47008810911601 50.5834531485266,-2.46994250475077 50.5832981130944,-2.46958833822739 50.5826295799101,-2.46952996150268 50.5824391296268,-2.46940722295629 50.5823110622951,-2.46898116538355 50.5813676217634,-2.46860264605432 50.5806596258613,-2.46835971492117 50.58023607807,-2.4681173424145 50.5798566702341,-2.46791988851243 50.5796029465705,-2.46761894664249 50.579305585469,-2.46731499138978 50.5789857597399,-2.46720924118533 50.5788666122141,-2.46710500527925 50.5787474585146,-2.46678168033249 50.5783287250579,-2.46642753871567 50.5779371751876,-2.4662918440738 50.5777803872062,-2.46625732735659 50.5777282913712,-2.46609546866077 50.5774924926328,-2.46583506827053 50.5771473155221,-2.4654494114596 50.5764275601305,-2.46530391207105 50.5761376626661,-2.46521933063594 50.5760031450325,-2.46503891572886 50.5757619347941,-2.46488645252351 50.5754738626756,-2.46474275506445 50.5752244139838,-2.46460416299848 50.5750676355477,-2.46442411866838 50.5747095479039,-2.46435232991763 50.5745847780916,-2.46426923076596 50.5744583451691,-2.46418324776819 50.5743346207988,-2.46400791249057 50.5741707059327,-2.46377381101018 50.5739153230459,-2.46367122151438 50.5738195346303,-2.46366981550946 50.5738186411924,-2.46349831355354 50.5736178497154,-2.46315019550633 50.5732523377693,-2.46243652908459 50.572630163588,-2.46211483733112 50.5723697310107,-2.46181185327613 50.5721407795698,-2.46163272982236 50.5720164338049,-2.46145360819069 50.5718921776597,-2.46133280814942 50.5718144401179,-2.46121205154019 50.5717411075666,-2.46096213867305 50.5716045445794,-2.46075944030555 50.5715217364893,-2.46067884106433 50.571506771831,-2.460540586423 50.5715252996535,-2.46050113323824 50.5715389413104,-2.46046880830406 50.5715552518726,-2.46042003998328 50.5716165793855,-2.46039619652553 50.571631058304,-2.46037368003205 50.5716383396623,-2.46031289693356 50.5716376809946,-2.46019531426343 50.5716030833946,-2.46015836848776 50.5715753592553,-2.46009559259922 50.5715135737389,-2.4600728921383 50.5715019759593,-2.46003892381306 50.5714930299174,-2.45999941174705 50.5714886908685,-2.45995986209033 50.5714924433005,-2.45990214833457 50.5715080448863,-2.45983863248835 50.5715136900367,-2.45981460502992 50.5715092897562,-2.45974517594713 50.5714816038874,-2.45972657060991 50.5714601004443,-2.45972068192517 50.5714412438931,-2.4597412760542 50.5713800279468,-2.45973408918742 50.5713593784463,-2.45970983159214 50.5713432915533,-2.45969148280658 50.5713361717061,-2.45913142704027 50.571249377201,-2.45763473010662 50.5711176280297,-2.45704817401611 50.5715039117891,-2.45653152041727 50.5716669569333,-2.45600165956632 50.5717769183512,-2.45585726691708 50.5717388252423,-2.45518944678467 50.5711739655546,-2.45528438759464 50.5710585173544,-2.45475489150684 50.5709158419075,-2.45450783343835 50.570771072679,-2.45444152374515 50.5707767257958,-2.45438918019565 50.5707697378217,-2.45436778340154 50.5707482444196,-2.45396725728092 50.5706500138349,-2.45357569396914 50.5706119825239,-2.45317398070065 50.5711296850248,-2.45306076533326 50.5712461915657,-2.45302014601863 50.5712841092594,-2.45298076847838 50.5713058394172,-2.45283307654135 50.571360356343,-2.45282039479961 50.5713613047137,-2.45199991540524 50.5710695190136,-2.45196056220879 50.5709357151047,-2.45196712509672 50.5708915468416,-2.45199642596253 50.5708509763474,-2.45205119329353 50.5708192973354,-2.45221455414302 50.5707719128324,-2.45240374301165 50.5707711777186,-2.45252494049842 50.5707464325954,-2.45266853444088 50.5707018214108,-2.45276369601881 50.5706088503639,-2.45285122853461 50.5704609776696,-2.45213163732108 50.5702227426512,-2.45201154540145 50.5702169157692,-2.45196058268363 50.5702081232654,-2.45166328904347 50.5701292627466,-2.45161371098371 50.5701069791419,-2.45149157757316 50.5700337317609,-2.45061637587798 50.5697628264058,-2.44997458271563 50.5695494499465,-2.44945914304466 50.5693878162827,-2.44879329219128 50.5691655358165,-2.44860064078016 50.5690952543746,-2.44811576790104 50.5688902532083,-2.44796682698564 50.5688251966701,-2.44791143662326 50.5687912463548,-2.44779736032072 50.5688177573715,-2.44768701467196 50.5687957058467,-2.44764528589391 50.5688641932565,-2.4476199404034 50.5696169657395,-2.447595055765 50.5696692955598,-2.44754710160473 50.5696829655177,-2.44752562234437 50.5696523908882,-2.44750139649288 50.5693197498967,-2.44750493803049 50.5688089925064,-2.44749867677795 50.5687379925315,-2.44712873974319 50.5685963770806,-2.44697157216723 50.5685475335634,-2.44681863851603 50.5685031687751,-2.44651588657183 50.5684360035716,-2.44632222096443 50.5684178664883,-2.44622754746596 50.5684155323376,-2.44604971988813 50.5684225071659,-2.44595103364952 50.5684390679768,-2.44575400045824 50.5685081495904,-2.44582125835713 50.5688990636754,-2.44581418223916 50.5689017878919,-2.44570118751322 50.5688950282869,-2.4456342530474 50.5685382763599,-2.44543709175592 50.5685938723476,-2.44510408798352 50.5686149250123,-2.44502736879249 50.5687141125822,-2.44488546644172 50.5686418328898,-2.44458331734826 50.5686384920968,-2.44428487717931 50.5685838911694,-2.44407867436862 50.5685819809002,-2.44375444931735 50.5686452510232,-2.44347346868376 50.5687884598241,-2.44347804519039 50.5694368288855,-2.44345423983356 50.5694557993826,-2.44342621797636 50.569472088822,-2.44261391115644 50.569433824607,-2.44260678420575 50.5694311545913,-2.44260042533356 50.5686037937317,-2.44227537978915 50.568567269586,-2.44200123630603 50.568545834915,-2.44190692455256 50.5685821545321,-2.44179826520496 50.5685906583367,-2.44170752809871 50.5686979882607,-2.44159291878055 50.5686678557987,-2.44142118193192 50.5687287427566,-2.44131970859198 50.5687462991512,-2.44122384765882 50.5687664413949,-2.4411450510455 50.5687937111976,-2.44100134990528 50.5694381469718,-2.44091362423114 50.5698683094849,-2.44104982794939 50.5699415146285,-2.44085626888771 50.5706833250083,-2.44077981986242 50.5709624062246,-2.44058538011276 50.5716232160299,-2.44043955107567 50.5721785641805,-2.44039401340566 50.5723019945598,-2.44033561531199 50.5723948163772,-2.44022596055333 50.5724473753168,-2.43860397222207 50.5728141021288,-2.43856095726849 50.5727459373292,-2.43856231265757 50.5727414370341,-2.43997839797325 50.5724069555512,-2.44010054152078 50.5723201861909,-2.44029820703971 50.5721665123625,-2.44089561316659 50.5700590637105,-2.44079571217619 50.5699460733383,-2.4400027028918 50.5697054342318,-2.439454453946 50.5695177183373,-2.43891912425764 50.569341638645,-2.43874507089756 50.569604903884,-2.43865550614629 50.5697015284273,-2.43863801309044 50.5697861039372,-2.43858242544895 50.5698807124011,-2.43836047244249 50.5700137969715,-2.43822127472769 50.5700691624147,-2.43783982816112 50.5702036554513,-2.43734538323205 50.5703314694379,-2.43707978807568 50.5703287809577,-2.43647245062837 50.5704615102626,-2.43518289564449 50.5707262503765,-2.432454297842 50.5712993969596,-2.43213423093827 50.5713500326867,-2.43207553430607 50.5712719443832,-2.43140045974008 50.5717160555634,-2.43132927955089 50.571660579001,-2.43132783315087 50.5716551901342,-2.43200567831754 50.5711957854447,-2.43195153740674 50.5711447412081,-2.43266214067738 50.5707167673083,-2.43371572366314 50.5701112102419,-2.43471388113004 50.5701020926176,-2.43645190328377 50.5700650216162,-2.43659439605309 50.570051001684,-2.4365943706762 50.5698971763584,-2.43660424991988 50.5698953412276,-2.43669034399011 50.5699013115418,-2.43672560408437 50.5700379229545,-2.43732705027108 50.5700365639167,-2.43735797392516 50.5698682376981,-2.43736924186759 50.5698654982465,-2.4374950191952 50.5698695207787,-2.43751465622605 50.5700160800927,-2.43773189050731 50.5699891013828,-2.43788260632242 50.5699453806922,-2.43820745261817 50.5697967159847,-2.43829150701909 50.5697334668539,-2.43839531816542 50.5696538706644,-2.43853463135898 50.5696110911074,-2.43863526435371 50.56949024082,-2.43870341515818 50.5693820094985,-2.43862385602567 50.5693274679825,-2.43864129882868 50.5692374984276,-2.43736435499546 50.5690363336669,-2.43766516427828 50.5688823665262,-2.43756288019138 50.5688126260738,-2.43725473615061 50.5689288608969,-2.43736569000907 50.568262975876,-2.43693576640238 50.5681899702786,-2.43691396191957 50.5681234333782,-2.43682213333067 50.5681138885978,-2.43672743591612 50.5681088497007,-2.43657694187163 50.5681634464488,-2.43645549323579 50.5681612047757,-2.4363153590095 50.5681274767703,-2.43602554601747 50.568097995427,-2.43595843097798 50.568167562671,-2.43579735078088 50.5681474879691,-2.43571355454373 50.5690209476672,-2.43560340475967 50.5690195618476,-2.43559918876162 50.56901688051,-2.43568556433639 50.5681325328775,-2.43511172715212 50.5680699485446,-2.43499295095017 50.5689643062538,-2.4349872712309 50.5689670245933,-2.43487702222309 50.5689548499989,-2.4349370244066 50.5681128562596,-2.43460948214876 50.5679558489156,-2.4345528956665 50.567942574604,-2.43449914459382 50.5679337848728,-2.43440360494265 50.5679889828016,-2.43434718388128 50.5679936885401,-2.43431304234804 50.5681169841876,-2.43413453550527 50.5680628087501,-2.43393849589911 50.5680770253162,-2.43386015146255 50.5680017981327,-2.43381910646215 50.5679947588048,-2.43370517333815 50.5678980872268,-2.4333814951214 50.5678570379833,-2.43304997717643 50.5683447414449,-2.43292437036106 50.568663558119 ,-2.43321309827222 50.568891828567,-2.43311739848743 50.5689299442979,-2.43280029959218 50.5686802021893,-2.43295426187711 50.5683810590277,-2.43240115225565 50.5682680381021,-2.43239958118847 50.5682617506702,-2.43243995102803 50.5681950718669,-2.4329846448015 50.5683045277608,-2.43325141697245 50.5678404404852,-2.43334308196561 50.567667393994,-2.43236058955834 50.5677034129013,-2.43234897031069 50.5678203310457,-2.43227552766965 50.5678224018878,-2.43220216029232 50.5678199772125,-2.43218153006003 50.5677283519,-2.43105564661087 50.5676668969223,-2.43071778582416 50.5676276908759,-2.43063381354804 50.5677134102104,-2.43080989683386 50.567821542279,-2.43104873128278 50.5679933633436,-2.43110241612374 50.5679949626053,-2.4311910224091 50.567957773839,-2.43129579364929 50.5679951452898,-2.43135856832924 50.5680614415099,-2.43159228413344 50.5681441857323,-2.43143644048883 50.5683911898519,-2.43005337695148 50.5680114296394,-2.42996409309188 50.5681277354076,-2.4301200012362 50.5681937781398,-2.43007953803897 50.5682505670596,-2.42962362401699 50.5681092137016,-2.42967411403725 50.5680667725394,-2.42982973430961 50.5681012604804,-2.42990348582265 50.5679796179522,-2.42922683786582 50.567799520384,-2.42904593000684 50.5677750142699,-2.42882972143023 50.5677605273525,-2.42856972393357 50.5677444031903,-2.42844695312239 50.5677502493804,-2.42825948260639 50.5677851027264,-2.42774236224423 50.5679030700029,-2.42698858116843 50.5680883422781,-2.42682680425792 50.5681581615478,-2.4267121338174 50.5682746478011,-2.42614716598896 50.5684196646078,-2.42593940807979 50.5683871606233,-2.4249674089128 50.568647029121,-2.42444070571978 50.5688017873406,-2.42412659936539 50.5688929259733,-2.42256261625019 50.5692628143989,-2.42245860946282 50.5693234274618,-2.4224135749258 50.5693388745434,-2.42235153486672 50.5693534842742,-2.4222909278296 50.5693590983943,-2.42224434338698 50.5693574693134,-2.42221029220634 50.5693512995643,-2.42211106506174 50.5693085056222,-2.42208982411651 50.5692897028521,-2.42207255343175 50.5692591981892,-2.42206506600384 50.5692160715196,-2.42207321911481 50.5691773833265,-2.42213028351352 50.569088081737,-2.42218091798839 50.5690609269604,-2.4222753183231 50.5690327143587,-2.4223612884375 50.5690252101424,-2.42246735942055 50.56903920982,-2.42254599833559 50.5689930734437,-2.42304164563637 50.5688276482242,-2.42320584497495 50.5687154807321,-2.42337882959213 50.5686483228563,-2.42390735475199 50.5685277262473,-2.42427059439665 50.5684112360547,-2.42487941082718 50.5682867461875,-2.42495274935302 50.5682729928952,-2.42496401764214 50.5682702546421,-2.42507806510307 50.5682392709156,-2.42583464936354 50.5680539108627,-2.42662170993328 50.5678019053584,-2.42761453651307 50.5675050859049,-2.42816921622978 50.5673313305574,-2.42822069605247 50.5672439344623,-2.4282614044421 50.5672140265248,-2.42840324671971 50.5671289949626,-2.42842514260225 50.566591109599,-2.42842608023133 50.566219713353,-2.42838539054066 50.5660975938732,-2.42830358667531 50.5659476655701,-2.42826899311962 50.5658686774638,-2.42824135994147 50.5657869666229,-2.42823776703193 50.5656988740611,-2.42803083829738 50.5654613000497,-2.4278704669967 50.5653638944623,-2.42744676241925 50.5652017362612,-2.42703018142777 50.5650288518234,-2.42691801495013 50.5649707358592,-2.42674050553532 50.5648572088733,-2.42637303596441 50.5645015472548,-2.42625639148157 50.5643984951171,-2.42620510708892 50.5643528319378,-2.42574529536197 50.5640964905757,-2.42553634584794 50.5639425300896,-2.42543830831477 50.5638628740123,-2.42534432916636 50.5637814049437,-2.42526875801795 50.5637015767179,-2.42520167753092 50.5636209082908,-2.42509296086542 50.5634539942583,-2.42503570769561 50.5633786840751,-2.4249188998393 50.5632568412686,-2.42465855398399 50.5630437302431,-2.42447987048875 50.5629535790845,-2.42439177638968 50.562891866633,-2.42430222831271 50.5628237762382,-2.42408749262531 50.5626465491148,-2.42382871210197 50.5624514112966,-2.42358812817374 50.5622212340616,-2.4234698934904 50.5621082954643,-2.42330856432273 50.5619146898703,-2.42297491899406 50.5615480160158,-2.42284212074306 50.5613812772511,-2.42265748568193 50.5610932663855,-2.42252194368794 50.5609318415399,-2.42238718914322 50.5607021765989,-2.42229927607183 50.5605037180232,-2.42219172064165 50.5603215133325,-2.42195194191346 50.5600230027468,-2.42186777307238 50.5599306168941,-2.42168698748796 50.5597595555002,-2.42139276422798 50.5593855418626,-2.4213496099588 50.5592975922303,-2.42134875980152 50.5592022971289,-2.42135219222721 50.5591042894042,-2.42139279479518 50.5589062638254,-2.42139399100956 50.5588837835076,-2.42141355378247 50.5587020167971,-2.42140171805906 50.5586409249624,-2.42137708700747 50.5585807784896,-2.42133276935648 50.5585189051983,-2.42125505496877 50.5583536733143,-2.42119789845666 50.5582747646848,-2.42109941897851 50.5581564477969,-2.42078037053875 50.5578293623053,-2.42034478808165 50.5572769479812,-2.419929086524 50.5567208641006,-2.41974466191389 50.5562952945741,-2.41971597123528 50.5562494571037,-2.41963041765751 50.5561571644845,-2.41942422620142 50.5559798978097,-2.41936727437948 50.5559233736122,-2.41933735600023 50.5557391782273,-2.41910944255592 50.5553434326311,-2.41893089499895 50.5551066389723,-2.41892473762824 50.5550554158542,-2.41891308146356 50.5550141019675,-2.41889154769798 50.554974531806,-2.41886014592003 50.5549377841781,-2.41882038835942 50.5549037637301,-2.41877345482021 50.5548742642885,-2.41869691168547 50.5548394771094,-2.41851248501143 50.5547268613765,-2.41832326653801 50.5545593312245,-2.41828345698385 50.5545325030993,-2.41819699821516 50.5544950541055,-2.41811500495043 50.5544755698075,-2.41806270065823 50.5544703634547,-2.41796115285116 50.5544770214488,-2.41789190922462 50.5544646835285,-2.41784201648144 50.5544163144935,-2.41776667181535 50.5543589564928,-2.41769533225187 50.5542675104492,-2.41761411114368 50.5541904844596,-2.41760483343467 50.554088926214,-2.41751243218534 50.553866205856,-2.41750502809421 50.5538185832869,-2.41749208812601 50.5537898604187,-2.41744928710125 50.5537404768281,-2.4173470259323 50.5536662232305,-2.41732420155293 50.5536384348269,-2.41730974877606 50.5536097173622,-2.41728333713474 50.5534920377908,-2.4172440275686 50.5533635260637,-2.41711993519173 50.5532156292245,-2.41682539016309 50.5529414882475,-2.41673918131773 50.5529319075202,-2.41669410497407 50.5529410593173,-2.41666323753301 50.5529645448746,-2.41662731501695 50.5530482842183,-2.41656405648556 50.5530808760971,-2.4165086595548 50.5530415165856,-2.4165162200069 50.5529354027752,-2.41654247226655 50.5528768712027,-2.41664189001873 50.5527874204524,-2.41668655387507 50.5527315200549,-2.41664604648118 50.5526120927078,-2.41653530979851 50.5523813458,-2.41625424760281 50.5518796978644,-2.41619271342668 50.5517908230168,-2.41612842680907 50.5517065430832,-2.41589621074901 50.5514645422903,-2.41585143217383 50.5513487260692,-2.41577762433698 50.5512932492537,-2.41562388112293 50.5511471648783,-2.41559571703608 50.5510016208812,-2.41553406440264 50.5508857748803,-2.41549483374815 50.550765443501,-2.41548802223574 50.5506261165222,-2.41547185006587 50.5505604543849,-2.41541927151154 50.5505102957936,-2.41539783838746 50.5504816029939,-2.41536457949413 50.5503918176312,-2.41532161860836 50.5503236438563,-2.41531659062254 50.5502282735827,-2.41530931004799 50.5502076216274,-2.41529786373154 50.5501896816586,-2.41521993426211 50.5501548971248,-2.41522658482893 50.5501171136882,-2.41528602716373 50.5499684699764,-2.41530656696889 50.5498955743841,-2.41532254801639 50.5497939257514,-2.41532645548655 50.5495897396484,-2.41533890297 50.5495627240039,-2.41538510408656 50.5495230013212,-2.41550044371499 50.5494713442782,-2.4154604424195 50.5494220398355,-2.41538556786016 50.5494169128509,-2.41533460052291 50.5493910225646,-2.41534139315346 50.549369421344,-2.41539028916778 50.5493053250338,-2.41538840265001 50.5492495912353,-2.41535705484028 50.5492182366865,-2.41539884491835 50.5491533565941,-2.41540424893617 50.5491326593661,-2.41539101908864 50.5490706727669,-2.41541556290661 50.5489635093948,-2.41551652997846 50.5488921247299,-2.41557213942627 50.5487975268815,-2.41564781629641 50.5487352228113,-2.41575616510725 50.5486960871411,-2.41612837837077 50.5486489057936,-2.41641520012233 50.5485256103332,-2.41652634940249 50.5484874528689,-2.41683649003383 50.5482902616387,-2.41694751678279 50.5482251329777,-2.41699931681668 50.5481871876659,-2.41704412670731 50.5481483683383,-2.41711108792925 50.5480482449094,-2.41710494936785 50.547998819651,-2.41706047271931 50.5479171663053,-2.41708751136366 50.5477767290934,-2.41708847129405 50.5477272783923,-2.41708663046466 50.5476769386869,-2.41705130739808 50.5475116417029,-2.41705591617884 50.5474009532214,-2.41707634899725 50.5473163701285,-2.41710252605852 50.5472497472677,-2.41712904163976 50.5472082963403,-2.41720179332777 50.5471315271587,-2.41732517000643 50.5470420797357,-2.41736136472124 50.5469898055506,-2.41733487734355 50.5468631357202,-2.41733513744592 50.546734481983,-2.41735568065528 50.5466624850125,-2.41745271054343 50.5464624599399,-2.4174774902352 50.5463958419962,-2.41750697081152 50.5462159279727,-2.41750806548172 50.5458525315186,-2.41756766121135 50.5454197888679,-2.41759063866967 50.5453073262375,-2.41761512792481 50.5451947682711,-2.41777430920365 50.544680754327,-2.41782340392921 50.5444952856023,-2.41794116750621 50.5442457383096,-2.41781377456079 50.5441958493991,-2.41776983282198 50.5441744301459,-2.41784718626718 50.5439870618665,-2.4178645533411 50.5438719221708,-2.41792067315792 50.543678336778,-2.41782124953595 50.5436067704281,-2.4177860700945 50.5434576557885,-2.41777987581666 50.543401937434,-2.4177828370162 50.543249898834,-2.41784440640771 50.543041010182,-2.41793446224309 50.5428428975998,-2.41796782080678 50.5427861381596,-2.4181497376309 50.5426073844678,-2.4182140700566 50.542553210786,-2.41837681843121 50.5424438417473,-2.41855384011948 50.5423433216607,-2.41862944216317 50.5422873091303,-2.41904051846048 50.5418524015379,-2.41925229699453 50.5416960146116,-2.41955832963653 50.5415142042572,-2.41997475373214 50.541211433214,-2.42008256231279 50.5411138576507,-2.42020352513318 50.541069367885,-2.42031014538582 50.5409952614005,-2.42034523184971 50.5409762547895,-2.42082916661963 50.5408080931295,-2.42173486777379 50.5404558961982,-2.42225011316081 50.5401599511174,-2.42312703576972 50.5397539051576,-2.42329980568785 50.5396615745318,-2.4234655010905 50.5395718766133,-2.42374337651152 50.5394063403787,-2.42439230936234 50.5390613505843,-2.42469933699552 50.5388389761417,-2.42487163985461 50.5386953994337,-2.42510320898551 50.5385569103427,-2.42532814976681 50.5384706793942,-2.42624847443558 50.5381876199725,-2.42645413048116 50.5381437124831,-2.42651626628203 50.5381443838156,-2.42657844265318 50.5381495501802,-2.42671131018186 50.5381751353171,-2.42679621702825 50.5382107856735,-2.42694037835418 50.5382372281726,-2.42713649406473 50.5382320133181,-2.42745766791537 50.5381607087277,-2.4275505154226 50.5381351944561,-2.42782468422559 50.5380254026893,-2.42809475214408 50.5379254249261,-2.42823231652148 50.5378529953773,-2.42836686238632 50.5377428169735,-2.42841278762301 50.537675129796,-2.42848911688566 50.5375345980842,-2.4285223123492 50.5374616533769,-2.4286071841047 50.5371726581287,-2.42866780950215 50.5370069210128,-2.42870648269137 50.5369222685088,-2.42889896068048 50.536670636375,-2.42914603271911 50.5363711533147,-2.42926595431627 50.5362142775201,-2.4293230726772 50.5361367491038,-2.42942736406547 50.5359627590712,-2.42952482028987 50.5358176534547,-2.42958917244799 50.535755292033,-2.4297808405773 50.5355819680388,-2.43051866385253 50.53494163932,-2.43073829911809 50.5347357547838,-2.43091056052466 50.5345912701095,-2.4312210112898 50.534291547814,-2.43128768514918 50.5341653447393,-2.43142525832802 50.5340956084508,-2.43139799286001 50.5340399688279,-2.43152830646847 50.5339396918456,-2.43167377087127 50.5338042059116,-2.43193365621458 50.5336755774136,-2.4321749615208 50.5335253503815,-2.43288278040308 50.5330074776578,-2.43297798605668 50.5329360091131,-2.43309279656962 50.532833090902,-2.43342002486652 50.5325135212181,-2.43394823826755 50.5321014988213,-2.43442733284721 50.5317382057382,-2.4347668706062 50.5315192791664,-2.43485794961675 50.5314551067331,-2.43506800126223 50.531286110483,-2.43527892960475 50.5312124991448,-2.43573374823895 50.5309562776592,-2.4365845522562 50.5304989816452,-2.43685138472822 50.5303702260926,-2.43698460140821 50.5302717301052,-2.43711313955279 50.5301453811642,-2.43719353455778 50.5299831612798,-2.4372760888636 50.5297526058513,-2.43734839829666 50.5294961064746,-2.43739579693496 50.5292755725468,-2.4373970325983 50.5291073566892,-2.4374209934229 50.5289562271573,-2.43742098510578 50.5289553281441,-2.43741643159218 50.5289157873034,-2.43748942274073 50.5282680210508,-2.43751214821166 50.5278200315871,-2.43749083277923 50.5275026590515,-2.43751770624474 50.527201288132,-2.43757369939578 50.5268539564126,-2.43765277260304 50.526549691997,-2.43784031633758 50.5262396251664,-2.43815488522126 50.5257798383372,-2.43834411437087 50.5256522704383,-2.43854093865674 50.5255787062109,-2.43866775218945 50.5255566511542,-2.43876106376575 50.5254340292383,-2.43885006948757 50.5252861603165,-2.43894775870601 50.5251716131406,-2.43904277253778 50.5250821593324,-2.43925421041282 50.5249042495163,-2.43948651430509 50.5247063916073,-2.4394656720755 50.5245913925377,-2.43960466728022 50.524516246781,-2.43969439743529 50.5244592679205,-2.4403070421763 50.5241988355289,-2.4405094468093 50.5241134693363,-2.44062766439631 50.5240806561299,-2.44074440331565 50.5240514445849,-2.44112306736398 50.5238089757087,-2.44137774006927 50.5234420086403,-2.44144596123547 50.523336561543,-2.44150313218002 50.522969444194,-2.44158867143914 50.5227631482936,-2.44215740211216 50.5223374483011,-2.44230341285231 50.5221057487793,-2.4423005206553 50.5220949712248,-2.4423364670087 50.5220211128454,-2.44233783743243 50.5220184104991,-2.4424326352588 50.5218947909462,-2.44253411721675 50.5217397691987,-2.4425065683314 50.5216544646211,-2.44250203649379 50.5214808761245,-2.44247155160268 50.5210817258189,-2.44233491425674 50.5209472985206,-2.4423864623111 50.5208877655358,-2.44242262484317 50.5208246948415,-2.44250195436003 50.5207138105605,-2.44263894795519 50.5205756456073,-2.44277193305531 50.5204690522525,-2.4429071382005 50.520450556793,-2.44322841645416 50.5202568477614,-2.44330865842706 50.5200947138207,-2.44342078524556 50.520021373971,-2.44346966448162 50.5199627497101,-2.443600546231 50.5199298851822,-2.44374145658744 50.5199122660463,-2.44380887259816 50.5198832394704,-2.44387344673399 50.5198488294195,-2.44408468378828 50.5196663262521,-2.44416116309142 50.5196984000133,-2.44427709107651 50.5197204336091,-2.4443683372473 50.5196778300305,-2.44440994337724 50.5196003531762,-2.44448734524925 50.5195820766199,-2.44449863461099 50.5195829325422,-2.44458410239878 50.5196680154089,-2.44470533388249 50.5196603597954,-2.44483006755993 50.5197283004422,-2.44489103748303 50.5197559377814,-2.44512228749313 50.5197478610511,-2.44529799417593 50.5196832666186,-2.44534562973595 50.5196534157977,-2.44538905310496 50.5196208839412,-2.44555225938499 50.5194269642314,-2.44567545021682 50.5193311036779,-2.44573242593006 50.5192310913225,-2.44577223797016 50.5191239523206,-2.44579195424201 50.5189700499851,-2.44592692269679 50.5189146910194,-2.44603775297133 50.51900057468,-2.44612927599112 50.5189876371763,-2.44622433860715 50.5188937718673,-2.44631149655755 50.5188619709878,-2.44643914342236 50.5187949519067,-2.44660338321706 50.5188590529989,-2.44673417178779 50.5189646384141,-2.44678578312858 50.5190480515589,-2.4468155772758 50.5190749085449,-2.44708498594022 50.5190684794747,-2.44723183252602 50.5190886831453,-2.447319900236 50.5190055424752,-2.44739218643363 50.5188892876078,-2.4474054249158 50.5188011301743,-2.44739313142138 50.5186941010294,-2.44744893108042 50.5186300541913,-2.44744546812937 50.5185590428494,-2.44744507689001 50.5183701547217,-2.44745350689646 50.5183638289816,-2.44752237349763 50.5183410879886,-2.44759362810989 50.5184109395422,-2.44767985669373 50.5184285887569,-2.44775056972861 50.5183060463811,-2.44783094364733 50.5182949485285,-2.44802093513306 50.5182537600928,-2.44803737209103 50.5182 87444876,-2.44806819936913 50.5180377170696,-2.44806201260905 50.5179739085973,-2.44803018719295 50.5178922179146,-2.44802804998124 50.5178139191994,-2.4481746537073 50.5178088594111,-2.44831536003775 50.5177705574409,-2.44842199769293 50.5178556458621,-2.44857138402731 50.5178496758047,-2.44869468945997 50.5177547106228,-2.4487374776573 50.5176556505122,-2.44868802354235 50.5175056105469,-2.44876744060256 50.5173938225249,-2.44890495635338 50.5173258636067,-2.44893145302118 50.5172871023834,-2.44895070539457 50.5172447729179,-2.44892967745635 50.5171000176461,-2.44913699587924 50.5169490768409,-2.44928383588879 50.5169691880445,-2.44948070099427 50.5169054945042,-2.44973196219666 50.5169243026943,-2.44990577687409 50.5169559964615,-2.44994511418895 50.5169468538941,-2.45002092590546 50.5169088007659,-2.45009670242725 50.5168670616328,-2.45017313081493 50.5167471927747,-2.45028363903484 50.5166523652973,-2.45046498344888 50.5165833358649,-2.4504864470824 50.5164680848909,-2.45048532551662 50.516350314114,-2.4505433603321 50.5162286282095,-2.45063643133008 50.5162201763885,-2.45076496937459 50.5162358613677,-2.45076941366943 50.5162629054582,-2.45075792028416 50.51638701843,-2.45080634587317 50.5164407736341,-2.45092197754439 50.5164322341796,-2.45096856220208 50.5164392460209,-2.45100820374368 50.5164498809415,-2.45110874976405 50.5164935444806,-2.45115261213397 50.5165077591756,-2.4512034262312 50.5165192497583,-2.45137575911911 50.5165419566112,-2.45164345206457 50.5165157445992,-2.45177434431996 50.5164855679441,-2.45189962012085 50.5164518167665,-2.4519994110128 50.516416366357,-2.45209498953545 50.5163782350874,-2.45219040864418 50.5163356091247,-2.45214260284471 50.5162008479707,-2.45215070529791 50.5161603593818,-2.45217582439108 50.5161359875099,-2.45220533210842 50.5161205890455,-2.45224898817926 50.516113227007,-2.45231849391166 50.5161579091872,-2.45245300364041 50.5160683806146,-2.45245960714816 50.5160171092695,-2.45241704573501 50.5159930004926,-2.45228250475615 50.5159332873752,-2.45234778279225 50.5158277552458,-2.45248529333648 50.5157481044796,-2.45253534286776 50.5155338467844,-2.45260369127614 50.515445474358,-2.45254958378259 50.5153935400829,-2.45246376308774 50.5154181480891,-2.45247750713551 50.5153839308628,-2.45259780511443 50.5152799827146,-2.45273672630463 50.5152021242485,-2.45282139197547 50.5152026938489,-2.45301430391691 50.5151767696556,-2.45306345902457 50.5151487078203,-2.45310712267542 50.515142244475,-2.45315088104404 50.515145670261,-2.45318624520212 50.5151590182401,-2.45322172135113 50.5151840533827,-2.45356625636107 50.5153742978333,-2.45356528146887 50.5152726194233,-2.45353259158693 50.5152349868682,-2.45350280044275 50.5152207182274,-2.45348708006495 50.5152063947429,-2.45348134315472 50.5151902342554,-2.45349795485584 50.5151640971533,-2.45352465341042 50.5151469112048,-2.45350880377176 50.5151191025222,-2.45351814518129 50.5150624261544,-2.4535601201832 50.5150254016226,-2.45361058404422 50.5149883439836,-2.45385056278561 50.5148623507882,-2.45390442093643 50.5148882130735,-2.45401466081832 50.514912057265,-2.45432920831214 50.5147768715398,-2.45454973130604 50.5146717208453,-2.45464229255935 50.514622720783,-2.45472506921133 50.5145720506945,-2.45479933091777 50.5145187166862,-2.45488419395588 50.5144069031245,-2.45500780719937 50.5143461836661,-2.45526250943929 50.5141437109542,-2.45536443475177 50.5140408207473,-2.45553608614547 50.5138485619224,-2.45570208526988 50.5136491325945,-2.45577462488118 50.5135742275622,-2.45603325818345 50.513333977743,-2.45611561505376 50.5132401540233,-2.45628100056135 50.5131343170788,-2.45650934514197 50.5129733011148,-2.45673969196007 50.5128753000607,-2.45689190772104 50.5128630148633,-2.45703901619263 50.5129118847511,-2.45742029496651 50.5131019735417,-2.45755602972009 50.513140997965,-2.45771271929642 50.5131583626673,-2.45781456414019 50.5131921258087,-2.45795371997462 50.5132841801034,-2.45805214594301 50.5133971625647,-2.45835590276255 50.5136027473232,-2.4584995790227 50.5137290368582,-2.45864843885094 50.5138021720871,-2.45876164372791 50.5138439810473,-2.45891752496154 50.5139215834856,-2.45908949565631 50.5140513568839,-2.45923205730944 50.5140624819514,-2.45930988950123 50.5140900452183,-2.45931691893316 50.5140954117547,-2.4592902880792 50.5142510520492,-2.45936371612428 50.5142561564818,-2.45936933271068 50.5142597304979,-2.45944174952475 50.5143043969525,-2.45944634857668 50.5144905714756,-2.45943511495857 50.5146390485241,-2.45944797345458 50.5146578777449,-2.45949345033552 50.514694559108,-2.45951604649553 50.5148419136146,-2.45945233287166 50.5152504225069,-2.45934504093614 50.5155305396415,-2.45928224689702 50.5156028011748,-2.45928630344005 50.5157331469834,-2.4593813784394 50.5157876135496,-2.45943328602578 50.5159115670072,-2.45944330313209 50.5160688606792,-2.45947275153398 50.5163349522059,-2.45950686955044 50.5162197394733,-2.45953862352412 50.5161484994611,-2.45955257226895 50.5161358577166,-2.45958346431154 50.5161195528651,-2.45961863009634 50.5161122215945,-2.45965527869796 50.5161138749255,-2.45969352642677 50.5161245123974,-2.45972334620815 50.5161414764827,-2.45974329618111 50.5161719652602,-2.45974359325053 50.5162025316833,-2.45977575314798 50.5163166734849,-2.4598083815137 50.5163354245445,-2.46005338057226 50.5164396446671,-2.46010336349696 50.5164969860477,-2.46013103807548 50.5165922654966,-2.46012715768472 50.5166237474823,-2.46010233974618 50.5166786874763,-2.46007852988954 50.516705753025,-2.46003368885317 50.5167346998094,-2.46006648373919 50.5167705320283,-2.4601097938878 50.5168711439398,-2.46011863292952 50.5169070708639,-2.46011972601869 50.5170194473983,-2.46013749777844 50.5171128779959,-2.46015488828464 50.517155154333,-2.46019940118974 50.5172358925144,-2.46021530536429 50.5172807819556,-2.46023042892996 50.517376920149,-2.46022421065246 50.5174669393258,-2.46020393753678 50.5175587222755,-2.46017656431499 50.517637946644,-2.46010441640018 50.5177649975293,-2.46010073016392 50.5179718827532,-2.46001494797534 50.5181440297217,-2.4599847917798 50.5182241640846,-2.45998592108815 50.5184957616087,-2.46002359609118 50.5188777973781,-2.46001571741344 50.5192276475284,-2.45999590742051 50.51936716795,-2.4599689673127 50.5195030304584,-2.45988266917701 50.5197659830079,-2.45982289665218 50.5198624171812,-2.45978728511991 50.519967746323,-2.45952840380078 50.520471515641,-2.45921558114425 50.521229927285,-2.45919522776199 50.5214575561848,-2.45916271999927 50.5215953284204,-2.45910711602642 50.5216782600513,-2.4590433620313 50.5217962866017,-2.45883991042783 50.5220570032088,-2.45871193850989 50.5222454982563,-2.45838513505034 50.5225840181716,-2.45832095114229 50.5226579927473,-2.45813991590772 50.5229042350589,-2.45803332662686 50.5231033437875,-2.45793120266597 50.523199134473,-2.45785415698699 50.5232542794319,-2.45779142794677 50.5233345413015,-2.4577409268956 50.52335631706,-2.45755243774186 50.5234217896351,-2.45721007574171 50.5236084286059,-2.45707685382698 50.5236880679812,-2.45682510809907 50.5239121097662,-2.45664520427195 50.5241322729192,-2.45649787327499 50.5243531171515,-2.45632440187971 50.5245049270896,-2.45605064395005 50.5247991790269,-2.45593920073166 50.5249425639576,-2.45588921712158 50.525018279607,-2.45579247135611 50.5252264279901,-2.45566642028692 50.5254715519006,-2.45564300541711 50.525673119661,-2.45564172611882 50.5258421452029,-2.4556898452953 50.5262970535365,-2.45570006990136 50.5263320762649,-2.45574612702613 50.5264280937456,-2.4557788301227 50.5264540379783,-2.45584678531938 50.5264807431632,-2.45590373904529 50.5265245732694,-2.45582992867649 50.5266265444308,-2.45585562295174 50.5268062528314,-2.45588339049034 50.5269114222512,-2.45600109280535 50.5271150443548,-2.45607113097877 50.5273576019896,-2.45611116560108 50.5275526277826,-2.45611234497615 50.5276748932954,-2.45607197341383 50.5277343884986,-2.4560130240839 50.5277732784502,-2.45598516121704 50.5278030561175,-2.4559586211602 50.5278373238204,-2.45594637678581 50.5278824139526,-2.45593441758543 50.5279570815483,-2.45593629018287 50.5280065216895,-2.45594936767975 50.5280478265242,-2.45600096190181 50.5281267403284,-2.45601423977051 50.52818881231,-2.45599092827984 50.5282563320318,-2.45595616036114 50.5283059157358,-2.45595230733711 50.5283526811721,-2.45599665034296 50.5284154405751,-2.45609217293676 50.5285140510903,-2.45613672442399 50.5285983867006,-2.4561770885418 50.5286827387073,-2.45621100868282 50.5288346342356,-2.45620856906823 50.5288831922253,-2.45620857774234 50.5288840912362,-2.45624871749561 50.5290898151551,-2.45627753701884 50.5293037647465,-2.45620727310566 50.5294722515066,-2.45620120100198 50.529578362599,-2.45622702067731 50.5297707468701,-2.45618375164735 50.5298194649105,-2.45616728379146 50.5298608855226,-2.45619375252722 50.5299758594952,-2.4561962862685 50.5302384605281,-2.45628431904787 50.5304404903594,-2.45628473549758 50.5304836428711,-2.45626344383017 50.5306158859158,-2.45622027036167 50.5306745829825,-2.45626319398812 50.5307346506926,-2.45636481539286 50.5307414445834,-2.45636652369317 50.530773803491,-2.45636117085257 50.5308097862674,-2.45626528484812 50.5309513122478,-2.45629289961538 50.5310402992957,-2.45626937024575 50.5310853437787,-2.45624130252323 50.5311061318456,-2.45622880514488 50.5311250607763,-2.45622345571168 50.5311493559512,-2.45625977838309 50.5312606950755,-2.4562608290271 50.5313695652506,-2.45619901409834 50.5314012741452,-2.45614691340866 50.5314149640404,-2.45611890105222 50.5314294585475,-2.45609653308609 50.5314502242382,-2.45608685342804 50.5314718392427,-2.45609283607397 50.5315131718435,-2.45613863379642 50.5315696321495,-2.45614440833109 50.5315893884947,-2.45614322924476 50.5316118692287,-2.45607626502408 50.5318333865279,-2.45600324456561 50.5320180666887,-2.45578228862829 50.5323759427988,-2.45575333896641 50.5324380902369,-2.45572337957168 50.5325523861931,-2.45570316085182 50.5327961962826,-2.45565772133876 50.5329097436903,-2.45558667431442 50.5330098157599,-2.45557841607036 50.533034122284,-2.45557347326973 50.5331006709085,-2.45562062071779 50.5333091545,-2.45559972560429 50.5333380057188,-2.45550600547408 50.5334273779607,-2.45539983777854 50.5336859090439,-2.45533341461513 50.533819317387,-2.45533533881098 50.5338741515504,-2.45528149825168 50.534142367242,-2.45521315558157 50.5343664965594,-2.45515813416593 50.5346571928887,-2.45515805956109 50.5348065243872,-2.45514585507571 50.5348560195375,-2.45513080657851 50.5349001315447,-2.45506637597412 50.5349507299645,-2.4549561325104 50.5353666091877,-2.45493869524058 50.5354647630412,-2.45489710124558 50.535543142447,-2.45488754997929 50.5355782424908,-2.4548844605171 50.5356924331348,-2.45481981841479 50.5358662911435,-2.45480175960835 50.5361901073837,-2.45476405616975 50.5363827399856,-2.45475902541515 50.536440298442,-2.45478668300545 50.5365336909104,-2.45476515694648 50.5367873952511,-2.45476774661339 50.5369114531559,-2.4547959243531 50.5370588761043,-2.45485949509522 50.5372087679435,-2.45474037477894 50.537440377559,-2.45455491220626 50.5376695490493,-2.45414444130157 50.5381297536168,-2.4540929285477 50.5382054742696,-2.45405833361253 50.5382740264518,-2.45402120452033 50.5383694699066,-2.45398012456138 50.5385017895384,-2.45394276135555 50.5387303821981,-2.45397072501111 50.5388435525826,-2.45398361474705 50.5388651692465,-2.4540392419687 50.5389269862288,-2.45416423779255 50.5390155037998,-2.45421123395239 50.5390629696876,-2.45424709555737 50.5391140751892,-2.45426582844765 50.5391625504088,-2.45427488420767 50.5392210427789,-2.4542685082647 50.5392840006952,-2.4542006903637 50.5394308094384,-2.4541885968846 50.5394920814794,-2.45418770178199 50.5395442294798,-2.45419517043102 50.5395828591911,-2.45426642431119 50.5398056337089,-2.45433970122276 50.5399482955323,-2.45461853153536 50.5403284908748,-2.45484235731082 50.5405542651027,-2.45497732656567 50.5406508341927,-2.45504262189165 50.540689237765,-2.45509651019125 50.5407150993037,-2.45535697107649 50.5408058728136,-2.45615669720786 50.5411939146935,-2.45619777939288 50.5412189268711,-2.45634862216743 50.5413442015204,-2.45640419550684 50.5413998141688,-2.45654273048406 50.5415637956771,-2.45658868275987 50.541647226404,-2.45660754153594 50.5417083772418,-2.45663984973128 50.5418368136224,-2.45665201327317 50.5419275692322,-2.45663920365301 50.5420589696607,-2.4565548334719 50.5423830459988,-2.45654003579384 50.5424532293879,-2.45653500314837 50.542522475427,-2.45650338264211 50.5426098066121,-2.45627625833151 50.542911966495,-2.45599720910907 50.5432476838544,-2.4558618312435 50.5433992533598,-2.45581649394829 50.5435243978602,-2.45580992598628 50.5435793550887,-2.45581289174207 50.543742070189,-2.4558071242524 50.5438679587414,-2.45578402754911 50.5439706299535,-2.45572993527254 50.5440688374158,-2.45565603951861 50.544152737704,-2.45562679373527 50.5441969951885,-2.45557960439363 50.5442870841698,-2.45553335450656 50.544462578491,-2.45550001480764 50.5445167414319,-2.45496678308692 50.5451275687584,-2.45486900617399 50.545233228801,-2.45476842663817 50.5453379107635,-2.45443813827438 50.5456359747363,-2.45429937683291 50.5457273197277,-2.45416447239328 50.5457962633487,-2.45366344643353 50.546092294094,-2.45341414633738 50.5462820644333,-2.45328682015266 50.5464013238644,-2.45327157659478 50.5464256573697,-2.45326336660272 50.546455357734,-2.45324890347037 50.5465731885776,-2.45322257081849 50.5466182432283,-2.4530684362652 50.546733111593,-2.45304607699923 50.5467556746827,-2.45300709043612 50.5468160622539,-2.45297911972874 50.5468359500451,-2.4529130027814 50.5468703709526,-2.45286132788906 50.54691822126,-2.45287882983173 50.5469837832282,-2.45284968745996 50.5470271405439,-2.45271393119995 50.5471535345611,-2.4526168603047 50.547188075696,-2.4526001336483 50.547203424457,-2.45258903559931 50.5472232465379,-2.45258256586773 50.5472889017619,-2.45255207387214 50.547349346046,-2.45241811271591 50.5475054011137,-2.45234853677309 50.5476162537056,-2.45234257977886 50.547723352751,-2.45236320566123 50.5478113786935,-2.45236053746655 50.5478365622371,-2.45229720593779 50.5480041200635,-2.45227037871295 50.5481435758027,-2.45229599510037 50.5483152831526,-2.4522998980923 50.5484312443793,-2.4522948029108 50.5484825095625,-2.45227024746305 50.5485797014979,-2.45224974646992 50.54879654013,-2.45220253345929 50.5488731421237,-2.45214807632364 50.5489345784343,-2.45212999954004 50.5489670141599,-2.45211384846295 50.5490425964042,-2.45211288214003 50.5490875522431,-2.45217154242355 50.5493193670204,-2.45216243379688 50.5494012151982,-2.45211998580159 50.5495380344274,-2.45213620394895 50.5496153789098,-2.45210279567923 50.5496631578916,-2.45202104329692 50.5498154134525,-2.45201009921177 50.5498514176189,-2.4520075175878 50.549885681129,-2.45203664762447 50.5499745731117,-2.45207120883662 50.5500472612427,-2.45217436052867 50.5502096769659,-2.45231916282214 50.5505894987776,-2.45234257432503 50.5506766148149,-2.45239266295743 50.5510460160708,-2.4523921195423 50.5511351131855,-2.45235645649305 50.5515309198993,-2.45223068595444 50.5519603412438,-2.45220299134416 50.5520215836517,-2.45189040237046 50.5523879882453,-2.4517908233496 50.5524656923605,-2.45169421828315 50.5525379906009,-2.45163511422271 50.5525642921517,-2.45157610069563 50.5525878961977,-2.4513605046981 50.5526309874023,-2.45128477438008 50.5526834254419,-2.45122343027807 50.5529139077026,-2.4512060267088 50.5530048682242,-2.45120208985446 50.5530435422519,-2.45122603292785 50.5531863969602,-2.45109163892004 50.5532992980285,-2.45105507677526 50.5534559627644,-2.45099439677917 50.5536099339111,-2.45095599500037 50.5537324421787,-2.45091022308375 50.553814432237,-2.45080988343575 50.5539470698358,-2.45073612170761 50.5540597356192,-2.45068200752025 50.5541579406239,-2.45065595125782 50.5542326619059,-2.4506292060671 50.5543937836741,-2.45061554385539 50.5544378895696,-2.45059189466688 50.5544721446769,-2.45032244914161 50.5547888406963,-2.45017939886272 50.5550322249754,-2.4501434349925 50.5551177729382,-2.45015251368286 50.5551788725955,-2.45004926795095 50.5553124197815,-2.45002459813075 50.5553862365039,-2.45001145750327 50.5554851817839,-2.44997529337273 50.5555375558616,-2.44996817590899 50.5556823289207))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "57": {
    "Question": "Where is the location of the County Cork?",
    "Query": "select ?geoWKT{     yago:County_Cork geo:hasGeometry ?geom .     ?geom geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  }",
    "Answer": "POLYGON ((-8.47753214463483 51.9292988272052, -8.48927093203553 51.9264452028952, -8.4908413926632..."
  },
  "58": {
    "Question": "What is the area of Londonderry?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?area WHERE {         <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_Londonderry_1414> y2geoo:hasOSNI_Area ?area }",
    "Answer": "945788.486^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "59": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Syros?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?pop WHERE {   yago:Syros y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?pop }",
    "Answer": "19782^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "60": {
    "Question": "Where is Kastanas beach located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?wkt WHERE{ yago:geoentity_Paralía_Kastanás_10277719 geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?wkt }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((24.538693300000002 36.735299600000005 5, 24.5385996 36.735318400000004, 24.5384394 36.7352592, 24.5382484 36.7351085, 24.538103600000003 36.734995000000005, 24.537989600000003 36.7348542, 24.537900200000003 36.7346888, 24.537875600000003 36.7346122, 24.537891000000002 36.7345332, 24.5378694 36.7344814, 24.537780100000003 36.7344542, 24.5376876 36.734394900000005, 24.537709200000002 36.7343184, 24.5376784 36.7342394, 24.537666100000003 36.7341406, 24.5376815 36.734056700000004, 24.537736900000002 36.733987500000005, 24.5378425 36.7339306, 24.537802600000003 36.734075100000005, 24.5378371 36.734343800000005, 24.538003200000002 36.7346653, 24.5382888 36.73499, 24.5384953 36.735191400000005, 24.538693300000002 36.735299600000005))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "61": {
    "Question": "Where is the Loch Leven National Nature Reserve located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?wkt WHERE{ yago:geoentity_Loch_Leven_2643816 geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?wkt }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-3.3463423000000003 56.1984664, -3.34 450219000000003 56.195536700000005, -3.3440611000000002 56.195534900000006, -3.3444378 56.193895100000006, -3.3420155 56.19063980000001, -3.3417006000000002 56.1906022, -3.3388635000000004 56.1909402, -3.3310959 56.190295400000004, -3.3246800000000003 56.18184110000001, -3.3363744000000004 56.179309200000006, -3.3400866000000002 56.178927, -3.3484551000000002 56.1790345, -3.3519742000000003 56.178509000000005, -3.3547174 56.177266900000006, -3.358613 56.175051200000006, -3.3594216 56.174618200000005, -3.3613648 56.1738396, -3.3640049000000003 56.173113900000004, -3.3647651 56.17302050000001, -3.3657721 56.172902300000004, -3.36864 56.1726742, -3.3705257000000004 56.1724654, -3.3706457000000003 56.172776600000006, -3.3714611000000003 56.1726541, -3.3713538 56.172337600000006, -3.3803880000000004 56.171303800000004, -3.3846217000000003 56.177679000000005, -3.38754 56.1770221, -3.3888319 56.1775376, -3.3847555000000003 56.1819202, -3.3908280000000004 56.18531170000001, -3.3990249 56.18910880000001, -3.4075007000000004 56.190768500000004, -3.4152898 56.193120500000006, -3.4196886 56.195317200000005, -3.4199676 56.196594600000005, -3.4193453000000003 56.197119900000004, -3.417221 56.1979674, -3.4155902 56.19827780000001, -3.4147963000000003 56.198385300000005, -3.4155902 56.1992686, -3.416942 56.199567, -3.4163412 56.2006771, -3.4170708000000003 56.200820400000005, -3.4167489000000004 56.2023482, -3.4138521 56.202407900000004, -3.4106120000000004 56.201858900000005, -3.4069428000000004 56.200701, -3.4041103 56.200498100000004, -3.4028658000000003 56.201214300000004, -3.4046897 56.203088300000005, -3.4062132000000003 56.206645, -3.4058484 56.2091751, -3.4031447000000004 56.21353070000001, -3.4025225000000003 56.21563080000001, -3.4037101 56.217407800000004, -3.3991865000000003 56.2197181, -3.3983043000000004 56.2202514, -3.3987456000000003 56.2210467, -3.3991808000000003 56.221223800000004, -3.3977570000000004 56.2214134, -3.3975146 56.2204732, -3.3941815 56.2205743, -3.3914932 56.2201766, -3.3853778 56.219818700000005, -3.3821162 56.219854500000004, -3.3766445000000003 56.2188165, -3.3703789000000004 56.2181603, -3.3652934 56.215929100000004, -3.3591136 56.213697800000006, -3.3536721000000003 56.212127200000005, -3.3500799000000003 56.209915, -3.3519695 56.209251800000004, -3.3540651 56.2088545, -3.3522069 56.206763300000006, -3.3497927 56.2051232, -3.3493324 56.2046086, -3.3470807000000002 56.202338600000004, -3.3463423000000003 56.1984664))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "62": {
    "Question": "What's the location of Killarney Beach?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?wkt WHERE{ yago:geoentity_Killarney_Beach_8215737 geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?wkt }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((142.3044213 -38.358556500000006, 142. .3046844 -38.3583927, 142.30487910000002 -38.3582215, 142.30499210000002 -38.358075, 142.305138 -38.3579461, 142.30533450000001 -38.3578508, 142.30556 -38.357730000000004, 142.3058364 -38.3575626, 142.30656960000002 -38.3574302, 142.30697550000002 -38.357361100000006, 142.30746670000002 -38.3570501, 142.30818190000002 -38.3566634, 142.30862000000002 -38.35654, 142.30902210000002 -38.3563976, 142.30937 -38.356320000000004, 142.3097654 -38.3563167, 142.31109 -38.35644, 142.3117363 -38.3565619, 142.31253890000002 -38.356794300000004, 142.3131932 -38.357049800000006, 142.3137132 -38.357323, 142.31392440000002 -38.3577047, 142.3134612 -38.3575194, 142.3127155 -38.3572292, 142.31217370000002 -38.357027300000006, 142.3117204 -38.3569011, 142.31110890000002 -38.356770700000006, 142.3107038 -38.3567181, 142.31032570000002 -38.3566865, 142.30997960000002 -38.3567181, 142.3093064 -38.356760200000004, 142.30871630000001 -38.356926300000005, 142.3081933 -38.357145100000004, 142.3080592 -38.3572628, 142.3080208 -38.357283, 142.3079623 -38.3572581, 142.30782580000002 -38.3572697, 142.3077336 -38.3573565, 142.3077373 -38.3574317, 142.3076005 -38.3577087, 142.30749590000002 -38.3578181, 142.30727330000002 -38.3579233, 142.3071188 -38.3579547, 142.30712110000002 -38.3578946, 142.30700670000002 -38.3578512, 142.3067337 -38.3578339, 142.3065223 -38.3578181, 142.3062031 -38.357816, 142.3059081 -38.357883300000005, 142.3056774 -38.357956900000005, 142.3054655 -38.3580242, 142.3053367 -38.3581231, 142.3052831 -38.358264000000005, 142.30530140000002 -38.3584466, 142.3051527 -38.3584643, 142.30501180000002 -38.3585993, 142.3047875 -38.3587057, 142.3046362 -38.3587384, 142.30459960000002 -38.3588121, 142.30452400000001 -38.3588277, 142.3043872 -38.3588992, 142.30428 -38.358977, 142.3040426 -38.3590588, 142.30411180000002 -38.3588408, 142.3044213 -38.358556500000006))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "63": {
    "Question": "Where is Selby District located?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?geoWKT where {     yago:Selby_District geo:hasGeometry ?o.     ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "175697^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer"
  },
  "64": {
    "Question": "What is the total area of town Ballinasloe?",
    "Query": "select distinct (strdf:area(?geoWKT) as ?totalArea) where {     yago:Ballinasloe geo:hasGeometry ?o.     ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "totalArea 0.06634563207626343^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double"
  },
  "65": {
    "Question": "Where is Drogheda city located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?geoWKT WHERE {  yago:Drogheda geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . }",
    "Answer": "geoWKT POLYGON ((-6.33000292218776 53.7178367086178, -6.33145519185506 53.7206899411865, -6.34056971695935 53.7234080746115, -6.34087802872861 53.7254989415462, -6.33419405095536 53.7266077821435, -6.33550956514316 53.7287781377437, -6.33060577570756 53.7308145723199, -6.33066990030869 53.7361017239558, -6.32622264487366 53.7371996684356, -6.32711160542369 53.7386023119439, -6.316385716357 53.7403186402093, -6.31484024775386 53.7458589774935, -6.32062651798935 53.7470614782845, -6.32152774186855 53.7528824216477, -6.33120479172244 53.7559757249214, -6.34152283519471 53.7560350857222, -6.344316254208 53.7581578777531, -6.34295217123734 53.7608233099474, -6.33611275461596 53.7634244790919, -6.33742854094065 53.7660623052745, -6.32999921916128 53.7673625175556, -6.33013176438591 53.768606068272, -6.34677991174374 53.7697950237259, -6.34645030631141 53.7684416822843, -6.34979070087336 53.7676741414607, -6.36586405992709 53.7670873882379, -6.36445749248606 53.7641972977685, -6.36118380306718 53.764592882146, -6.36138100622784 53.7594401976868, -6.37251409066575 53.7581896996052, -6.36748836203774 53.7538331515609, -6.35801035861156 53.7503208279393, -6.3488133669736 53.7511047791137, -6.34857831105715 53.7494754253239, -6.34980157009174 53.7458052248955, -6.35254699061182 53.7458014244208, -6.35343463050393 53.7433790086549, -6.35704458828668 53.7426131109608, -6.35739787991164 53.7458704434027, -6.36052785371095 53.7460670996756, -6.36061528036531 53.7426989000059, -6.36539874466479 53.7428551556618, -6.37062731899368 53.7401713445106, -6.36888155893939 53.7485325562414, -6.36329619872903 53.7494319142824, -6.36581893250347 53.7493351354196, -6.36334571179064 53.7504072671808, -6.36746194930691 53.7536680349049, -6.37910373201642 53.7484421056686, -6.38233797883655 53.7554903359858, -6.38981995562101 53.7574687079433, -6.40839742774751 53.7604371471307, -6.41242048239781 53.7555062960063, -6.41158808739536 53.7519792093775, -6.40919219694308 53.7497818459333, -6.40503615147149 53.7501446602074, -6.39830259429748 53.7421665256524, -6.38835540904327 53.7394203994983, -6.38667329791807 53.7375887250164, -6.37731767819281 53.7397471274789, -6.36962819866724 53.73716141008, -6.3764173500212 53.7344440211176, -6.37510149110591 53.7322222425353, -6.36439912836635 53.7247774401167, -6.36086236587192 53.7245586105695, -6.36113710646012 53.7196191415869, -6.37038563379987 53.7190410327759, -6.36886231288905 53.717360363322, -6.3634491084493 53.7163990219575, -6.35372289101576 53.711386880707, -6.35379612464402 53.706793556023, -6.3485102540749 53.707094168995, -6.34205223281294 53.7130955852588, -6.33258741106579 53.7151401313651, -6.33000292218776 53.7178367086178))^^http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral"
  },
  "66": {
    "Question": "Where is the Crewe city located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?geoWKT WHERE {  yago:Crewe geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . }",
    "Answer": "geoWKT <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>  POLYGON ((-2.45385221602687 53.1256662043664,-2.45330093222642 53.1256871772142,-2.45244616635631 53.1256841396065,-2.45100600368209 53.1257273496723,-2.44977057405031 53.1257661740952,-2.44868617739206 53.1258143913174,-2.44739521658738 53.1258336302012,-2.44667216204629 53.1258660017891,-2.44630457232869 53.1258619891002,-2.44603800456992 53.1258090696926,-2.44552751727785 53.1257246219769,-2.44338710754886 53.1253955335732,-2.44324454429468 53.1254787402573,-2.44276570711021 53.1254158202252,-2.4424435212657 53.1253334443346,-2.4419292945251 53.1253155848975,-2.44147767967863 53.1252876058468,-2.44115441816106 53.1252321898904,-2.4401684877597 53.12512521736,-2.4397192273116 53.1250379121949,-2.43885702709405 53.1248964128014,-2.43841232024234 53.124808097404,-2.43801573097833 53.1247502471238,-2.43735745265158 53.1246690941283,-2.43713449063477 53.124637562073,-2.43579905793467 53.1243988369343,-2.43543669568879 53.1243255757092,-2.43494595798739 53.1242652738802,-2.43429757066265 53.1241373381571,-2.43406584613693 53.124128298529,-2.43389747223825 53.1241702503789,-2.43380500327846 53.1241885604644,-2.43370499158534 53.1242042020266,-2.43348698564579 53.1242238679906,-2.43328259535655 53.1242497745115,-2.43296803866339 53.1240289535143,-2.43285079471951 53.1241075623828,-2.4326680027382 53.1242106729659,-2.43256376282678 53.124246997834,-2.43234132075368 53.1242666778248,-2.43218316849102 53.1242960989084,-2.43213095653765 53.1242989844686,-2.4320621539237 53.1242938424192,-2.43199623522392 53.1242814108162,-2.43191081200804 53.1242529641833,-2.43174160949743 53.1242248214875,-2.43158877255417 53.1241822408369,-2.43142407508558 53.1241486894661,-2.43127265417715 53.1240998127441,-2.43134471249934 53.1239872206318,-2.43128252497475 53.1238920995422,-2.43126569782097 53.1238481268025,-2.4312558489296 53.1237627909858,-2.43126441979061 53.1237205234912,-2.43131289021452 53.1236393796738,-2.43138097148944 53.1235726329686,-2.43140846192022 53.1234880604392,-2.4313727199502 53.1233515955871,-2.43123306518073 53.1231363364927,-2.43116878886012 53.1229801148653,-2.43115336861893 53.122928947825,-2.4311369767127 53.1227807303591,-2.43115669005653 53.1226700354075,-2.43118430356229 53.1225854624708,-2.43117789782787 53.122548641128,-2.43114729160583 53.1224696710314,-2.43098918604773 53.1222077487954,-2.43093666445791 53.1220317141957,-2.43085289048383 53.1218720582566,-2.43078186738676 53.121792335747,-2.43073964656487 53.1217591487565,-2.43069300955823 53.1217278648958,-2.43053416121015 53.1216745208739,-2.43032155924626 53.1216420399448,-2.43013349275187 53.1216606928712,-2.42997549773873 53.1216927165581,-2.42976188407305 53.1217069679692,-2.42965282708165 53.1217046658544,-2.42935669978743 53.1216850658323,-2.42896515717215 53.1216720996173,-2.42889608166851 53.1216390986473,-2.42878790375678 53.1215765831738,-2.42874421615189 53.1215443892754,-2.42866423898571 53.1214682024937,-2.42853524354424 53.1214183428513,-2.42845898457643 53.1214186174646,-2.42821411543578 53.1214365732305,-2.4281513991788 53.1214359002623,-2.42809603901582 53.1214316062054,-2.42800446232625 53.1213905978391,-2.4279572513122 53.1214500783948,-2.42773771577048 53.121463448826,-2.42766320999209 53.1214789936385,-2.42759574800129 53.1214594658318,-2.42762346589685 53.1213847784635,-2.42760774878505 53.1213156390699,-2.42750692796397 53.1212369203352,-2.42729383911085 53.1211549202624,-2.42686968430942 53.121020746822,-2.42671241067068 53.1209763785349,-2.4266683418678 53.1207562779912,-2.42662696203803 53.1206458926813,-2.42659355270748 53.1205938908888,-2.4264581955888 53.1205107119694,-2.42634380069644 53.1204293449502,-2.42616318019795 53.1205900411546,-2.42580374258308 53.1209571674387,-2.4257532891809 53.1210004830644,-2.42570439280881 53.1210392998593,-2.42558689501206 53.1210927403788,-2.42542053761651 53.1212012628497,-2.42508859414015 53.1213219693009,-2.42492286083382 53.121344128801,-2.42480918374675 53.1213229671492,-2.42467981211004 53.12123446283,-2.42457286184998 53.1211457885052,-2.42453075362705 53.1211234725529,-2.42448721138331 53.1211056549398,-2.42435718624831 53.1211007268338,-2.42415289506917 53.1212983489217,-2.42395339918923 53.1215202170496,-2.42379474476074 53.1216483901688,-2.42310747234973 53.1215052550423,-2.42282755687402 53.1214549372586,-2.42244253729917 53.1213529603116,-2.42243902520502 53.1212963579832,-2.42221931854807 53.1211415818837,-2.42205003753823 53.1210909595181,-2.42198973260579 53.1210345586013,-2.42196680901717 53.1209834169824,-2.42194827650549 53.1209277665497,-2.421935181026 53.1208108989307,-2.42196000362753 53.120603223301,-2.42193832877033 53.1205160414733,-2.42189111844415 53.1204254454562,-2.42189061663769 53.120374224317,-2.42191434738868 53.120206003188,-2.42189992445469 53.1201045071347,-2.42187241691406 53.1200506858005,-2.42169533544224 53.1199704352089,-2.42154657929328 53.1198890954955,-2.42140127371424 53.1198455764466,-2.42118067203047 53.1197493035496,-2.42115964144334 53.1197403915115,-2.42111414917063 53.1196740525873,-2.42100243260348 53.1195503446539,-2.42089134087607 53.1195031093318,-2.42075825023083 53.1194865057243,-2.42065477016964 53.1194491283913,-2.42053960397284 53.1194387517051,-2.420421709325 53.1194517493907,-2.42029173347199 53.1194513099167,-2.42001907797147 53.119385772747,-2.4198752188747 53.1193386521398,-2.4197489679259 53.1192653185938,-2.41969166017714 53.1192125005224,-2.41964246263458 53.1192207618713,-2.41937714103948 53.1192881972403,-2.41930409676829 53.1193019343821,-2.41885151003587 53.1193179966331,-2.41863979723388 53.1190580439817,-2.41859765135272 53.1190186517555,-2.41855100777172 53.1189854760053,-2.41842195284277 53.1189275177936,-2.41811754107953 53.1188261420283,-2.41803680922123 53.1188093513825,-2.4177434107284 53.1187636521321,-2.41733366547911 53.11857268948,-2.41699398471128 53.1183653042318,-2.4168318250081 53.1182849941132,-2.41738010683885 53.1175046632765,-2.41793756098283 53.1167448766062,-2.4189540330962 53.1152680579047,-2.41946693545257 53.114543467858,-2.42065609009434 53.1130003337717,-2.41997142814287 53.1126548854918,-2.41969347143392 53.112495906804,-2.41946690189683 53.1123896767254,-2.41933281833286 53.112281412859,-2.41923308332712 53.1121586494339,-2.4191096620271 53.1120700281541,-2.41874465900211 53.1120155971088,-2.41863485640366 53.1120860781177,-2.41831549055213 53.1121268318127,-2.41812139415026 53.1119773498544,-2.41779133678769 53.1118428133277,-2.41760419315264 53.1118003351886,-2.41746422051146 53.1116937973198,-2.41721229740699 53.1115886404214,-2.41700538157768 53.1115138793144,-2.41672986785649 53.1114527480062,-2.41663859261698 53.1114395879375,-2.41646997311457 53.1114527593776,-2.41609504586863 53.1116069313532,-2.41588823598638 53.1115429517232,-2.41560418401613 53.1115286672619,-2.41565029237954 53.1113414973651,-2.41551322227921 53.1112287463865,-2.41538946467395 53.1111041764709,-2.4151077006657 53.1107006779963,-2.41505793184922 53.1106487299899,-2.41495702910978 53.1105565211115,-2.41483050944034 53.1104517305168,-2.41467857588467 53.1103426249869,-2.41454925807055 53.1102541093909,-2.41446960366331 53.1102066686436,-2.41439299269829 53.1101682935976,-2.4141605610888 53.1100774407328,-2.41391607353687 53.1099623658343,-2.41383059334694 53.1099366023681,-2.41362392338757 53.1098860081876,-2.41351714870571 53.1096563251952,-2.41325333226058 53.1092463794844,-2.4130266194716 53.1089675970066,-2.41293244287917 53.1088052684141,-2.41288036557552 53.1086661585305,-2.4127624657875 53.1085343763306,-2.41313048940237 53.1084324502412,-2.4130521010517 53.108195389152,-2.41300916275562 53.1076220202357,-2.41300381133473 53.1073721244258,-2.41298425208362 53.1070405008279,-2.41306667275963 53.1067606448493,-2.41309100208667 53.1060225893816,-2.413068189299 53.1051974386188,-2.41335330339317 53.1051856645497,-2.41361564395166 53.1051236445901,-2.41366327113625 53.105107303302,-2.41376731691186 53.1050539211484,-2.41373223311134 53.1049785565826,-2.41369307603892 53.1049535305569,-2.41355359487964 53.1048820336481,-2.41347385752849 53.1048247972141,-2.41344466836681 53.1047476147752,-2.41357602253955 53.1045755161035,-2.41369587566543 53.1044626782988,-2.41372841126412 53.1044266191629,-2.41372760882484 53.104343047517,-2.41368540349268 53.1041543879454,-2.41369006596795 53.1040114863988,-2.4136985380791 53.1039575379435,-2.41376949277399 53.1038826133763,-2.41387519449132 53.1038480970022,-2.41413086149708 53.1037204976489,-2.41418875573457 53.1036834514543,-2.41423767745701 53.1036482337731,-2.41427735155419 53.10357341781,-2.41426938174311 53.1035258171129,-2.41421859430471 53.1033669329022,-2.41411208237071 53.1031632202829,-2.41398921912639 53.1029622604146,-2.41398525128428 53.1028697132635,-2.41407428721639 53.1028055992424,-2.414109811254 53.1027731241887,-2.41413632846103 53.102738883178,-2.41417894007986 53.1026622597091,-2.41437116737109 53.1026103672617,-2.41446416750508 53.1023439529835,-2.41463335767168 53.1020737683614,-2.41470659716188 53.1019296391722,-2.4148469509895 53.1017727846781,-2.4149274845297 53.1016061636506,-2.41508339295499 53.101351211861,-2.41513105609491 53.1011856938811,-2.41524241640144 53.1009596541184,-2.41526976846754 53.1008589097958,-2.41556397368005 53.1005414676194,-2.41572274782096 53.1004311876592,-2.41602588865455 53.1002746613979,-2.41632942575593 53.1001593810319,-2.41654896178832 53.1000040446327,-2.41647099575094 53.0998110178558,-2.41666859740798 53.099552413183,-2.41698919971003 53.0991907511747,-2.4172073291408 53.0990435063121,-2.41749123818896 53.0986065747822,-2.4172451357557 53.0983188814195,-2.41689074989529 53.0979749520513,-2.41678210055118 53.0978557223164,-2.41664534125008 53.0976053878953,-2.41647997587775 53.0973380790931,-2.41634896445375 53.0970833208013,-2.41621653857533 53.096822186883,-2.41594984124517 53.0962612830312,-2.41585453635159 53.0959802485527,-2.41569979501886 53.0957281785413,-2.41523782385867 53.0952174709254,-2.41501652193289 53.0948676793292,-2.41480650833049 53.0946158009437,-2.41466024583596 53.0944760313971,-2.41380612579555 53.094475411027,-2.41341763197027 53.0944587887939,-2.4133699394613 53.0941461339927,-2.41322268397699 53.0935938851184,-2.41331154142571 53.0933589385115,-2.41352764457908 53.0930022315853,-2.41333648221894 53.0929939094628,-2.41311663898292 53.0929605243988,-2.41290534369467 53.0928811881635,-2.4127313024282 53.0927964202559,-2.41267580848571 53.0927741464989,-2.41261135298057 53.0927545997557,-2.41256805346607 53.0927457634233,-2.41246776289237 53.0927254422319,-2.41239305183996 53.0927149174466,-2.41225720989451 53.0927234761734,-2.41195457170837 53.0926192925379,-2.41178378856327 53.0925659647675,-2.41174110845665 53.0924672608316,-2.41157505300715 53.0924318894292,-2.4114190649902 53.0923677261249,-2.41119233031865 53.0922309265456,-2.41109290193557 53.0921458983,-2.41095672202121 53.0921059295263,-2.41075464240067 53.0920625935658,-2.41060751823832 53.0919722478274,-2.41052308571312 53.0918844713854,-2.41045338760172 53.0917795696602,-2.41036213880942 53.0917646074067,-2.41026650934119 53.0917550521022,-2.41005341331339 53.091808807325,-2.409960107216 53.0918882102768,-2.40983259742791 53.0919830080794,-2.40982093736514 53.0920127037546,-2.40980545259663 53.0921063067333,-2.40976849587432 53.0921558598845,-2.40948052920956 53.0921694326439,-2.40935960222424 53.0921797340256,-2.40911663262371 53.0922255025006,-2.40902962307273 53.0921772745384,-2.40891882818183 53.0921524932211,-2.40887857850974 53.0921535302304,-2.40883973422324 53.092159954305,-2.40867481537963 53.0922440956083,-2.40864855090482 53.0921489287767,-2.40866698058279 53.0920410272758,-2.40865257218862 53.0919367433285,-2.40860558319242 53.0918632153167,-2.4085793663375 53.0917860213328,-2.40861274289388 53.0916833705374,-2.40862966105088 53.0915718796194,-2.40867533782259 53.0915070197817,-2.40874009973163 53.0914034523259,-2.4087310672993 53.0910870681047,-2.40881777350999 53.0909348081343,-2.40875258973064 53.0908379777555,-2.40874017944798 53.0907885945541,-2.40872997321634 53.0906600325571,-2.40871324183009 53.0906223466724,-2.40868900932647 53.0905855852094,-2.40860181232229 53.0905301683566,-2.40846250248389 53.0904839169183,-2.40840708489486 53.0904561591321,-2.40833162578559 53.0903791341361,-2.40820451027393 53.0902034346733,-2.40801894791885 53.0899918996288,-2.40785529851245 53.0898972037653,-2.40765178904069 53.089857462051,-2.40727601482111 53.0899054791662,-2.40720263862259 53.0898922506011,-2.4071682874786 53.0898788884134,-2.4071366999303 53.0898583275418,-2.4071019363607 53.0898143227186,-2.40707409775781 53.089708377073,-2.40704756255692 53.0895970350478,-2.40701099223906 53.0893616235242,-2.4071388786479 53.0889809662241,-2.40732752421694 53.0885685580233,-2.40768031542166 53.0882914632102,-2.40865559453624 53.0875410669948,-2.40911014905469 53.0871314264528,-2.40921515681861 53.0870277202207,-2.40890371039586 53.08678157203,-2.40919301222244 53.086588175664,-2.4094014986409 53.086362705284,-2.40978061409667 53.0858796321961,-2.40988022467006 53.0856877861268,-2.40991037523162 53.0855573776025,-2.40990714594446 53.085373075084,-2.40987134191188 53.0852195288685,-2.40990277121066 53.0849128901414,-2.41091338675064 53.0841237109731,-2.41193283440118 53.083309420057,-2.41221456528126 53.0831133464393,-2.41232088961738 53.0829817745639,-2.4124483459408 53.0825758603902,-2.4125943857687 53.0819254479167,-2.41266021976445 53.0816276754396,-2.4127243780628 53.0813092396983,-2.41278987230673 53.0808218524331,-2.41272957594826 53.0802961696968,-2.4130929515225 53.0802095361141,-2.41363460382592 53.0801797953833,-2.41415597215327 53.0799091938015,-2.41465313762714 53.0797590938783,-2.41494267017216 53.0795972251366,-2.41584562767704 53.0794214401784,-2.41612127560735 53.0793647595793,-2.4163967997335 53.0793080787737,-2.41670107665083 53.0792719656327,-2.41733542353841 53.079270640161,-2.41767866003272 53.079254158193,-2.41799864162013 53.0791622700451,-2.4181636145589 53.0790780254784,-2.41823840794292 53.0790993301883,-2.41843680805228 53.0790860512103,-2.41863972696921 53.0790691613808,-2.41906290310177 53.0789957788254,-2.41954951082866 53.0789904687226,-2.41987440768833 53.0789363016435,-2.42025532652181 53.0789601186323,-2.42043021654796 53.0789846628608,-2.42075418763835 53.0789871118475,-2.42116169924495 53.0791376319275,-2.42122295599351 53.0791464015415,-2.42140272586738 53.0792167584092,-2.42162989004088 53.0792375210414,-2.42200141487498 53.0793701028692,-2.42226401942447 53.0795157413,-2.42240743123914 53.079530509184,-2.42273441298282 53.0795257528631,-2.42286945378524 53.0794524818595,-2.42299447205867 53.0794115080213,-2.4231951170418 53.079476485885,-2.42370567892904 53.0793280977205,-2.42405120452818 53.0792441901676,-2.42427514289138 53.0792496821358,-2.42469689531406 53.0791699940379,-2.42468680376366 53.0790576084528,-2.42512988484192 53.0790317618988,-2.4255781221603 53.0790670037213,-2.42636743884852 53.0793410521676,-2.42680169599975 53.0794680920786,-2.42708168062989 53.0795524591959,-2.42740950066864 53.079644741656,-2.42770406815713 53.0796976020152,-2.42802245911144 53.0797324927016,-2.42820311269551 53.0797417276565,-2.42847332254338 53.079746146483,-2.42900568640777 53.0796875224316,-2.4301424530697 53.0794632465621,-2.43043894261749 53.0794001668195,-2.43048226080396 53.0788076171882,-2.43056483795452 53.0785600984941,-2.43101100095808 53.078683395487,-2.4320499037095 53.0791246398205,-2.432928107054 53.0794702142463,-2.43296548965262 53.079479064716,-2.43301476564733 53.0794833786046,-2.43310131274664 53.0794731782955,-2.4337995038804 53.0792845226226,-2.4338679456089 53.0792609079722,-2.4340187324947 53.0792621551525,-2.43424690927346 53.0792361599922,-2.4346019178704 53.0792159916085,-2.43520212919593 53.0792227835152,-2.43618117986156 53.079204818709,-2.4375420434373 53.0790065198127,-2.43788458860493 53.0792138369219,-2.43810612502705 53.0794189028597,-2.43833513862685 53.0796328375047,-2.43886336846581 53.0796048286837,-2.43892334454259 53.0796324656611,-2.43895377958365 53.0796962476738,-2.43906428508871 53.0796940424967,-2.43917441952518 53.0796674850524,-2.43922524144104 53.0796663987362,-2.43928041683513 53.0796697895922,-2.43950034137622 53.0797157970561,-2.43957952760768 53 0795752244749,-2.43984867828234 53.0794636949635,-2.43988744755402 53.0794635515886,-2.43992625348976 53.0794670026833,-2.44002814962513 53.0795016732862,-2.44013746724133 53.0795399109574,-2.44045222064158 53.0796636587925,-2.44052108243843 53.0796814667279,-2.44080423364289 53.0796273072221,-2.44105105482624 53.079679502722,-2.44137474136821 53.0797978230682,-2.44179864542831 53.0799427299664,-2.44186742444141 53.0799523596754,-2.44193616665253 53.0799583948636,-2.4421977748823 53.0798558746096,-2.44287758798961 53.0797625812066,-2.44310337745848 53.0798039770427,-2.44326344667458 53.0798339348782,-2.44356981611335 53.0798714348894,-2.44381744583399 53.0798462474863,-2.44389382635114 53.080020391306,-2.44392111995373 53.0800652221701,-2.4440422265917 53.0800764526238,-2.44423589596925 53.0800343913495,-2.44454093295308 53.0799423977197,-2.44468576284508 53.0797953756485,-2.44469919686943 53.0797971227321,-2.44480407000457 53.0798335754303,-2.44490286403746 53.0800085334437,-2.44495255899376 53.0800532802799,-2.44521385496049 53.0800523025213,-2.44531468721611 53.07999530982,-2.44545249758249 53.0800388278654,-2.44569517311732 53.0802607851147,-2.44595407303138 53.0804683924297,-2.44600817487595 53.0804987438293,-2.44606878876971 53.0805874833262,-2.44614413854087 53.0806609802592,-2.44624576352238 53.0806686869263,-2.44644312218512 53.0806976019304,-2.44658102897972 53.0807501048524,-2.44676868040882 53.0808518467771,-2.44712540806778 53.0808424184507,-2.44737697619784 53.0807812626654,-2.4476140537495 53.0807471205144,-2.44791718080033 53.0807558646015,-2.44802189093967 53.0807761392985,-2.44811121185031 53.0807605256994,-2.44816226763389 53.0809239783343,-2.44817277621719 53.0809284320123,-2.44825502074527 53.0809425005684,-2.44840284890341 53.0809545245385,-2.44850950558435 53.0810080416865,-2.44863368995356 53.0810426208849,-2.44877730421652 53.0810636468294,-2.44908355609695 53.0810885519411,-2.44917520734448 53.0811430238002,-2.44930579905529 53.0812136141484,-2.4495019100355 53.0812640965064,-2.4497683844848 53.0813340828981,-2.44994362880028 53.0813900353569,-2.45011266432618 53.0814289366172,-2.45023847940153 53.0814662039355,-2.45047533908758 53.081564248996,-2.45054007651042 53.0816107338388,-2.45054827824737 53.081688885714,-2.45052958315406 53.081749166377,-2.45050900630497 53.0817824945291,-2.45043052155279 53.0818457874413,-2.45064556750039 53.0818467702156,-2.45082454151023 53.0818353081614,-2.45084367777524 53.0818054901674,-2.45087837708977 53.0816984187566,-2.45092248409879 53.081631751123,-2.4510376316318 53.0816492876377,-2.45129982955911 53.0817453478011,-2.45133337927024 53.0820930896565,-2.45138599969737 53.0821342280872,-2.45143370944113 53.0821295537546,-2.45154549989524 53.082108460378,-2.45160354943379 53.0820920642169,-2.45171348547559 53.0820467140517,-2.45190125751225 53.0820055613697,-2.45207010880403 53.0820264874628,-2.45221388759514 53.0820744682746,-2.45228305869322 53.0821209353137,-2.45243581472291 53.0821680729333,-2.45254047381428 53.0821829519263,-2.45261393549791 53.0822042401237,-2.45274127916885 53.0822459922545,-2.45278778547993 53.0822673829398,-2.45290370891598 53.0823702868732,-2.45303625982101 53.0824741158851,-2.4531754590056 53.0825077345066,-2.45322673688202 53.0825614584017,-2.45337843320412 53.0826480497804,-2.45345923400442 53.0826648162105,-2.45352399797044 53.0825729065426,-2.45355202415296 53.0825458400475,-2.45370318344369 53.0824409297925,-2.45377035020232 53.0824370789617,-2.45393609017145 53.0824428270183,-2.45407566842023 53.0825123893214,-2.45413143534956 53.0825598051104,-2.45422015148772 53.082615182947,-2.45441413470561 53.0826144420382,-2.45451130622242 53.0826194627047,-2.45469346382495 53.0826295503807,-2.45465503284681 53.0826620488428,-2.45453050805887 53.0827478969224,-2.45434176090456 53.0829652836078,-2.45419820425178 53.0830908346857,-2.45408333451395 53.0832404498817,-2.45402647760412 53.0832298830644,-2.45397563309101 53.0832174959648,-2.45384543529235 53.0831856412429,-2.45366751741682 53.0831692455157,-2.45346942157171 53.0832122376373,-2.45360624596006 53.0833006827249,-2.45378491216475 53.0833998417554,-2.45378971228167 53.0834231884561,-2.45381191390177 53.0835444220906,-2.45398273166277 53.0836111693444,-2.45441403532529 53.0837381198842,-2.45457015985867 53.0838121116604,-2.45473151221971 53.0839732527138,-2.45491311112966 53.0841982104356,-2.45522841522355 53.0839470884111,-2.45540932562837 53.083826874894,-2.45565430736686 53.0837010237545,-2.45589761966173 53.0835571155509,-2.45590055478448 53.0835553069927,-2.45599112713044 53.0835064324823,-2.45606096435072 53.0834756104923,-2.45624393696173 53.0834111043581,-2.45629758380813 53.0833974187613,-2.45644501261943 53.0833707022803,-2.45672854943219 53.0833525394927,-2.45687031808531 53.0833492990985,-2.45696885502007 53.0833552111712,-2.45710048430869 53.0833708811987,-2.45731733121698 53.0834132729808,-2.45737115880617 53.0834166606396,-2.4574263776734 53.0834119550336,-2.45749185012179 53.0833991220758,-2.45756488724036 53.0833799694018,-2.45773292537047 53.0833235164458,-2.45781779775302 53.0833061153808,-2.45791023566537 53.0832940770581,-2.45799082946052 53.0832910708124,-2.45811192009378 53.0832995910619,-2.45853658030681 53.0833681397259,-2.45869522496691 53.0834007782826,-2.45937595590005 53.0835419360236,-2.45993512805298 53.0836188568321,-2.46016300568072 53.0837025388906,-2.46040852966539 53.0837671906022,-2.46052373468416 53.0837892109988,-2.46084525986211 53.0838355944531,-2.46092691276743 53.0839431166238,-2.46106983160582 53.0838976300109,-2.46118216188721 53.0839385326586,-2.46126909561361 53.0839642565592,-2.46135337617405 53.084029621351,-2.46158169601484 53.084016154427,-2.46141841341393 53.0842522354018,-2.46134885238543 53.0844467044428,-2.46117737898743 53.0844581532252,-2.46104717397887 53.0844379889089,-2.4608578876372 53.0847407601667,-2.46008765572803 53.0846124483968,-2.46007580310829 53.0846206719953,-2.45996796143054 53.0847352181567,-2.45975379941448 53.0849455224215,-2.45960473527745 53.0851078562413,-2.45915707781271 53.0855518128016,-2.45894706309086 53.0857477210971,-2.4587576942078 53.0859058059169,-2.45840900805709 53.0862469312763,-2.45828549284015 53.0864280366673,-2.45879939234449 53.0865968898225,-2.45911668822382 53.0866720511981,-2.45924710140526 53.0867227710621,-2.45988607953404 53.0869953804388,-2.46001969668585 53.087057769572,-2.46015619344043 53.0871246406861,-2.46059167578559 53.0873611884757,-2.46104291842604 53.0875284772325,-2.46148856449745 53.0877361355548,-2.46159160469261 53.0878742183399,-2.46165977530489 53.0878254264804,-2.46183603200625 53.0876961449256,-2.46204819523621 53.0875632188914,-2.46217587802959 53.0873586385464,-2.46249589727657 53.0875488979236,-2.46236674977051 53.0876167990268,-2.46250661859828 53.0877106139613,-2.46274873393084 53.0875928473344,-2.46324495265957 53.0879235078141,-2.46297992109754 53.0881313198972,-2.46317607943292 53.0881817795595,-2.46327503134754 53.0882137457753,-2.46359287826989 53.0883383190517,-2.46392525807736 53.0885662698704,-2.4641344932113 53.0887219093285,-2.46447265825803 53.088926381175,-2.46510772282039 53.0891154029988,-2.46550949335119 53.0888477400316,-2.46572432016658 53.088961926872,-2.4657790792767 53.0893357322281,-2.46614086737284 53.0892416638852,-2.46639410616325 53.0891849547493,-2.46669213597969 53.0892628674473,-2.4667668428817 53.0891358641329,-2.46688193713056 53.089009600918,-2.46706989035524 53.0888586980174,-2.46726642599793 53.0886592337852,-2.46747195437477 53.0884831887509,-2.46759170679676 53.0883667917187,-2.46770984752985 53.0882494123799,-2.46790011145745 53.0880284040304,-2.46803140382901 53.0882948776793,-2.46820143609414 53.0885576040889,-2.46839474340937 53.0887528395511,-2.46855541393221 53.0888447681718,-2.46873218048005 53.0888997883373,-2.46859609304661 53.0890082528359,-2.46877941414643 53.0891225582763,-2.46903469184192 53.0892536541679,-2.46924319563744 53.0893400911907,-2.46970653049238 53.0895161961129,-2.47021585833865 53.0896760315367,-2.47066497777808 53.0897784992942,-2.47096108522402 53.0898258546859,-2.47098658781611 53.0898275510262,-2.471211000498 53.0894653135347,-2.47197457534556 53.0896492963827,-2.47172738399621 53.089988260638,-2.47258070452789 53.0901933615171,-2.47264943728515 53.090061884966,-2.47316231349496 53.0899825618636,-2.47361284455276 53.0903582935819,-2.47356004345605 53.0904492678381,-2.47426816244312 53.0906145850016,-2.4746082665827 53.0907210670803,-2.47567874343729 53.0905649189468,-2.47581703278035 53.0903782546452,-2.47609780382226 53.0901173303895,-2.4768027732538 53.0904093553251,-2.47692561563267 53.0912529686462,-2.47703851541866 53.0921433515997,-2.47717325927527 53.0924484433727,-2.47732125782616 53.0924604307982,-2.47733359916366 53.0927633174729,-2.47794748356669 53.0927752311839,-2.47861707209429 53.0927032529627,-2.47924180917029 53.0926171630644,-2.47933075039857 53.0928208890233,-2.47955176280366 53.0930986708634,-2.47965008053824 53.0932043156469,-2.47981300319986 53.0933511277376,-2.480022057641 53.0934832851461,-2.48017361285691 53.0935599577497,-2.48031456945274 53.0936025241097,-2.48053745200446 53.0936384688306,-2.48061226215071 53.0936562295662,-2.48069807738508 53.0937223832248,-2.48072875641143 53.0937905569419,-2.48072908710208 53.0938202111788,-2.48069893470772 53.0939317660798,-2.48070274514209 53.0939974422693,-2.48074659084099 53.0940538802779,-2.48064541214932 53.0940785527526,-2.48050418823254 53.09414472496,-2.48047421824786 53.0942616709817,-2.48041826275716 53.0943338791162,-2.48038118808593 53.094354697862,-2.48034097532809 53.0943701373448,-2.48013033193484 53.0943611024681,-2.48010299538977 53.0944492808462,-2.48008677764637 53.094474508595,-2.4799915173188 53.0945000552797,-2.47995596975571 53.0945253609984,-2.47992490447184 53.0945551418923,-2.47988414834206 53.0946434642173,-2.47984402516189 53.0946669910514,-2.47980236448856 53.0946851321514,-2.47975598143717 53.0946772313272,-2.47962566015089 53.0946391146992,-2.47936861419045 53.0947533810773,-2.47943903245324 53.0947746649951,-2.47970701608489 53.0948355918052,-2.47980754678848 53.0950069190847,-2.47947992713516 53.0950972066597,-2.47972629582497 53.0952293040316,-2.47913755415756 53.0954554413415,-2.47880183110761 53.0956258296883,-2.47869504371196 53.0956891651584,-2.47858536091581 53.0957579040994,-2.4783393269716 53.0959333222087,-2.47780130984459 53.0964271374267,-2.47782905534277 53.096641893976,-2.47794746317228 53.0969488475939,-2.47819520048827 53.0974701492714,-2.4782870568901 53.0978140540115,-2.47837974749625 53.0980887590282,-2.47853754795528 53.0983163822682,-2.47865818574634 53.0982799508448,-2.47881871413466 53.0982208924335,-2.47942348689379 53.0979379872661,-2.47981098970989 53.097738721407,-2.48014488424299 53.0975467700003,-2.48138196147018 53.0967930130262,-2.48254174265339 53.0975415657756,-2.48145484398442 53.0978282362209,-2.48156234371046 53.0979608018038,-2.48176899152066 53.098150569497,-2.48194147024209 53.0983457773026,-2.48240406264935 53.0989813171014,-2.48247131395279 53.099114943692,-2.4825199467028 53.0993233238177,-2.48259271838356 53.0995539824622,-2.48262488242845 53.0997651252915,-2.48262434063916 53.0998487022089,-2.48258887322333 53.1000133894222,-2.48253355676396 53.1001430197993,-2.48250510058824 53.100802027437,-2.48249979468367 53.1011310457156,-2.48247383916937 53.101474526159,-2.4824876369898 53.1017720140868,-2.48245239646881 53.1019681531223,-2.4824422132746 53.1021255484774,-2.48243362984243 53.1022828474753,-2.4824396846251 53.102559697758,-2.4823942510987 53.1029014597744,-2.48226101734931 53.1035519052925,-2.48224828841097 53.1036139638967,-2.48212013066977 53.1039039391859,-2.48188174745693 53.1043589040194,-2.48169337225017 53.1047488730649,-2.48139731399839 53.1052453184618,-2.48116346418571 53.1054458550116,-2.48091904686818 53.1056266634629,-2.48066763550511 53.1058541396932,-2.48040229286724 53.1061689307257,-2.48015955055806 53.1065007043237,-2.48019782806429 53.1068521024182,-2.48024112406051 53.107653704707,-2.48042092856573 53.1085141566354,-2.4805485062079 53.1092300463843,-2.48006393150949 53.1091825766506,-2.47964388803372 53.1091564124609,-2.479222267175 53.1091212666292,-2.47901594574473 53.1091086176642,-2.47821782295067 53.1090749834359,-2.47817601156057 53.1090697595682,-2.4780062696594 53.1089903717773,-2.47782367795912 53.1092293376476,-2.47788485746986 53.1093594862457,-2.4780162199641 53.1096096822763,-2.47808472057033 53.1097335107943,-2.47829605519731 53.1100643536202,-2.4782901932178 53.11006887044,-2.4781426924105 53.1101072066148,-2.47802347272064 53.1101301519199,-2.47787723014971 53.110148712384,-2.47717227549663 53.110165920009,-2.47670010202623 53.1101489409827,-2.47641601023228 53.1101321058041,-2.47530797478338 53.1101652940606,-2.47529884418509 53.1102866484271,-2.47528174966426 53.1103560027073,-2.4752053411428 53.1104749298296,-2.4751788182523 53.1105046912378,-2.47509107799898 53.1105454808999,-2.47496802253846 53.1106341298415,-2.47478921056443 53.110804688525,-2.47466573692302 53.1108555056122,-2.47455644970864 53.1115121364161,-2.47429768719519 53.1114808167346,-2.47408363945828 53.1114385345299,-2.47383672158657 53.1114089639552,-2.47364987096977 53.1113980254404,-2.47342440040075 53.1114034160154,-2.47313117690663 53.1113632444015,-2.47218884115153 53.1112563638278,-2.47223835437087 53.1115483186922,-2.4722837444861 53.1118798305193,-2.47233880177904 53.1121268307749,-2.47243948708631 53.1124572243463,-2.47250038926207 53.1126979107447,-2.4723976298649 53.1127288728784,-2.47247049960989 53.1129713090691,-2.47264180752137 53.1134623702853,-2.47172624823975 53.1134875711274,-2.47124370304519 53.113493976439,-2.47077791830649 53.1135236783931,-2.47025837025583 53.1135481991137,-2.46926547646209 53.1136096326505,-2.46922696947197 53.1132295655418,-2.46818122126422 53.1132327861959,-2.46816151443622 53.1130629289517,-2.46807865566382 53.112590474956,-2.46795367636453 53.1119482517153,-2.4677507517758 53.1111489809958,-2.46721598000242 53.1111528793767,-2.46682160883554 53.1111553259441,-2.46610771626802 53.1111680098238,-2.46594075661711 53.1111965219176,-2.46555849725914 53.1112141939294,-2.46479965692934 53.1112279444744,-2.46252665133785 53.1112871264259,-2.46257696682526 53.1117975439845,-2.46262122888951 53.1123061877156,-2.46250580180259 53.1122706904331,-2.46231480285292 53.112424203253,-2.46216799308895 53.1125290170149,-2.46203037748236 53.1126527564112,-2.46192679743088 53.1127457195453,-2.46164986213899 53.1129724453967,-2.46151837639138 53.113116739492,-2.46130927238168 53.1132596269517,-2.46122666729084 53.1133561027411,-2.46116215101653 53.1134623935155,-2.46109952895929 53.1136190911795,-2.46109145102224 53.113704494236,-2.46085379763621 53.1136892392371,-2.4605558397244 53.1136328792955,-2.46011429677617 53.1135573036287,-2.45972236768844 53.1135021137312,-2.45952640471993 53.1134804044506,-2.45911821219569 53.1134478314891,-2.45890438129081 53.1134369739285,-2.45847251392376 53.1134251590101,-2.45795362580028 53.1133732382333,-2.45708056766007 53.1133181830029,-2.45622601900402 53.1133241585986,-2.45533172057578 53.1132404151909,-2.45513124033425 53.1132105382529,-2.45496823460796 53.1131949859546,-2.45482922893849 53.113189226843,-2.45444996011434 53.1132005611624,-2.4537955980794 53.1132084505112,-2.45339251926393 53.1132280499803,-2.45325843014241 53.1132681014412,-2.45320944443737 53.1132952475295,-2.45316935552224 53.1133250556628,-2.45316983764955 53.1133708849666,-2.45318928635429 53.11351010161,-2.45324605464146 53.1138011377664,-2.45327542321122 53.1140284741356,-2.45333443049723 53.1142395218768,-2.45337527391689 53.114433474585,-2.45349186981249 53.1148609672119,-2.45367371291679 53.1153896684742,-2.45393546694276 53.116265122995,-2.454015080038 53.1165956120824,-2.45407863334691 53.1168165271723,-2.45410754421606 53.1169998311636,-2.45411355159344 53.1171489840166,-2.45410052311939 53.1173270561536,-2.45407066464178 53.1174745485703,-2.45405525748962 53.1179995982089,-2.45364960235445 53.1180712400728,-2.45319525720738 53.1181987822464,-2.45195528550238 53.1185001424208,-2.451210014138 53.1186693107007,-2.45067249893876 53.1188438883004,-2.45007772854131 53.1189864185442,-2.45037028693489 53.1195255792748,-2.45082488997755 53.12042088 956,-2.45130633286305 53"
  },
  "67": {
    "Question": "Where is Lesbos island located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?geoWKT WHERE {  yago:Lesbos geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "68": {
    "Question": "Where is Dire Dawa located?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?geoWKT where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dire_Dawa> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((41.92614746 9.6680603,41.93584824 9. .66346359,41.95233917 9.65467262,41.95819092 9.6515522,41.96609879 9.64733601,41.99642944 9.63116264,42.00838852 9.62216282,42.01890945 9.61792278,42.0308075 9.61848259,42.12228775 9.71002769,42.18577194 9.77356148,42.2133522 9.78374195,42.25099182 9.78349113,42.29352188 9.75749111,42.33977127 9.71961784,42.33412933 9.71599102,42.32834244 9.71338177,42.31814194 9.70566177,42.3112793 9.69909191,42.30276108 9.69113159,42.28594208 9.67614174,42.27185059 9.66695213,42.26264954 9.65690136,42.25863647 9.65158176,42.24077225 9.65664196,42.22052002 9.65616226,42.20053101 9.65314198,42.18038177 9.64434242,42.15959167 9.63068199,42.14225006 9.62029266,42.12485886 9.61452198,42.12784958 9.59837246,42.13005066 9.59210205,42.13341141 9.58249187,42.14612961 9.57063198,42.15259933 9.55637264,42.13890076 9.53469276,42.12186813 9.51922226,42.10968018 9.50796223,42.09626007 9.50131226,42.0810585 9.48816299,42.07477188 9.47371674,42.06761551 9.47480774,42.05781937 9.48508263,42.05213928 9.4919529,42.04390717 9.49831295,42.03171921 9.50440311,42.01910019 9.50817299,42.00233078 9.50771236,41.99535751 9.50646305,41.99000931 9.50662327,41.98252487 9.50849247,41.95448685 9.48911285,41.93874741 9.47954273,41.91337967 9.47246361,41.90829849 9.47389317,41.88241959 9.48118305,41.85970688 9.48801327,41.83867645 9.47791386,41.81519699 9.4767437,41.79254913 9.4895134,41.77299881 9.49105358,41.75452805 9.48457336,41.73461914 9.47148418,41.72802734 9.4890337,41.74906921 9.60055351,41.74860001 9.63635349,41.75574875 9.64032364,41.7738266 9.65370369,41.79100037 9.64903355,41.80103683 9.64241314,41.80867767 9.64055347,41.85327911 9.67374325,41.87323761 9.68388271,41.90613937 9.67930317,41.92614746 9.668060)^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "69": {
    "Question": "Where is Chichester located?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?geoWKT where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chichester> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. }",
    "Answer": "<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-0.799399497892057 50.8331689750718, ,-0.799727338134161 50.8332875132509,-0.802263441906647 50.8341822130584,-0.802764976914298 50.8343357892736,-0.803074757178392 50.8344423553823,-0.803377120465147 50.8345551378334,-0.803885809353333 50.8347681186159,-0.804323517499387 50.8349776728763,-0.804564555483853 50.8351033093844,-0.804796909457055 50.8352343405447,-0.805022082833728 50.8353715010275,-0.805238597460763 50.8355130675824,-0.805408720719489 50.8356326720398,-0.805563441085881 50.8357502306392,-0.80574153803888 50.8358923919842,-0.805911095319503 50.8360388709295,-0.806072014176067 50.8361889472769,-0.806224299146842 50.8363424413025,-0.806366517925256 50.836500417228,-0.806556428564934 50.8367397035531,-0.806649473328922 50.8368791956407,-0.80682241479265 50.8371687436254,-0.806976864685508 50.837462597463,-0.807115629755602 50.8377562907617,-0.807238737425032 50.8380533300782,-0.80729725979907 50.8382059542416,-0.807361185201696 50.8384314550628,-0.807361162294475 50.8384323538593,-0.807410625106016 50.8386648091926,-0.807451430631545 50.8391221134687,-0.807535122617471 50.8398540601567,-0.807763273862206 50.8409877307208,-0.807835680208924 50.8412115197316,-0.807895984459892 50.8413541824614,-0.807963336444937 50.8414960181073,-0.80827874685813 50.8420505243376,-0.808604516708852 50.8425296168747,-0.808968367593384 50.8429667527495,-0.809170426592731 50.8431765803186,-0.809610566336618 50.8435200943372,-0.810144227618679 50.843925694118,-0.810301794210533 50.8440387800058,-0.810545476728044 50.8441780060561,-0.810822339945421 50.8443480467635,-0.811058186700849 50.8444593219749,-0.810907871557673 50.8448948088752,-0.81077850885066 50.8452891536966,-0.810532223588848 50.845873889988,-0.810339903598547 50.8464501854969,-0.810119063226139 50.8470378772797,-0.809981882126831 50.8474582132599,-0.809941830940067 50.8475271200457,-0.809870198778724 50.8476082013055,-0.809844030136971 50.8476286121388,-0.809730394283153 50.8476849912138,-0.809688378100704 50.8477160287493,-0.809626926606696 50.8477882233931,-0.809512327126461 50.8478824415523,-0.809883651095471 50.8479725351416,-0.809811799604321 50.8481174451857,-0.809775614503078 50.8484210378967,-0.809571246878864 50.8492490270965,-0.809460779702293 50.8497973867944,-0.809414496640622 50.8499407593016,-0.809381470477878 50.8500096476318,-0.809329345889984 50.8501018057789,-0.809242281555601 50.8502321757902,-0.809154012538693 50.8503500369452,-0.808344473997976 50.8512355890881,-0.807967614512024 50.8517524583279,-0.807652202002574 50.8521422020956,-0.807328093579071 50.8524869047226,-0.807058902229826 50.8527908124205,-0.806865374270957 50.8530856036368,-0.806610981898043 50.8533096480361,-0.806385112322207 50.8535312864755,-0.805702397823193 50.8533956520059,-0.805135859005337 50.8532747781824,-0.804164775191375 50.8531938100777,-0.803723680799296 50.8531650163956,-0.803442420948016 50.8531612344169,-0.803104508208714 50.8532108125637,-0.802543533522662 50.8532023617662,-0.801052357177743 50.8532365007867,-0.800890842519212 50.8532222552222,-0.800454566093647 50.8531152831585,-0.800054052935313 50.8529977988705,-0.799617392078164 50.8528557575765,-0.799213980525945 50.8527418366932,-0.798862224187658 50.8526644970479,-0.798678315938612 50.8526329364112,-0.79856924275833 50.8526201263778,-0.798281307092212 50.8526027777923,-0.797583803267478 50.8526018876783,-0.797101036763406 50.8525906202092,-0.796360937036401 50.8525335439812,-0.796246868451208 50.8524964064705,-0.795048047005508 50.8523769623924,-0.793987219581709 50.8522527285677,-0.793868505017719 50.8521732863322,-0.793867099809282 50.8521732718115,-0.793652426832695 50.8520676649027,-0.793363376435674 50.8518757910084,-0.793086381688486 50.8516525750068,-0.792985230538635 50.8515553328702,-0.792909189840961 50.851474532865,-0.792768934066747 50.8512949845164,-0.79242960832835 50.8507914340548,-0.79222454269512 50.850259693819,-0.792129865394116 50.8500752220897,-0.792047730232695 50.849953902075,-0.791912802040467 50.8497905903002,-0.791450088290139 50.8493352961626,-0.791277349655374 50.8492030581636,-0.79112374893032 50.8491007760164,-0.790727499587356 50.8488205791368,-0.790164221435087 50.8484640301524,-0.790058402955531 50.8483847176082,-0.78998471760596 50.8483219206416,-0.789919673078667 50.848255617091,-0.789814856829092 50.8481330713521,-0.789641782074498 50.84817712724,-0.789504194412347 50.8480084807268,-0.789244144392995 50.8476254036365,-0.789151247270638 50.8474814041885,-0.789019998182441 50.8472309211501,-0.78892838889993 50.8470915199277,-0.788859714151026 50.8470027023295,-0.788778278739014 50.8469091672096,-0.788660494185025 50.8467946669844,-0.78850355548891 50.8466589926197,-0.788357320242888 50.8465441967607,-0.788240244909778 50.8464611695341,-0.78813951814167 50.8463980906116,-0.788049942399716 50.846347623918,-0.787840999875104 50.8462438636412,-0.787541875601158 50.8461130943044,-0.787331997938928 50.8459867577167,-0.787215065624432 50.8458983367434,-0.786222753815101 50.8449995091162,-0.785805907325111 50.8446399661666,-0.78539838946493 50.8443092877627,-0.785080661838937 50.8440703447538,-0.784516877003706 50.843741632572,-0.784061283047644 50.8434545012393,-0.783590918144437 50.8431861837129,-0.783072510163738 50.8428606344458,-0.78241893283837 50.8424328913262,-0.782046511682269 50.8421681963969,-0.781379487374497 50.841713425958,-0.780672627685125 50.8411520597798,-0.780477025114668 50.8409738057978,-0.78044094396544 50.8409383665269,-0.780168151244597 50.8406171684223,-0.779901284961178 50.8403382861168,-0.779832989635924 50.8402898335224,-0.779762842051134 50.8402540378748,-0.779747412341827 50.8402484823584,-0.779771974147178 50.8402316575489,-0.779849850427275 50.8401866210963,-0.779924659085638 50.8401514418771,-0.780012064215853 50.8401226875092,-0.780116327211301 50.8400986044414,-0.780330659586603 50.84004780161,-0.780666418717003 50.8399703071646,-0.78091182013879 50.839927020118,-0.781346849960298 50.8398596408317,-0.781602107467907 50.8398200513793,-0.781743315990845 50.8397936554547,-0.781840389447443 50.8397757890279,-0.781960454993796 50.8397473740945,-0.78206211706803 50.8397151708592,-0.782176892736713 50.8396695289875,-0.782294709511958 50.8396195134759,-0.782480096935509 50.8395333424506,-0.782639892779848 50.8394540964534,-0.782792362054649 50.8393773810198,-0.782981282089793 50.8392678712096,-0.783184646895489 50.8391477233121,-0.783297262488806 50.8390769748257,-0.783483840180948 50.8389493692399,-0.783634312204902 50.8388412556707,-0.783811264413855 50.8387009627936,-0.783933451553647 50.8385907560229,-0.784057323166306 50.8384697782884,-0.784129057924233 50.8383859267186,-0.78417175964424 50.8383288335199,-0.784216449529339 50.8382447900517,-0.784245196271549 50.8381794601623,-0.784287942606788 50.8380620423252,-0.784341711258393 50.837907968865,-0.784410510508637 50.837720697836,-0.784446887498417 50.8376320725288,-0.784458635608353 50.8375629694056,-0.784463875488588 50.8374694347217,-0.784465743184474 50.8373975315922,-0.784457497082417 50.8373318163503,-0.784444705914785 50.8372246982825,-0.7844325978144 50.8371408722628,-0.784508639503035 50.8371119961845,-0.784573232657241 50.8370865969579,-0.78466224406039 50.8370497645588,-0.784746994398023 50.837014685787,-0.784845955453087 50.8369734616902,-0.784894815598107 50.8369541916998,-0.784980339884275 50.836938899528,-0.785051629980792 50.8369306513721,-0.785158226559283 50.83692906392,-0.785673324424752 50.836942515883,-0.785836696201795 50.8369415185367,-0.786095775321533 50.8369163435755,-0.786385150215058 50.8368743115676,-0.786567740032436 50.8368456430424,-0.786782073943526 50.836793929391,-0.786943521044861 50.8367587472649,-0.78708605225112 50.8367350557472,-0.787532119353979 50.8366785565886,-0.787758768804811 50.8366440507042,-0.78808527167115 50.8365970059389,-0.78830300250661 50.8365767909004,-0.788529558575254 50.8365503738412,-0.788713293960073 50.8365271080494,-0.789029772791915 50.836482743607,-0.789515890952322 50.8364122679326,-0.789952140593803 50.8363457683586,-0.790477802549081 50.8362810029666,-0.791043470355067 50.836208648249,-0.791685973511033 50.8361307931024,-0.792203060938538 50.8360714152697,-0.792714483019802 50.8360091895445,-0.793151758422568 50.8359570731513,-0.793409471243989 50.835934564943,-0.793677248546759 50.8359031698777,-0.793810187997354 50.835756203649,-0.793888007665157 50.8356580244942,-0.79395276413107 50.8355714876106,-0.793988264373587 50.8355161144862,-0.794036580683703 50.8354041448689,-0.794088859828074 50.8354155633599,-0.794169515861344 50.8354253870586,-0.79423623937967 50.8354260764379,-0.794284677291092 50.8354229807409,-0.794300338734145 50.8354195464133,-0.794337469273719 50.8354099507504,-0.794391942752408 50.8353907347862,-0.794432182627415 50.8353740688613,-0.794481267433962 50.8353413117122,-0.79458246414294 50.8353810153515,-0.794658628327159 50.8354015806998,-0.794746355607897 50.8354141741264,-0.794883994952939 50.8354209896683,-0.79501771971681 50.8354115820565,-0.7951476236818 50.8353868513048,-0.795236299715318 50.8353625938511,-0.795343932251046 50.8353160562062,-0.795456335269367 50.8352524860939,-0.795714310739156 50.8351058192196,-0.796142450659235 50.8348576084341,-0.796339822639293 50.8347498724256,-0.796475070695175 50.8346811427565,-0.796637589593223 50.8346037038072,-0.79677246707282 50.8345493544837,-0.796871460194963 50.8345108176499,-0.797054520522977 50.8344586728725,-0.797174794391946 50.8344212541636,-0.79740773922567 50.8343643186685,-0.797827861551636 50.8342589651704,-0.797957968633785 50.8342261421064,-0.798113942247914 50.8341800099046,-0.798288684993173 50.8341233722825,-0.798410823209468 50.8340679908637,-0.798513269372315 50.8340043153023,-0.798595746643372 50.833943131182,-0.798654112647835 50.8338816089055,-0.798718419510129 50.8338121463672,-0.798755248218892 50.8337594825701,-0.79879714603879 50.8336781019157,-0.798830637140207 50.8335912405298,-0.798846809841223 50.833513101306,-0.798852684588949 50.8334484314731,-0.798859322231492 50.8333585965974,-0.798965954812675 50.8333507037043,-0.799050042101031 50.8333407806503,-0.799140047728311 50.8333192310192,-0.799220195947015 50.8332939837686,-0.799279017261594 50.8332694160745,-0.799342679056149 50.8332250295446,-0.799399497892057 50.8331689750718))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "70": {
    "Question": "Which is the population of Nikaia Agios Ioannis Rentis?",
    "Query": "select ?o where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nikaia-Agios_Ioannis_Rentis> <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/hasGAG_Population> ?o. }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "71": {
    "Question": "Where is Mullingar city located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?geoWKT WHERE {  yago:Mullingar geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "72": {
    "Question": "Where is the Manchester city located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?geoWKT WHERE {  yago:Manchester geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "73": {
    "Question": "Where is Paxi island located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?geoWKT WHERE {  yago:Paxi geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "74": {
    "Question": "Where is the municipality of Athens located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?geoWKT WHERE{ yago:geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876 geo:hasGeometry ?o.                 ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.}",
    "Answer": "geoWKT <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((23.7039432525635 37.9611511230469,23...   more MULTIPOLYGON(((477353.59375 4209291,477411.90625 4209215,477406.1875 4209050,477442.5 4208972,4776...   more"
  },
  "75": {
    "Question": "Where is Coventry located?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?geoWKT WHERE {        yago:Coventry geo:hasGeometry ?o.        ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.}",
    "Answer": "geoWKT <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-1.47454226 52.46456146,-1.47189045 ...   more <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326> POLYGON ((-1.61412404396869 52.427741754924,-1...   more"
  },
  "76": {
    "Question": "Where is Cork City located?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?geoWKT WHERE {        <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cork_City_7778678>  geo:hasGeometry ?o .                        ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . }",
    "Answer": "geoWKT MULTIPOLYGON (((-9.88553190386653 51.6455212468997, -9.88555563831235 51.6455346123881, -9.8855515...   more"
  },
  "77": {
    "Question": "Where is the municipality of Chania located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?gWKT WHERE{         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Chania_8133762> geo:hasGeometry ?g. ?g geo:asWKT ?gWKT.  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "78": {
    "Question": "Where is the county Norfolk located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?gWKT WHERE{         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norfolk> geo:hasGeometry ?g.  ?g geo:asWKT ?gWKT.  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "79": {
    "Question": "Where is barony Ballymoe located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?gWKT WHERE{         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ballymoe> geo:hasGeometry ?g. ?g geo:asWKT ?gWKT.  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "80": {
    "Question": "Is Crete south of Thessaly?",
    "Query": "ASK { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Crete> geo:hasGeometry ?geo1 . <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Thessaly> geo:hasGeometry ?geo2 . ?geo1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 . ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 . FILTER(strdf:below(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "81": {
    "Question": "Is Worcestershire west of Oxfordshire?",
    "Query": "ASK { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Worcestershire> geo:hasGeometry ?geo1 . <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oxfordshire> geo:hasGeometry ?geo2 . ?geo1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 . ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 . FILTER(strdf:left(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "82": {
    "Question": "Is county Cavan east of county Mayo?",
    "Query": "ASK { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Cavan> geo:hasGeometry ?geo1 . <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Mayo> geo:hasGeometry ?geo2 . ?geo1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 . ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 . FILTER(strdf:right(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "83": {
    "Question": "Is Kythira within Attika ?",
    "Query": "ASK {         yago:geoentity_Kythira_8133702 geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Attica_(region)> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.         FILTER(geof:sfWithin(strdf:buffer(?WKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre)))  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "84": {
    "Question": "Is Bedford east of Essex?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:Bedford geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT. yago:Essex geo:hasGeometry ?o1. ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1. FILTER(strdf:right(?WKT, ?WKT1)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "85": {
    "Question": "Does Mayo border with Sligo?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:County_Mayo geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT. yago:County_Sligo geo:hasGeometry ?o1. ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1. FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:buffer(?WKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "86": {
    "Question": "Is Dublin above Kilkenny?",
    "Query": "ASK {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin> geo:hasGeometry ?o.     ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kilkenny> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.     ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.     FILTER(strdf:above(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "87": {
    "Question": "Is Samos east of Mykonos?",
    "Query": "ASK {      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Samos> geo:hasGeometry ?geo1 .     ?geo1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1 .     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mykonos> geo:hasGeometry ?geo2 .     ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2 .     FILTER(strdf:right(?wkt1,?wkt2)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "88": {
    "Question": "Is Municipality Thessaloniki north from Dimos Trikala ?",
    "Query": "ASK { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Thessaloniki_8133841> geo:hasGeometry ?thesgeo . ?thesgeo geo:asWKT ?thesWKT . <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Trikala_8133844> geo:hasGeometry ?trikgeo . ?trikgeo geo:asWKT ?trikWKT . FILTER (strdf:above(?thesWKT,?trikWKT)) . }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "89": {
    "Question": "Is  Oxfordshire far away from Kent more than 100km ?",
    "Query": "ASK{ yago:Oxfordshire geo:hasGeometry ?geo . ?geo geo:asWKT ?oxfWKT . yago:Kent geo:hasGeometry ?geo2 . ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?kentWKT . FILTER (geof:distance(?oxfWKT,?kentWKT,uom:metre)>100000.0) . }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "90": {
    "Question": "Is Lough Leane lake in County Kerry ?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:County_Kerry geo:hasGeometry ?kgeo . ?kgeo geo:asWKT ?kWKT . yago:Lough_Leane geo:hasGeometry ?lgeo . ?lgeo geo:asWKT ?lWKT . FILTER (geof:sfWithin(?lWKT,?kWKT)) .  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "91": {
    "Question": "Is Peristeri west of Zografou?",
    "Query": "ASK {         yago:Peristeri geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.         yago:Zografou geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT2.     FILTER(strdf:left(?WKT1, ?WKT2)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "92": {
    "Question": "Do Cambridge and Oxford intersect?",
    "Query": "ASK {         yago:Cambridge geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.         yago:Oxford geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT2.       FILTER(strdf:intersects(?WKT1, ?WKT2)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "93": {
    "Question": "Does County Galway contains Claregalway?",
    "Query": "ASK {     yago:County_Galway geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.     yago:Claregalway geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT2.     FILTER(strdf:contains(?WKT1, ?WKT2)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "94": {
    "Question": "Is Samos west of  Rodos ?",
    "Query": "ASK {    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Samos> geo:hasGeometry ?samos_geo .    ?samos_geo geo:asWKT ?samosWKT .    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rhodes> geo:hasGeometry ?rodos_geo .    ?rodos_geo geo:asWKT ?rodosWKT .    FILTER(strdf:left(?samosWKT,?rodosWKT))  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "95": {
    "Question": "Does Cardiff have common border with Birmingham?",
    "Query": "ASK {    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cardiff> geo:hasGeometry ?cardiff_geo .    ?cardiff_geo geo:asWKT ?cardiff_geoWKT .     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Birmingham> geo:hasGeometry ?birmingham_geo .    ?birmingham_geo geo:asWKT ?birmingham_geoWKT .    FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(?cardiff_geoWKT, ?birmingham_geoWKT))  }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "96": {
    "Question": "Is Mullingar within 70 km of Dublin?",
    "Query": "ASK {    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin> geo:hasGeometry ?dublin_geo .    ?dublin_geo geo:asWKT ?dublin_geoWKT .     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mullingar> geo:hasGeometry ?mullingar_geo .    ?mullingar_geo geo:asWKT ?mullingar_geoWKT .    FILTER(geof:distance(?dublin_geoWKT,?mullingar_geoWKT,uom:metre) <= 70000)  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "97": {
    "Question": "Is Denbighshire located in Wales?",
    "Query": "ASK {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Denbighshire> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wales> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "98": {
    "Question": "Is Dublin at most 210km from Galway County?",
    "Query": "ASK {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Galway> geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(geof:distance(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1,uom:metre) < 210000)  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "99": {
    "Question": "Is Kallithea at the border of Nea Smyrni?",
    "Query": "ASK {  yago:Kallithea geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  yago:Nea_Smyrni geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "100": {
    "Question": "Is the city of Cork located southern of the city of Galway?",
    "Query": "ASK { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cork_City_7778678> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Galway_City_7778676>  geo:hasGeometry ?o1. ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(strdf:below(?geoWKT,?geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "101": {
    "Question": "Is Southampton located south of Oxford?",
    "Query": "ASK { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Southampton> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oxford>  geo:hasGeometry ?o1. ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(strdf:below(?geoWKT,?geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "102": {
    "Question": "Is Agia Paraskevi west of Chalandri?",
    "Query": "ASK { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Agia_Paraskevi> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chalandri> geo:hasGeometry ?o1. ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(strdf:left(?geoWKT,?geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "103": {
    "Question": "Is Delta municipality within Thessaloniki regional unit ?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {   <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gagentity_202> geo:hasGeometry ?gx .  ?gx geo:asWKT ?xWKT .     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Delta,_Thessaloniki> geo:hasGeometry ?gy .  ?gy geo:asWKT ?yWKT .   FILTER(strdf:within( strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>) ))   }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "104": {
    "Question": "Does Essex border Hertfordshire ?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Essex> geo:hasGeometry ?g .  ?g geo:asWKT ?gWKT .   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hertfordshire> geo:hasGeometry ?g1 .  ?g1 geo:asWKT ?g1WKT .  FILTER(strdf:touches( strdf:transform(?gWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?g1WKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>) ))  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "105": {
    "Question": "Is Donegal County north of Wexford ?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Donegal> geo:hasGeometry ?gx .  ?gx geo:asWKT ?xWKT .  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Wexford> geo:hasGeometry ?gy .  ?gy geo:asWKT ?yWKT .   FILTER(strdf:above( strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>) ))    }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "106": {
    "Question": "Is Elafonisos west of Galatsi?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:Elafonisos geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. yago:Galatsi geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type. ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(strdf:left(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "107": {
    "Question": "Is Oxford at most 3km from Cambridge?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:Oxford geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. yago:Cambridge geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type. ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(geof:distance(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1,uom:metre) <= 3000) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "108": {
    "Question": "Does Dublin borders with Clane?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. yago:Clane geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type. ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "109": {
    "Question": "Is  Rhodes west of Patmos?",
    "Query": "ASK {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rhodes> geo:hasGeometry ?geo1 . ?geo1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1 . <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Patmos> geo:hasGeometry ?geo2 . ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2 . FILTER(strdf:left(?wkt1,?wkt2)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "110": {
    "Question": "Is Doolin Below Dublin?",
    "Query": "ASK {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Doolin> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(strdf:below(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "111": {
    "Question": "Is Liverpool east of Adare?",
    "Query": "ASK {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Liverpool> geo:hasGeometry ?o.   ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Adare> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.   ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.   FILTER(strdf:right(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "112": {
    "Question": "Is Sfakia within Scotland?",
    "Query": "ASK {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sfakia> geo:hasGeometry ?o.   ?o geo:asWKT ?pWKT.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Scotland> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.   ?o1 geo:asWKT ?sWKT.   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?pWKT, ?sWKT)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "113": {
    "Question": "Is Belfast close to Edinburgh?",
    "Query": "ASK {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_City_of_Belfast_3333223> geo:hasGeometry ?o.   ?o geo:asWKT ?bWKT.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Edinburgh> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.   ?o1 geo:asWKT ?eWKT.   FILTER(geof:distance(?bWKT, ?eWKT, uom:metre) > 10000) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "114": {
    "Question": "Does Cephissus cross Peristeri?",
    "Query": "ASK{         yago:geoentity_Cephissus_Creek_9073805 geo:hasGeometry ?g.         ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.         yago:Peristeri geo:hasGeometry ?g2.         ?g2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2. FILTER(strdf:crosses(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT2)). }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "115": {
    "Question": "Is Essex above of Kent?",
    "Query": "ASK {       yago:Essex geo:hasGeometry ?g.      ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.      yago:Kent geo:hasGeometry ?g2.      ?g2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2. FILTER(strdf:above(?geoWKT,?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "116": {
    "Question": "Is Ballymoe in the county Longford?",
    "Query": "ASK {                  yago:Ballymoe geo:hasGeometry ?g.         ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.         yago:County_Longford geo:hasGeometry ?g2.         ?g2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT2))  }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "117": {
    "Question": "Is Ierapetra south of Athens?",
    "Query": "ASK {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ierapetra> geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876> geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.     ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.   FILTER (strdf:above(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "118": {
    "Question": "Is Scotland north of London?",
    "Query": "ASK {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Scotland> geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_City_of_London_2643744> geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.     ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.   FILTER (strdf:below(strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "119": {
    "Question": "Is Dublin west of London?",
    "Query": "ASK {    <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gadmentity_Dublin_IRL.6_1> geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_City_of_London_2643744> geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.     ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.   FILTER (strdf:left(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "120": {
    "Question": "Does Bristol Belong to Wales?",
    "Query": "ASK{  yago:Wales geo:hasGeometry ?WalesGeo. ?WalesGeo geo:asWKT ?WalesPolygon.  yago:Bristol geo:hasGeometry ?BristolGeo. ?BristolGeo geo:asWKT ?BristolPolygon.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?BristolGeo , ?WalesGeo)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "121": {
    "Question": "Does Thessaly borders West Macedonia?",
    "Query": "ASK{  yago:geoentity_Western_Macedonia_6697811 geo:hasGeometry ?WestMakGeo. ?WestMakGeo geo:asWKT ?WestMakPolygon.  yago:Thessaly geo:hasGeometry ?ThessGeo. ?ThessGeo geo:asWKT ?ThessPolygon.  FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?WestMakPolygon, ?ThessPolygon)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "122": {
    "Question": "Is the Distance between Bublin and Arklow more than 10km?",
    "Query": "ASK{ yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?DublnGeo. ?DublnGeo geo:asWKT ?DublnPolygon.  yago:Arklow geo:hasGeometry ?Geo. ?Geo geo:asWKT ?Polygon.  FILTER( (geof:distance(?DublnPolygon, ?Polygon, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>))> 10000) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "123": {
    "Question": "Does Kallithea borders Nea Smyrni?",
    "Query": "ASK {            yago:Kallithea  geo:sfTouches yago:Nea_Smyrni . }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "124": {
    "Question": "Is Norwich at least 100 km far from London?",
    "Query": "ASK where {   yago:geoentity_Norwich_District_7290598 geo:hasGeometry ?norwichGeometry .   ?norwichGeometry geo:asWKT ?wktNorwich .   yago:Greater_London geo:hasGeometry ?londonGeometry .   ?londonGeometry geo:asWKT ?wktLondon .   FILTER(geof:distance( strdf:transform(?wktNorwich, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),        strdf:transform(?wktLondon,<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), uom:metre) >= 100000) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "125": {
    "Question": "Is Norilsk north of Dublin?",
    "Query": "Ask where {   yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?dublinGeometry .   ?dublinGeometry geo:asWKT ?wktDublin .   yago:Norilsk geo:hasGeometry ?norilskGeometry .   ?norilskGeometry geo:asWKT ?wktNorilsk .   FILTER(strdf:above(?wktNorilsk , ?wktDublin)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "126": {
    "Question": "Does the Athens municipality touch Kallithea?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876 geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. yago:Kallithea geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type. ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "127": {
    "Question": "Is Manchester within Northwestern European region?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:Manchester geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. y2geor:osentity_North_West_Euro_Region_41431  geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type. ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "128": {
    "Question": "Is Belfast south of Dublin?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:Belfast geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type. ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(strdf:below(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "129": {
    "Question": "Is lake Yliki north of dimos Athens ?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {   yago:Lake_Yliki geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .    yago:geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876 geo:hasGeometry ?yGeom .   ?yGeom geo:asWKT ?yWKT .   FILTER(strdf:above(?xWKT, ?yWKT)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "130": {
    "Question": "Is Limerick close to Waterford?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {    y2geor:gadmentity_Limerick_IRL.13_1 geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .    ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .     y2geor:gadmentity_Waterford_IRL.23_1 geo:hasGeometry ?yGeom .    ?yGeom geo:asWKT ?yWKT .     FILTER(geof:distance(?xWKT, ?yWKT, uom:metre) < 2000 )  }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "131": {
    "Question": "Does Rochdale border Manchester?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {   yago:Metropolitan_Borough_of_Rochdale geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .   yago:Manchester geo:hasGeometry ?yGeom .   ?yGeom geo:asWKT ?yWKT .       FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?xWKT, ?yWKT)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "132": {
    "Question": "Is Nafpaktia west of Athens?",
    "Query": "ASK where {     yago:Nafpaktia geo:hasGeometry ?geomNaf.     ?geomNaf geo:asWKT ?wktNaf.     yago:Athens geo:hasGeometry ?geomAth.     ?geomAth geo:asWKT ?wktAth.     FILTER(strdf:left(?wktNaf, ?wktAth)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "133": {
    "Question": "Is Liverpool south of Wales?",
    "Query": "ASK where {     yago:Liverpool geo:hasGeometry ?geomLiv.     ?geomLiv geo:asWKT ?wktLiv.     yago:Wales geo:hasGeometry ?geomWal.     ?geomWal geo:asWKT ?wktWal.     FILTER(strdf:below(?wktLiv, ?wktWal)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "134": {
    "Question": "Is Scotland north of Dublin?",
    "Query": "ASK where {     yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?geomDub.     ?geomDub geo:asWKT ?wktDub.     yago:Scotland geo:hasGeometry ?geomSco.     ?geomSco geo:asWKT ?wktSco.     FILTER(strdf:above(?wktSco, ?wktDub)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "135": {
    "Question": "Is Thessaly region south of Attica?",
    "Query": "ASK {         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Thessaly> geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Attica_(region)> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.           FILTER(strdf:below(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1))}",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "136": {
    "Question": "Is Plymouth near Cardiff?",
    "Query": "ASK {         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Plymouth>  geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cardiff> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.           FILTER(geof:distance(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1, uom:metre) <=10000) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "137": {
    "Question": "Is Dublin south of Belfast?",
    "Query": "ASK {         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin>  geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_City_of_Belfast_3333223> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.           FILTER(strdf:below(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "138": {
    "Question": "Is Astypalaia within the Aegean?",
    "Query": "ASK {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Astypalaia> geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gadmentity_Aegean_GRC.1_1>  geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.             FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?wkt1,?wkt2)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "139": {
    "Question": "Is the beach Sennen Cove east of Helston?",
    "Query": "ASK {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sennen_Cove> geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.      yago:Helston geo:hasGeometry ?g2.      ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.     FILTER(strdf:right(?wkt1, ?wkt2)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "140": {
    "Question": "Is Howth far from Dublin?",
    "Query": "ASK {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Howth>  geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.     FILTER(geof:distance(?wkt1, ?wkt2, uom:metre) > 5000). }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "141": {
    "Question": "Is Athlone northeast of Portumna?",
    "Query": "ASK WHERE {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Athlone> geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .     ?o2 geo:asWKT ?athloneWKT .      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Portumna> geo:hasGeometry ?o .     ?o geo:asWKT ?portumnaWKT .      FILTER(strdf:right(?athloneWKT, ?portumnaWKT)) .     FILTER(strdf:above(?athloneWKT, ?portumnaWKT)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "142": {
    "Question": "Is Kalamata north of Tripoli?",
    "Query": "ASK WHERE {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Kalamata_8133971> geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .     ?o1 geo:asWKT ?kalamataGeo .      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tripoli,_Greece> geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .     ?o2 geo:asWKT ?tripoliGeo .      FILTER(strdf:above(?kalamataGeo , ?tripoliGeo )) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "143": {
    "Question": "Is Kastanas beach located to the south of Athens?",
    "Query": "ASK{ yago:Athens geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?aWKT. yago:geoentity_Paralía_Kastanás_10277719 geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?kWKT. FILTER(strdf:below(?kWKT, ?aWKT)). }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "144": {
    "Question": "Is Liverpool south of Scotland?",
    "Query": "ASK{ yago:Liverpool geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?lWKT. yago:Scotland geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?sWKT. FILTER(strdf:below(?lWKT, ?sWKT)). }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "145": {
    "Question": "Is Killarney Beach north of Cork?",
    "Query": "ASK{ yago:gadmentity_Cork_IRL.4_1 geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?cWKT. yago:geoentity_Killarney_Beach_8215737 geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?kWKT. FILTER(strdf:above(?kWKT, ?cWKT)). }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "146": {
    "Question": "Is Ierapetra east of Chania?",
    "Query": "ASK {     yago:Ierapetra geo:hasGeometry ?o.     ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT_Ierapetra.      yago:geoentity_Chania_8133762 geo:hasGeometry ?o1.     ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT_Chania.          FILTER(strdf:right(?geoWKT_Ierapetra,?geoWKT_Chania)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "147": {
    "Question": "Is Cambridge south of London?",
    "Query": "ASK {     yago:London geo:hasGeometry ?o.     ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT_London.      yago:Cambridge geo:hasGeometry ?o1.     ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT_Cambridge.          FILTER(strdf:below(?geoWKT_Cambridge,?geoWKT_London)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "148": {
    "Question": "Is County Cavan at the border of Laois county council?",
    "Query": "ASK {     yago:County_Cavan  geo:hasGeometry ?o.     ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT_Cavan.      yago:County_Laois geo:hasGeometry ?o1.     ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT_Laois.          FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?geoWKT_Cavan,?geoWKT_Laois)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "149": {
    "Question": "Is Kinsale city south of Kilkenny city?",
    "Query": "ASK {  yago:Kinsale geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  yago:Kilkenny geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  FILTER(strdf:below(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "150": {
    "Question": "Is Bristol west of Liverpool city?",
    "Query": "ASK {  yago:Bristol geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  yago:Liverpool geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  FILTER(strdf:left(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "151": {
    "Question": "Is Chios east of Paxi island?",
    "Query": "ASK {  yago:Chios geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  yago:Paxi geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2.  FILTER(strdf:right(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "152": {
    "Question": "Is Canada east of China?",
    "Query": "ASK {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Canada> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/China> geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(strdf:right(?geoWKT,?geoWKT) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "153": {
    "Question": "Is Kriti south of Athens?",
    "Query": "ASK {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Crete> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Attica_(region)> geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(strdf:below(?geoWKT,?geoWKT) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "154": {
    "Question": "Is Tullyhaw within Northern Irland?",
    "Query": "ASK {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tully_2635377> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northern_Ireland> geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT,?geoWKT) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "155": {
    "Question": "Is Liverpool around 40 kms of Manchester?",
    "Query": "ASK {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Manchester> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Liverpool> geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(geof:distance(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1,uom:metre) <= 40000 ) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "156": {
    "Question": "Is Athlone north of Kilkenny city?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:Athlone geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. yago:Kilkenny geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(strdf:above(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "157": {
    "Question": "Is Nottingham east of Liverpool?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:Nottingham geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. yago:Liverpool geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(strdf:right(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "158": {
    "Question": "Is Lesbos west of Farsala town?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:Lesbos geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. yago:Chania geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. FILTER(strdf:left(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "159": {
    "Question": "Is Kozani north of Livadeia?",
    "Query": "ASK {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kastoria> geo:hasGeometry ?o.     ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Livadeia> geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type.     ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.     FILTER(strdf:above(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1))}",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "160": {
    "Question": "Is Birmingham west of Leicester?",
    "Query": "ASK {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Birmingham> geo:hasGeometry ?o.     ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Leicester> geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type.     ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.     FILTER(strdf:left(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "161": {
    "Question": "Is Cork City west of Dublin?",
    "Query": "ASK {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cork_City_7778678> geo:hasGeometry ?o.     ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin> geo:hasGeometry ?o1; rdf:type ?type.     ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.     FILTER(strdf:left(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "162": {
    "Question": "Is Chania east of Athens?",
    "Query": "ASK { SELECT ?g1 WHERE{          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Chania_8133762> geo:hasGeometry ?g1.         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876> geo:hasGeometry ?g2.         ?g1 geo:asWKT ?w1.         ?g2 geo:asWKT ?w2.         FILTER(strdf:right(?w1, ?w2)) } }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "163": {
    "Question": "Is the County of Kent west of the County of Norfolk?",
    "Query": "ASK { SELECT ?g1 WHERE{        <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kent> geo:hasGeometry ?g1.         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norfolk> geo:hasGeometry ?g2.         ?g1 geo:asWKT ?w1.         ?g2 geo:asWKT ?w2.         FILTER(strdf:left(?w1, ?w2)) } }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "164": {
    "Question": "Is Ballymoe west of Ratoath?",
    "Query": "ASK { SELECT ?g1 WHERE{    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ballymoe> geo:hasGeometry ?g1.         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ratoath> geo:hasGeometry ?g2.         ?g1 geo:asWKT ?w1.         ?g2 geo:asWKT ?w2.         FILTER(strdf:left(?w1, ?w2)) } }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "165": {
    "Question": "Is Athens south of Manchester?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876 geo:hasGeometry ?geo1 . ?geo1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1 . yago:Manchester geo:hasGeometry ?geo2 . ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2 . FILTER(strdf:below(?wkt1,?wkt2)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "166": {
    "Question": "Is Dublin east of Thessaloniki?",
    "Query": "ASK { ?instance owl:sameAs yago:Dublin; geo:hasGeometry ?geo1 . ?geo1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1 . yago:geoentity_Dimos_Thessaloniki_8133841 geo:hasGeometry ?geo2 . ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2 . FILTER(strdf:right(?wkt1,?wkt2)) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "167": {
    "Question": "Is Suffolk north of Cork county?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:Suffolk geo:hasGeometry ?geo1 . ?geo1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1 . yago:County_Cork geo:hasGeometry ?geo2 . ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2 . FILTER(strdf:above(?wkt1,?wkt2)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "168": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are in Epirus region?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?lake WHERE { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Epirus_(region)> geo:hasGeometry ?geoC . ?geoC geo:asWKT ?cWKT . ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake . ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?geoL . ?geoL geo:asWKT ?lWKT . FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?cWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Límni_Ziroú_251199 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Límni_Zaravínas_252498"
  },
  "169": {
    "Question": "Which streams cross Oxfordshire?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?stream WHERE { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oxfordshire> geo:hasGeometry ?geoC . ?geoC geo:asWKT ?cWKT . ?stream rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream . ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?geoL . ?geoL geo:asWKT ?lWKT . FILTER(geof:sfCrosses(?lWKT, ?cWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Leach"
  },
  "170": {
    "Question": "Which county councils border County Mayo?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?county WHERE { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Mayo> geo:hasGeometry ?geo1 . ?geo1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 . ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council . ?county geo:hasGeometry ?geo2 . ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 . FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Roscommon http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Sligo http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Galway_City_7778676"
  },
  "171": {
    "Question": "Which Municipalities border with Moschato Tavros?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?municipality WHERE {         yago:Moschato-Tavros geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.          ?municipality rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.          FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:buffer(?WKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": "municipality http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Piraeus http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kallithea http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Aigaleo_8133973 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nikaia-Agios_Ioannis_Rentis"
  },
  "172": {
    "Question": "Which District Wards are within Essex?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?districtWard WHERE{         yago:Essex geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.         ?districtWard rdf:type y2geoo:OS_DistrictWard;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.         FILTER(geof:sfWithin(strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT, 0, uom:metre)))  }",
    "Answer": "districtWard http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Coggeshall http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Rural_North_Ward_19812 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Gosfield_&_Greenstead_Green_Ward_19862 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Bocking_Blackwater_Ward_41998 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_The_Colnes_Ward_19840 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Braintree_Central_&_Beckers_Green_Ward_19900 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kelvedon http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Bocking_North_Ward_19887 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Silver_End_&_Cressing_Ward_19799 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Trinity_Ward_19664 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hullbridge http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Downhall_&_Rawreth_Ward_19665 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Sweyne_Park_&_Grange_Ward_41773 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Wheatley_Ward_19716 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hockley http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hawkwell http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Lodge_Ward_19669 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Roche_South_Ward_19477 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Clavering,_Essex http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Stanway,_Essex http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Prettygate_Ward_19591 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Shrub_End_Ward_19592 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Lexden_&_Braiswick_Ward_19815 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Stour_Valley_North_Ward_19880 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Boreham_and_The_Leighs_Ward_19789 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Springfield_North_Ward_19790 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Chelmer_Village_and_Beaulieu_Park_Ward_19788 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Felsted http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Little_Baddow,_Danbury_and_Sandon_Ward_19727 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Broomfield_and_The_Walthams_Ward_19919 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hatfield_Peverel http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._George's_Ward_19710 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Appleton_Ward_19712 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._Peter's_Ward_19715 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Pitsea_South_East_Ward_19657 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Maylandsea http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tillingham http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Southminster http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Althorne http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wivenhoe http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Ardleigh_and_Little_Bromley_Ward_19587 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Mersea_&_Pyefleet_Ward_44698 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Greenstead_Ward_19822 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Thorrington,_Frating,_Elmstead_and_Great_Bromley_Ward_19585 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Wickford_Park_Ward_41790 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rettendon http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/South_Hanningfield http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Witham http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wickham_Bishops http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Witham_West_Ward_19695 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Littlebury,_Chesterford_&_Wenden_Lofts_Ward_20133 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ashen,_Essex http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Sumners_and_Kingsmoor_Ward_20068 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Broadley_Common,_Epping_Upland_and_Nazeing_Ward_20055 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Hastingwood,_Matching_and_Sheering_Village_Ward_41782 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Staple_Tye_Ward_20067 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Great_Parndon_Ward_20069 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_South_Woodham-Chetwood_and_Collingwood_Ward_19676 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Purleigh_7293530 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Marks_Tey http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Maldon_West_Ward_19685 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tolleshunt_Major http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Maldon_North_Ward_41975 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Heybridge_West_Ward_19621 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_South_Weald_Ward_19940 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Manningtree,_Mistley,_Little_Bentley_and_Tendring_Ward_19543 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lawford http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Great_Bentley http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Vange_Ward_19659 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._Bartholomews_Ward_19512 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tiptree http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Flitch_Green http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Great_Dunmow_South_&_Barnston_Ward_20006 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Stort_Valley_Ward_20090 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Moreton_and_Fyfield_Ward_20017 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Passingford_Ward_20021 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Brizes_and_Doddinghurst_Ward_19990 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Chipping_Ongar,_Greensted_and_Marden_Ash_Ward_19965 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_Weald_Bassett http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Shelley_Ward_19970 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Three_Fields_Ward_19910 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Bumpstead_Ward_20100 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Yeldham_Ward_19882 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Mile_End_Ward_19819 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Highwoods_Ward_41765 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._James_Ward_19528 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Rush_Green_Ward_19527 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Alton_Park_Ward_42009 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Debden_&_Wimbish_Ward_20107 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Takeley http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Thaxted_&_the_Eastons_Ward_20000 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Elsenham http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Bicknacre_and_East_and_West_Hanningfield_Ward_19720 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Billericay http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Epping_Upland http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Theydon_Garnon http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hatfield_Heath http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Foulness_&_The_Wakerings_Ward_19438 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Roche_North_&_Rural_Ward_19671 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Maldon_7293529 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Maldon_South_Ward_19623 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Heybridge_7293525 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Pier_Ward_42010 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._Marys_Ward_19510 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Brightlingsea http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Burstead_Ward_19737 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ingatestone_and_Fryerning_7298519 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Billericay_West_Ward_19767 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Golf_Green_Ward_19509 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._Osyth_and_Point_Clear_Ward_19530 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Bockings_Elm_Ward_19526 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Great_and_Little_Oakley_Ward_19549 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Beaumont_and_Thorpe_Ward_19539 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Canvey_Island_North_Ward_19466 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._James_Ward_19662 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Canvey_Island_East_Ward_19456 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Canvey_Island_Winter_Gardens_Ward_19458 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Canvey_Island http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Laindon_Park_Ward_19741 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Tipps_Cross_Ward_41762 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Grange_Hill_Ward_19962 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Chigwell_Village_Ward_19964 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Loughton_Forest_Ward_19955 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chigwell http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Waltham_Abbey_High_Beach_Ward_20061 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Harwich_West_Central_Ward_19551 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Harwich_East_Central_Ward_19555 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_New_Town_&_Christ_Church_Ward_41767 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Little_Parndon_and_Hare_Street_Ward_20084 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Toddbrook_Ward_20054 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Stansted_Mountfitchet_7292044 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Warley_Ward_19938 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_The_Sampfords_Ward_20093 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Wickford_North_Ward_19643 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Trinity_Ward_19787 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_High_Easter_&_the_Rodings_Ward_20008 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Writtle http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_High_Ongar,_Willingale_and_The_Rodings_Ward_19989 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Great_Baddow http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Moulsham_and_Central_Ward_19732 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Waterhouse_Farm_Ward_19730 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Wickford_Castledon_Ward_19645 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Patching_Hall_Ward_19781 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Great_Baddow_West_Ward_19722 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_South_Woodham-Elmwood_and_Woodville_Ward_19674 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._Andrews_Ward_19924 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_The_Lawns_Ward_19786 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Moulsham_Lodge_Ward_19733 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Goat_Hall_Ward_19734 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Peter_Bruff_Ward_42011 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._Johns_Ward_19514 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Haven_Ward_19515 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Bradfield,_Wrabness_and_Wix_Ward_19562 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Little_Clacton_and_Weeley_Ward_19523 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Holland_and_Kirby_Ward_19522 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._Anne's_&_St._John's_Ward_19590 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ramsey_and_Parkeston_7298549 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Alresford,_Essex http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Harwich_East_Ward_19554 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Walton_Ward_19517 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Homelands_Ward_42008 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Frinton_and_Walton_2649050 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Stour_Valley_South_Ward_19851 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Braintree_West_Ward_19902 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tollesbury http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Loughton_Broadway_Ward_19953 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Church_Langley_Ward_20073 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Galleywood http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Mark_Hall_Ward_20074 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Harlow_Common_Ward_20083 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Bush_Fair_Ward_20081 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Hutton_East_Ward_19772 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Shenfield_Ward_19986 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Hutton_North_Ward_19769 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Great_Totham http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lambourne http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Saffron_Walden_Castle_Ward_20111 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Crouch_Ward_41788 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Herongate_and_Ingrave_7300507 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Fryerns_Ward_19738 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._Pauls_Ward_19511 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Lower_Nazeing_Ward_20065 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Roydon,_Essex http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Waltham_Abbey_North_East_Ward_20064 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Brentwood_West_Ward_19939 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Chelmsford_Rural_West_Ward_19933 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Witham_South_Ward_19696 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Loughton http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Buckhurst_Hill http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Buckhurst_Hill_East_Ward_19959 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Loughton_Alderton_Ward_41784 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Halstead_St._Andrew's_Ward_19860 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Halstead http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rayne,_Essex http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Stansted_South_&_Birchanger_Ward_20047 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Broad_Oak_&_the_Hallingburys_Ward_20032 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Hutton_Central_Ward_41763 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Burnham-on-Crouch http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Newport,_Essex http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Saffron_Walden_Audley_Ward_20114 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Hockley_&_Ashingdon_Ward_19636 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Braintree_South_Ward_41997 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Berechurch_Ward_19595 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Nethermayne_Ward_19740 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Loughton_Fairmead_Ward_20059 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Waltham_Abbey_Honey_Lane_Ward_41785 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Brentwood_North_Ward_19976 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Burrsville_Ward_42007 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Hamford_Ward_42012 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Witham_North_Ward_19693 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Brentwood_South_Ward_19977 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Hutton_South_Ward_19771 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Loughton_St._John's_Ward_19957 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Loughton_St._Mary's_Ward_19954 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Bocking_South_Ward_19890 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Castle_Ward_19597 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Pitsea_North_West_Ward_19709 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Netteswell_Ward_20078 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sible_Hedingham http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Cedar_Hall_Ward_19713 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Victoria_Ward_19663 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Boyce_Ward_19460 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Langdon_Hills_Ward_19743 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Waltham_Abbey_South_West_Ward_20089 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Epping_Lindsey_and_Thornwood_Common_Ward_41783 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Waltham_Abbey_(parish) http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._Mary's_Ward_19462 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Hawkwell_East_Ward_41774 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Canvey_Island_West_Ward_19465 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Great_Notley_&_Black_Notley_Ward_19889 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Lower_Sheering_Ward_20026 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Old_Harlow_Ward_20076 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Pilgrims_Hatch_Ward_19974 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Harwich_West_Ward_19550 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_St._Martin's_Ward_41789 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Saffron_Walden_Shire_Ward_20105 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Lee_Chapel_North_Ward_19742 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Burnham-on-Crouch_North_Ward_19490 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Marconi_Ward_19784 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Canvey_Island_South_Ward_19467 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Old_Heath_&_The_Hythe_Ward_19567 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Great_Dunmow"
  },
  "173": {
    "Question": "Which Forests are less than 25km far away from County Sligo?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?forest WHERE{         yago:County_Sligo geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.         ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.         FILTER(geof:distance(?WKT, ?WKT1, uom:metre) < 25000) }",
    "Answer": "forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Slish_Wood_2961420"
  },
  "174": {
    "Question": "Which parks are in Liverpool?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?park where {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Liverpool>     <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.     ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park .     ?park <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT))  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rice_Lake_Recreational_Ground_10244496 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Stanley_Park,_Liverpool http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Walton_Hall_Park_10244527 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sefton_Park"
  },
  "175": {
    "Question": "Which bays are at most 5000 meters from Doolin?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?bay where {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Doolin>     <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.     ?bay rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_bay .     ?bay <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.     FILTER (geof:distance(?lcnWKT, ?lWKT, uom:metre)<5000). }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Galway_Bay"
  },
  "176": {
    "Question": "Which beaches are near Mykonos?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?beach where {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mykonos>     <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.     ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach .     ?beach <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.     FILTER (geof:distance(?lcnWKT, ?lWKT, uom:metre)<2000). }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ágios_Sóstis_11552847 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Liá_8128533"
  },
  "177": {
    "Question": "Which regional units border regional unit of Thessaly?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?rg where  { yago:Thessaly geo:hasGeometry ?tgeo . ?tgeo geo:asWKT ?tWKT . ?rg rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_RegionalUnit . ?rg geo:hasGeometry ?rggeo . ?rggeo geo:asWKT ?rgWKT . FILTER (strdf:touches(?rgWKT,?tWKT)) . }",
    "Answer": "rg http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Central_Greece_(region) http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Central_Macedonia http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Western_Greece_6697810 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Western_Macedonia_6697811"
  },
  "178": {
    "Question": "Which Metropolitan Districts border Manchester ?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?Mdistrict WHERE { yago:Manchester geo:hasGeometry ?egeo . ?egeo geo:asWKT ?eWKT . ?Mdistrict rdf:type y2geoo:OS_MetropolitanDistrict . ?Mdistrict geo:hasGeometry ?cgeo . ?cgeo geo:asWKT ?cWKT . FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?eWKT,?cWKT)) . }",
    "Answer": "Mdistrict http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/City_of_Salford http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Borough_of_Oldham http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Trafford http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Borough_of_Rochdale http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Borough_of_Bury http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tameside http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Borough_of_Stockport"
  },
  "179": {
    "Question": "Which canals cross Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?canal WHERE { yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?dgeo . ?dgeo geo:asWKT ?dWKT .  ?canal rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal . ?canal geo:hasGeometry ?pgeo . ?pgeo geo:asWKT ?pWKT . FILTER(strdf:crosses(?dWKT,?pWKT)) . }",
    "Answer": "canal http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Royal_Canal"
  },
  "180": {
    "Question": "Which Municipalities intersect with Periferiaki Enotita Perios?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?municipality WHERE {      yago:geoentity_Perifereiakí_Enótita_Peiraiós_8200486 geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.      ?municipality rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality.      ?municipality geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT2.      FILTER(strdf:intersects(strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Piraeus http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Keratsini-Drapetsona http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Chaidari_8133972 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Korydallos http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Aigaleo_8133973 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Perama http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Agia_Varvara http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Moschato-Tavros http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nikaia-Agios_Ioannis_Rentis"
  },
  "181": {
    "Question": "Which forests are in Cambridge?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?forest WHERE {      yago:Cambridge geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.     ?forest rdf:type  y2geoo:OSM_forest.      ?forest geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT2.     FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hayley_Wood"
  },
  "182": {
    "Question": "Which Townlands border Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?townland  WHERE {      yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.      ?townland rdf:type  y2geoo:OSI_Townland.     ?townland geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT2.     FILTER(strdf:touches(strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Belcamp_3315308 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE1962A036013A3E055000000000001 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE1962A04A513A3E055000000000001 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE1962A087313A3E055000000000001 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE1962A081C13A3E055000000000001 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE1962A084113A3E055000000000001 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE1962A064813A3E055000000000001 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE1962A044913A3E055000000000001"
  },
  "183": {
    "Question": "Does Corfu have any beaches?",
    "Query": "ASK {    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Corfu_8133855> geo:hasGeometry ?corfu_geo .    ?corfu_geo geo:asWKT ?corfu_geoWKT .    ?beach rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_beach> .    ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?geomL .    ?geomL geo:asWKT ?fWKT.    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?fWKT, ?corfu_geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "184": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are within 50km of Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT  distinct ?lake  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin> geo:hasGeometry ?dublin_geo .   ?dublin_geo geo:asWKT ?dublin_geoWKT .   ?lake rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_lake> .   ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?lake_geo .   ?lake_geo geo:asWKT ?lake_geoWKT .   FILTER(geof:distance(?dublin_geoWKT,?lake_geoWKT,uom:metre) <= 50000)   }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lough_Dan  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Nahanagan_2962320  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Ouler_3315103  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Arts_Lough_3315033  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lough_Tay  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cleevaun_Lough_3315106  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kelly’s_Lough_3315032  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Firrib_3315037"
  },
  "185": {
    "Question": "Which Unitary Authorities have common borders with Cardiff?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?order3neighbour  WHERE {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cardiff> geo:hasGeometry ?cardiff_geo .    ?cardiff_geo geo:asWKT ?cardiff_geoWKT .  ?order3neighbour rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_UnitaryAuthority> .  ?order3neighbour geo:hasGeometry ?order3neighbourgeo .  ?order3neighbourgeo geo:asWKT ?order3neighbourgeoWKT .  FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?cardiff_geoWKT,?order3neighbourgeoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rhondda_Cynon_Taf  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Vale_of_Glamorgan  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Newport_3333246  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Caerphilly_County_Borough  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bristol"
  },
  "186": {
    "Question": "Which parks are at most 10km from Westminster?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?park where{  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/City_of_Westminster> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.   ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park; geo:hasGeometry ?geomC.  ?geomC geo:asWKT ?geoWKTr.   FILTER(geof:distance(?geoWKT,?geoWKTr,uom:metre) < 10000)  }",
    "Answer": "park http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hampstead_Heath http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cranmer_Green_9883935 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Old_Deer_Park_10377300 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kew_Green_9884145 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Clapton_Park_2652946 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Postman's_Park_6956840 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Richmond_Park http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kennington_Park_10346778 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Springfield_Park_(London) http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hyde_Park,_London http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lincolns_Inn_Fields_2644485 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Wandworth_Park_9884531 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Battersea_Park_10377298 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Terrace_Gardens_11395387 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Peckham_Rye_Park_6547119 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cator_Park_7667957 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Regent's_Park http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Beckenham_Place_Park http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Green_Park http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Woodside_Park_9255415 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Greenwich_Park"
  },
  "187": {
    "Question": "Which rural areas border Castleblayney?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?rural_area where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Castleblayney> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcWKT.  ?rural_area rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_Rural_Area>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?lcWKT, ?cWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "rural_area_name MONAGHAN RURAL AREA@en CLONES No.1 RURAL AREA@en CARRICKMACROSS RURAL AREA@en MONAGHAN RURAL AREA CLONES No.1 RURAL AREA CARRICKMACROSS RURAL AREA"
  },
  "188": {
    "Question": "Which villages are located in Thessaly?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?village where{  ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village .  ?village geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.   yago:Thessaly geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": "village        http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oichalia,_Trikala         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Makrinitsa         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Alonissos_265263         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Portaria         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kallithéa_261405         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kalochóri_261376         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Gerakári_251424         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Synoikismós_Prosfýgon_253799         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Níki_256420         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Aetólofos_265683         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Xynóvrysi_251510         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Krókion_258752         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Sotírio_253458         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Omorfochóri_256297         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Amygdaliá_265176         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Anávra_265094         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cheimádio_253449         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Anatolí_265106         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Stagiátes_253219         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Sklíthro_253592         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Akhíllio_8581472         http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Stomio,_Larissa"
  },
  "189": {
    "Question": "Which 3rd order administrative units border Hampshire?",
    "Query": "Select distinct ?city  Where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hampshire> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  ?city rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/GADM_3rdOrder_AdministrativeUnit>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT. FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:transform(?geoWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?cWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": "city http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Portsmouth http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/West_Berkshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/West_Sussex http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Southampton http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wiltshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Wokingham_3333221 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bracknell_Forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dorset http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey"
  },
  "190": {
    "Question": "Which county councils border the city of  Cork?",
    "Query": "Select distinct ?CountryCouncil Where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cork_City_7778678> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  ?CountryCouncil rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT. FILTER(strdf:touches(strdf:transform(?geoWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?cWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Tipperary http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Kerry"
  },
  "191": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities border Agia Paraskevi?",
    "Query": "Select distinct ?dimos  Where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Agia_Paraskevi> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  ?dimos rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT. FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:transform(?geoWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/2100>), strdf:transform(?cWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/2100>))) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Paiania  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Papagou-Cholargos_8133839  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chalandri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pallini"
  },
  "192": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities does the Central Athens Regional Unit contain ?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?y  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Perifereiakí_Enótita_Kentrikoú_Toméa_Athinón_8200482>  geo:hasGeometry ?gx .  ?gx geo:asWKT ?xWKT .     ?y a y2geoo:GAG_Municipality . ?y geo:hasGeometry ?gy .  ?gy geo:asWKT ?yWKT .   FILTER(strdf:contains( strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>) )) }",
    "Answer": "m_name ΔΗΜΟΣ ΚΑΙΣΑΡΙΑΝΗΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΓΑΛΑΤΣΙΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΖΩΓΡΑΦΟΥ"
  },
  "193": {
    "Question": "Which districts border Greater London Authority ?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?x  WHERE {   ?x a y2geoo:OS_District. ?x geo:hasGeometry ?g .  ?g geo:asWKT ?gWKT .   ?y a y2geoo:OS_GreaterLondonAuthority.  ?y geo:hasGeometry ?g1 .  ?g1 geo:asWKT ?g1WKT .    ?y geo:sfTouches ?x.   }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Borough_of_Brentwood  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Bucks_District_7290659  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Epping_Forest_District_7290543  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tandridge_District_7290643  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Reigate_and_Banstead_District_2639505  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Welwyn_Hatfield  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hertsmere  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Sevenoaks_District_6945814  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Borough_of_Broxbourne  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mole_Valley  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Epsom_and_Ewell_District_7290639  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Three_Rivers_2635925  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Elmbridge_District_2650079  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Spelthorne_District_7290642  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Borough_of_Dartford_6945813"
  },
  "194": {
    "Question": "Which counties are west of County Wexford ?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?x  WHERE {   ?x a y2geoo:OSI_County_Council . ?x geo:hasGeometry ?gx .  ?gx geo:asWKT ?xWKT .  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Wexford> geo:hasGeometry ?gy .  ?gy geo:asWKT ?yWKT .   FILTER(strdf:left( strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>) ))    }",
    "Answer": "county_name ROSCOMMON COUNTY COUNCIL@en ROSCOMMON COUNTY COUNCIL SLIGO COUNTY COUNCIL@en SLIGO COUNTY COUNCIL MAYO COUNTY COUNCIL@en MAYO COUNTY COUNCIL CORK COUNTY COUNCIL@en CORK COUNTY COUNCIL LEITRIM COUNTY COUNCIL@en LEITRIM COUNTY COUNCIL LONGFORD COUNTY COUNCIL@en LONGFORD COUNTY COUNCIL TIPPERARY COUNTY COUNCIL@en TIPPERARY COUNTY COUNCIL GALWAY COUNTY COUNCIL@en GALWAY COUNTY COUNCIL KERRY COUNTY COUNCIL@en KERRY COUNTY COUNCIL CLARE COUNTY COUNCIL@en CLARE COUNTY COUNCIL"
  },
  "195": {
    "Question": "Is Dublin located on an island?",
    "Query": "ASK { ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island. ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom. ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT. yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom. ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT. FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(?iWKT,?xWKT)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "196": {
    "Question": "Which beaches are near by Naxos?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?beach where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Naxos> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach . ?beach <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER (geof:distance(?lcnWKT, ?lWKT, uom:metre)<2000). }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mikri_Vigla_-Southern_bay_(Limanaki)_6942749 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Orkos_bay_7731772 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Plaka_beach_6942748 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kastraki_beach_6942750"
  },
  "197": {
    "Question": "Which parks are in Manchester?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?park where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Manchester> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park . ?park <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT))  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ordsall_Park_9884111 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_The_Meadow_9884109"
  },
  "198": {
    "Question": "Which bays are near Doolin?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?bay where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Doolin> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?bay rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_bay . ?bay <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER (geof:distance(?lcnWKT, ?lWKT, uom:metre)<5000). }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Galway_Bay"
  },
  "199": {
    "Question": "Which counties are at the border of county Lincolnshire?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lincolnshire> geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC.   ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcWKT.   ?county rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_County>;   geo:hasGeometry ?geomC.   ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT.   FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:transform(?lcWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),   strdf:transform(?cWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)))  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cambridge http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nottinghamshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Leicestershire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norfolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northamptonshire"
  },
  "200": {
    "Question": "Which parks are in Greece?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?p WHERE {   ?p rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park;   geo:hasGeometry ?o.   ?o geo:asWKT ?pWKT.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Greece> geo:hasGeometry ?g.   ?g geo:asWKT ?gWKT.   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?pWKT, ?gWKT)). }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Alsos_Pagkratiou_10345875 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Pedío_Áreos_11057595 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Filopappou_Hill_10345876 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/National_Garden,_Athens http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Attikó_Álsos_9036476 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tináneios_Kípos_9062348 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Parko_Iroon_10345877"
  },
  "201": {
    "Question": "Which islands are north of Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?p WHERE {   ?p rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island;   geo:hasGeometry ?o.   ?o geo:asWKT ?bWKT.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin> geo:hasGeometry ?g.   ?g geo:asWKT ?dWKT.   FILTER(strdf:above(?bWKT, ?dWKT)). }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Anisor_661168 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Brusen_3332259 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kalkskär_654753 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_San_Adrian_Island_5556965 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Anderholmarna_3332361 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Killingen_3329833 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Strupö_2671202 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Andholmen_3328694 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Sollerøya,store_3136329 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Brännskäret_3232227 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Granö_2711146 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Trutgrund_10073157 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ostrov_Firnleya-Yuzhnyy_2012788 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Saltö …"
  },
  "202": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities border Athens?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?municipality WHERE {         yago:geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876 geo:hasGeometry ?g.         ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.         ?municipality rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality.         ?municipality geo:hasGeometry ?g2.         ?g2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2.   FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": "municipality_name ΔΗΜΟΣ ΖΩΓΡΑΦΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΒΥΡΩΝΟΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΑΙΓΑΛΕΩ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΝΕΑΣ ΙΩΝΙΑΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΦΙΛΟΘΕΗΣ - ΨΥΧΙΚΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΔΑΦΝΗΣ - ΥΜΗΤΤΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΠΑΠΑΓΟΥ - ΧΟΛΑΡΓΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΜΟΣΧΑΤΟΥ - ΤΑΥΡΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΑΓΙΩΝ ΑΝΑΡΓΥΡΩΝ - ΚΑΜΑΤΕΡΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΚΑΙΣΑΡΙΑΝΗΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΝΕΑΣ ΣΜΥΡΝΗΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΚΑΛΛΙΘΕΑΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΦΙΛΑΔΕΛΦΕΙΑΣ - ΧΑΛΚΗΔΟΝΟΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΠΕΡΙΣΤΕΡΙΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΓΑΛΑΤΣΙΟΥ"
  },
  "203": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are in Oxford?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?lake WHERE {  yago:Oxford geo:hasGeometry ?g.         ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.         ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake.         ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?g2.         ?lake geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT2, )) }",
    "Answer": "lake"
  },
  "204": {
    "Question": "Which counties councils intersects the Lough Neagh lake?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?county WHERE{  ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council.  ?county geo:hasGeometry ?cg.  ?cg geo:asWKT ?cgeoWKT.  yago:Lough_Neagh geo:hasGeometry ?g.  ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. FILTER(strdf:intersects(?lgeoWKT, ?geoWKT)). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "205": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities are east of Ierapetra?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x  where{     ?x y2geoo:hasGADM_Description Dímos.    ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ierapetra> geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.     ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.  FILTER (strdf:right(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": "n Λειψών Καρπάθου Leros@en Didymoteicho@en Σάμου Kasos@en Nisyros@en Πάτμου Oinousses@en Karpathos@en Αγαθονησίου Kos@en Fournoi Korseon@en Διδυμοτείχου Αστυπαλαίας Ρόδου Κω Καλυμνίων Τήλου Οινουσσών Chalki@en Leipsoi@en Κάσου Λέρου Tilos@en Φούρνων Κορσεών Νισύρου Patmos@en Χάλκης Rhodos@en Samos@en Agathonisi@en Kalymnos@en Σύμης Astypalaia@en Symi@en"
  },
  "206": {
    "Question": "Which Metropolitan Boroughs are north of London?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?n where{      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_City_of_London_2643744>  geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.       ?y y2geoo:hasGADM_Description MetropolitanBorough.     ?y geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.   ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.      FILTER (strdf:above(strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": "n Gateshead@en Doncaster@en Kirklees@en Rotherham@en Oldham@en Barnsley@en Sandwell@en Tameside@en Solihull@en Trafford@en Calderdale@en Bolton@en Knowsley@en Sefton@en Wirral@en Saint Helens@en Rochdale@en Walsall@en North Tyneside@en Stockport@en Wolverhampton@en Dudley@en Bury@en Wigan@en South Tyneside@en"
  },
  "207": {
    "Question": "Which civil parishes border the Kilkieran?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?n where{      ?x a y2geoo:OSI_Civil_Parish.     ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.    ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.        <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kilkieran_3302356>  geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.     ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.  FILTER(strdf:touches(strdf:buffer(?xWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?yWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>)))  }",
    "Answer": "n WELLS DUNLECKNY@en WELLS@en DUNLECKNY"
  },
  "208": {
    "Question": "Which Metropolitan districts border Birmingham?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?Metropol_District WHERE{ yago:Birmingham geo:sfTouches ?Metropol_District.  ?Metropol_District rdf:type y2geoo:OS_MetropolitanDistrict. }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sandwell http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Borough_of_Solihull http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Borough_of_Dudley http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Borough_of_Walsall"
  },
  "209": {
    "Question": "Which countries are north of Ireland",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?Country WHERE { ?Country rdf:type y2geoo:GADM_1stOrder_AdministrativeUnit. ?Country geo:hasGeometry ?CountryGeo. ?CountryGeo geo:asWKT ?CountryGeometry.  yago:Republic_of_Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?IrelandGeo. ?IrelandGeo geo:asWKT ?IrelandGeometry.  FILTER(strdf:above(?CountryGeometry,?IrelandGeometry)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Finland  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Faroe_Islands_2622320 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Estonia http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Latvia http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norway http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Iceland  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gadmentity_Svalbard_and_Jan_Mayen_SJM http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Åland_Islands"
  },
  "210": {
    "Question": "Give me some lakes of United Kingdom.",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?x WHERE {  ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake. ?x geo:hasGeometry ?GeoX. ?GeoX geo:asWKT ?PolygonX.  yago:United_Kingdom geo:hasGeometry ?GeoY. ?GeoY geo:asWKT ?PolygonY  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?PolygonX, ?PolygonY))  }limit 10",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Whitlingham_Great_Broad_10103843  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Llyn_Cwmffynnon_7534672 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hollingworth_Lake http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Shepherds_9613021 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Llyn_Idwahttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Llangorse_Lake http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Llyn_Dinas .…. …. …. …. …. …. …. …."
  },
  "211": {
    "Question": "which beaches are near to Nea Smirni?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?x WHERE{  ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach. ?x geo:hasGeometry ?beachGeo. ?beachGeo geo:asWKT ?beachPolygon .  yago:Nea_Smyrni geo:hasGeometry ?NsGeo. ?NsGeo geo:asWKT ?NsGeometry.  FILTER (geof:distance(?NsGeometry, ?beachPolygon , <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>) < 30000 ) . }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Erotospiliá_9036772 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Paralía_Freattydos_9062351 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Plaz_Votsalákia_9062352"
  },
  "212": {
    "Question": "Which are the municipalities that Athens borders with?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?x1 {            ?x1 a y2geoo:GAG_Municipality .           ?x1 geo:hasGeometry ?geometry .   ?geometry geo:asWKT ?x1WKT .    yago:geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876 geo:hasGeometry ?athensGeo .   ?athensGeo geo:asWKT ?athWKT .      FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:buffer(?x1WKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?athWKT, 0, uom:metre))). }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Papagou-Cholargos_8133839 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Galatsi http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Galatsi http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Agioi_Anargyroi-Kamatero_8133819 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Agioi_Anargyroi-Kamatero_8133819 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Filothei-Psychiko http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nea_Ionia http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nea_Ionia http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Filadelfeia-Chalkidona http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dafni-Ymittos http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kallithea http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kallithea http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Vyronas_8133859 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Vyronas_8133859 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Zografou http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Zografou http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nea_Smyrni http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nea_Smyrni http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Aigaleo_8133973 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Aigaleo_8133973 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Moschato-Tavros http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kaisariani http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kaisariani http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Peristeri http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Peristeri"
  },
  "213": {
    "Question": "Which are the cities near Greater London?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?city where {   ?city a y2geoo:GADM_4thOrder_AdministrativeUnit .   ?city geo:hasGeometry ?cityGeometry .   ?cityGeometry geo:asWKT ?wktCity .   yago:Greater_London geo:hasGeometry ?londonGeometry .   ?londonGeometry geo:asWKT ?wktLondon .   FILTER(geof:distance(strdf:buffer(?wktCity,0,uom:metre),strdf:buffer(?wktLondon,0,uom:metre), uom:metre) <= 5000) }",
    "Answer": "Endpoint didn't bring results before resetting the connection."
  },
  "214": {
    "Question": "Which are the cities north of Dublin?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?citiesAbove where {   yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?dublinGeometry .   ?dublinGeometry geo:asWKT ?wktDublin .    ?citiesAbove a y2geoo:OSM_city .   ?citiesAbove geo:hasGeometry ?citiesAboveGeometry .   ?citiesAboveGeometry geo:asWKT ?wktCitiesAbove .    FILTER(strdf:above(?wktCitiesAbove , ?wktDublin)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Zelenograd http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Unalaska,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Deering,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nuiqsut,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norilsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Angoon,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nome,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Alakanuk,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nizhnevartovsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nikolai,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Elim,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Novy_Urengoy http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ambler,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Scammon_Bay,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kenai,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/St._George,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Seldovia,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Thorne_Bay,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Grodno_628096 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pilot_Point,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Selawik,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dimitrovgrad,_Russia http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chefornak,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Voskresensk,_Moscow_Oblast http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Homer,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lower_Kalskag,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Omsktselinstroy_7553845 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Valdez,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Oborino_6266900 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Point_Hope,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Uzlovaya http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pilot_Station,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ouzinkie,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lida_626081 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Aleknagik,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Togiak,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Old_Kasaan_5556175 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Zlatoust http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Naberezhnye_Chelny http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ruby,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Votkinsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Podolsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Serov_1492664 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chuathbaluk,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Põhja-Tallinn http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kobuk,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Napakiak,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/False_Pass,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Noorvik,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Houston,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hooper_Bay,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kolpino,_Saint_Petersburg http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Balashikha http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Koyuk,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Orekhovo-Zuyevo http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Chashkintsy_467386 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Petrogradka_8504948 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Anaktuvuk_Pass,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nizhnekamsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Galena,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kalskag_5865719 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Nunachuk_5870494 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Port_Heiden,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kielerkamp_2891112 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Shchyolkovo http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Unalakleet,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hydaburg,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nightmute,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Craig,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sterlitamak http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Noginsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dolgoprudny http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Koyukuk,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/St._Paul,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Velikiye_Luki http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wales,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Khimki http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Grayling,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kivalina,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Shageluk,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kirovo-Chepetsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bethel,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Atqasuk,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Murom http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Emmonak,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Shungnak,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Obninsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Coffman_Cove,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Domodedovo_(town) http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sarapul http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Platinum,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Serpukhov http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wasilla,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Neftekamsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Larsen_Bay,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Navapolatsk_624784 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kupreanof,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Borovsk_572069 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Port_Alexander,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Korolyov,_Moscow_Oblast http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Goodnews_Bay,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tanana,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cordova,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Brevig_Mission,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cold_Bay,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Teller,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chevak,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Zhukovsky,_Moscow_Oblast http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Stuyahok,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Eek,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/St._Mary's,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hoonah,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Toksook_Bay,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wrangell,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Whittier,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Berdsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Akutan,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Vorkuta http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dillingham,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Noyabrsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Pushkino_503978 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Arzamas http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_McMurray http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wainwright,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lübsee_2875564 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tobolsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lyubertsy http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cherepovets http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nulato,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ekwok,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Miass http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Golovin,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Saxman,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Gambell,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nenana,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Oktjabrski_6198442 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Old_Harbor,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Thompson,_Manitoba http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kolomna http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Clark's_Point,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nefteyugansk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kovrov http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Huslia,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tolyatti http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kamensk-Uralsky http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Manokotak,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Anderson,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Seversk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Quinhagak,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hughes,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Newhalen,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dzerzhinsk,_Russia http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Holy_Cross,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kopeysk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Flin_Flon http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kwethluk,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Abakanets_1512234 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Glazov http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nizhny_Tagil http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bettles,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Novokuznetsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chignik_Lagoon,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Soldotna,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tenakee_Springs,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nondalton,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Elektrostal http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kotlik,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Almetyevsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Gustavus_5846871 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Anvik,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kaktovik,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Klawock,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Buckland,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pervouralsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nunam_Iqua,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/St._Michael,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Akhiok,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Egegik,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Allakaket,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kake,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_King_Cove_5866308 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Shishmaref,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kaltag,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kiana,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Prokopyevsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mountain_Village,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Odintsovo http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rybinsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surgut http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kodiak_Station,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_Pole,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Novocheboksarsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Severodvinsk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Stebbins,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sergiyev_Posad http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ivan’kovo_6423391 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Achinsk_Pervyy_1512162 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Moose_Creek_5878682 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Marshall,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Zelenograd http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Russian_Mission,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mekoryuk,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pelican,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Krasnogorsk,_Moscow_Oblast http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Napaskiak,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Akiak,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Savoonga,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/McGrath,_Alaska http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mytishchi http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Novomoskovsk,_Russia"
  },
  "215": {
    "Question": "Which are all the parks in Dublin?",
    "Query": "select distinct  ?park where { yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park; geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "park http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/St_Stephen's_Green http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ringsend_Park_3289060"
  },
  "216": {
    "Question": "Which are the District Wards which have north of them Manchester?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?District_Ward where { yago:Manchester geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcWKT. ?District_Ward rdf:type y2geoo:OS_DistrictWard; geo:hasGeometry ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT. FILTER(strdf:above(?lcWKT, ?cWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "District_Ward http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Chapel_West_Ward_13803 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Chapel_West_Ward_13803 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Halmerend_Ward_15159 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Halmerend_Ward_15159 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Beare_Green_Ward_13916 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Beare_Green_Ward_13916 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Castle_Ward_18458 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Castle_Ward_18458 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Ely_West_Ward_1225 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Ely_West_Ward_1225 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Fetcham_East_Ward_13938 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Fetcham_East_Ward_13938 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Ilfracombe_West_Ward_23092 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Ilfracombe_West_Ward_23092 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Central_Ward_16248 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Central_Ward_16248 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Park_Farm_North_Ward_18072 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Park_Farm_North_Ward_18072 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Thames_Ditton_Ward_13959"
  },
  "217": {
    "Question": "Which regional units border regional unit of Thessaloniki?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?neighboring WHERE {   y2geor:gagentity_202 geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .    ?neighboring a y2geoo:GAG_RegionalUnit .   ?neighboring geo:hasGeometry ?yGeom .  ?yGeom geo:asWKT ?yWKT .    FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:buffer(?xWKT,0,uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?yWKT ,0,uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": "http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gagentity_204  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gagentity_203  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gagentity_207  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gagentity_201  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gagentity_206"
  },
  "218": {
    "Question": "Which 2nd Order Administrative Units border Dublin ?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?adm WHERE {   y2geor:gadmentity_Dublin_IRL.6_1 geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .    ?adm a y2geoo:GADM_2ndOrder_AdministrativeUnit .   ?adm geo:hasGeometry ?yGeom .   ?yGeom geo:asWKT ?yWKT .    FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?xWKT, ?yWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gadmentity_Meath_IRL.17_1  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gadmentity_Kildare_IRL.9_1  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gadmentity_Wicklow_IRL.26_1"
  },
  "219": {
    "Question": "Which streams are inside Greater London?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?stream  WHERE {   yago:Greater_London geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom.   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT . ?stream a yago:OSM_stream. ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?yGeom.   ?yGeom geo:asWKT ?yWKT .   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?yWKT, ?xWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "in file"
  },
  "220": {
    "Question": "Which cities are in Attica?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?county where {     yago:Attica_(region) geo:hasGeometry ?geomAtt.     ?geomAtt geo:asWKT ?wktIre.     ?city rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_city ;     geo:hasGeometry ?geomC.     ?geomC geo:asWKT ?wktC.     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?wktC, ?wktAtt)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "221": {
    "Question": "Which counties border county Essex?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?county where {     yago:Essex geo:hasGeometry ?geomEss.     ?geomEss geo:asWKT ?wktEss.     ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OS_County; geo:hasGeometry ?geomC.     ?geomC geo:asWKT ?wktC.     FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?wktEss, ?wktC)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cambridge  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hertfordshire"
  },
  "222": {
    "Question": "Which county councils are in Ireland?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?county where {     yago:Republic_of_Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?geomIre.     ?geomIre geo:asWKT ?wktIre.     ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council; geo:hasGeometry ?geomC.     ?geomC geo:asWKT ?wktC.     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?wktC, ?wktIre)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Laois  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Roscommon  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Kildare  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kilkenny  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Longford  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Tipperary  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Westmeath  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Offaly  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Dublin_7288565  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Carlow"
  },
  "223": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities are in Ipiros region?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?municipality WHERE {   ?municipality a y2geoo:GAG_Municipality.  ?municipality geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.         ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Epirus_(region)>    geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.          ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT))}",
    "Answer": "name ΔΗΜΟΣ ΙΩΑΝΝΙΤΩΝ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΙΩΑΝΝΙΤΩΝ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΗΓΟΥΜΕΝΙΤΣΗΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΜΕΤΣΟΒΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΖΑΓΟΡΙΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΚΕΝΤΡΙΚΩΝ ΤΖΟΥΜΕΡΚΩΝ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΓΕΩΡΓΙΟΥ ΚΑΡΑΪΣΚΑΚΗ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΚΟΝΙΤΣΑΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΖΗΡΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΖΗΡΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΠΡΕΒΕΖΗΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΠΑΡΓΑΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΑΡΤΑΙΩΝ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΦΙΛΙΑΤΩΝ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΖΙΤΣΑΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΖΙΤΣΑΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΒΟΡΕΙΩΝ ΤΖΟΥΜΕΡΚΩΝ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΔΩΔΩΝΗΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΔΩΔΩΝΗΣ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΝΙΚΟΛΑΟΥ ΣΚΟΥΦΑ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΣΟΥΛΙΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΣΟΥΛΙΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΠΩΓΩΝΙΟΥ"
  },
  "224": {
    "Question": "Which districts borders Greater London authority?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?district WHERE {   ?district a y2geoo:OS_District. ?district geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.         ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Greater_London>    geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.          ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.   FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT))}",
    "Answer": "name Tandridge District South Bucks District Epsom and Ewell District (B) Elmbridge District (B) Hertsmere District (B) Welwyn Hatfield District (B) Spelthorne District (B) Brentwood District (B) Sevenoaks District Dartford District (B) Broxbourne District (B) Reigate and Banstead District (B) Three Rivers District Epping Forest District Mole Valley District"
  },
  "225": {
    "Question": "Which are the wards that comprise of City Belfast?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?ward WHERE {   ?ward a y2geoo:OSNI_Ward. ?ward geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.         ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_City_of_Belfast_3333223>    geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.          ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT))}",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Balmoral_(District_Electoral_Area)  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Windsor_2633841  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ballymacarret_2656496  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Beltoy_2655931  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Legoniel_2644670  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_BEERSBRIDGE_N08000308  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_LADYBROOK_N08000334  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_BALLYMURPHY_N08000305  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_FORTH_RIVER_N08000327  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_CAVEHILL_N08000314  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_SANDOWN_N08000346  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_KNOCK_N08000333  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_TWINBROOK_N08000355  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_SHANKILL_N08000348  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_MUSGRAVE_N08000339  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_INNISFAYLE_N08000332  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_TURF_LODGE_N08000354  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_ANDERSONSTOWN_N08000301  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_CLONARD_N08000318  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_STRANMILLIS_N08000352  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_NEW_LODGE_N08000340  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_FORTWILLIAM_N08000328  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_ARDOYNE_N08000302  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_CONNSWATER_N08000320  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_MEROK_N08000338  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_BLACKSTAFF_N08000312  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_WOODVALE_N08000360  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_BEECHMOUNT_N08000307  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_CLIFTONVILLE_N08000317  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_MALONE_N08000337  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_BALLYSILLAN_N08000306  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_FALLS_N08000324  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_BLOOMFIELD_N08000313  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_FALLS_PARK_N08000325  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_SHAW'S_ROAD_N08000349  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_WATER_WORKS_N08000357  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_CENTRAL_N08000315  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_WOODSTOCK_N08000359  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_CHICHESTER_PARK_N08000316  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_STEWARTSTOWN_N08000350  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_RAVENHILL_N08000344  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_ORANGEFIELD_N08000341  http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_ORMEAU_N08000342"
  },
  "226": {
    "Question": "Is there a stream near Greenwich?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?stream WHERE {    ?stream a y2geoo:OSM_stream. ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.         ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Greenwich_3333147> geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.         ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.   FILTER(geof:distance(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT, uom:metre) < 100000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "227": {
    "Question": "Find beaches intersects with Alonnisos?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?beach  WHERE {     ?beach a y2geoo:OSM_beach.     ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Alonnisos_8133938> geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.     FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(?wkt1, ?wkt2)) }`",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Megáli_Ámmos_11498184 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Megáli_Ámmos_11498184 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Leftó_Gyalós_11498191 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Glýfa_11498170 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tourkonéri_11498183 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tourkonéri_11498183 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Vamvakiés_11498165 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ágios_Pétros_11498179 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Vrysítsa_11498198 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Vrysítsa_11498198 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Strovíli_11498148 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Spartínes_11498213 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Miliá_11498207 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Gyaliá_11498200 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Gyaliá_11498200 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kalýva_Stamatíou_11498150 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Chrysí_Miliá_11498208 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Megálos_Mourtiás_11498224 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tsoukália_11498196 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tsoukália_11498196 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rousoúm_Gyalós_11498228 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mourtítsa_11498151 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kalývia_Alexíou_11498166 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mikrós_Mourtiás_11498223 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Výthisma_11498225"
  },
  "228": {
    "Question": "What other counties are there near Nottingham?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?shire  WHERE {     yago:Nottinghamshire geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     ?shire a y2geoo:OS_County.     ?shire geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.     FILTER(          ?shire != yago:Nottinghamshire  &&         (geof:distance(?wkt1, ?wkt2, uom:metre) < 3000 )) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Leicestershire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Derbyshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lincolnshire"
  },
  "229": {
    "Question": "What villages are within 100 km from Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?village  WHERE {     ?village a y2geoo:OSM_village.     ?village geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.     FILTER( geof:distance(?wkt2, ?wkt1, uom:metre) < 100000 ) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Spink,_County_Laois http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Daingean http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rathangan,_County_Kildare http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Clogh_3308007 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_The_Swan_7870941"
  },
  "230": {
    "Question": "Does Worcestershire County have any parks?",
    "Query": "ASK WHERE {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Worcestershire>  geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?countyGeo .          ?park a y2geoo:OSM_park .         ?park geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .         ?o2 geo:asWKT ?parkGeo .       FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?parkGeo , ?countyGeo)) }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "231": {
    "Question": "In which barony is Coolea townsland?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?barony  WHERE {     yago:geoentity_Coolea_3300151 geo:hasGeometry ?o .     ?o geo:asWKT ?cooleaGeo .      ?barony a y2geoo:OSI_Barony . ?barony geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .     ?o2 geo:asWKT ?baronyGeo .      FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cooleaGeo , ?baronyGeo ))  }",
    "Answer": "BARRYMORE@en BARRYMORE BARRYMORE@en BARRYMORE"
  },
  "232": {
    "Question": "Which is the lake in Kilkis?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?lake WHERE {    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Kilkis_8133969> geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .    ?o1 geo:asWKT ?munGeo .     ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake .    ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .    ?o2 geo:asWKT ?lakeWKT .     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lakeWKT , ?munGeo)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Pikrolímni_734646"
  },
  "233": {
    "Question": "Which are the districts that border Copeland district?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?district WHERE {  ?district a y2geoo:OS_District .         ?district geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?districtGeo .          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Copeland_District_7290665> geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .         ?o2 geo:asWKT ?copelandGeo .          FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?copelandGeo, ?districtGeo)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Borough_of_Barrow-in-Furness http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Allerdale_District_7290662 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Lakeland_District_7290667 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Allerdale_District_7290662 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Lakeland_District_7290667 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Borough_of_Barrow-in-Furness"
  },
  "234": {
    "Question": "Which forests are in a 10km radius from Kastanas beach?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?forest WHERE{  yago:geoentity_Paralía_Kastanás_10277719 geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?kWKT.  ?forest a y2geoo:OSM_forest;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?fWKT.   FILTER(strdf:distance(?kWKT, ?fWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>) < 10000).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "235": {
    "Question": "Show me the parks of Liverpool",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?park WHERE{  yago:Liverpool geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?lWKT.  ?park a y2geoo:OSM_park;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?pWKT .   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?pWKT, ?lWKT)). }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rice_Lake_Recreational_Ground_10244496  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Walton_Hall_Park_10244527  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sefton_Park  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Stanley_Park,_Liverpool"
  },
  "236": {
    "Question": "Which streams intersect with Cork?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?stream WHERE{  y2geor:gadmentity_Cork_IRL.4_1 geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?cWKT.  ?stream a y2geoo:OSM_stream;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?sWKT .   FILTER(strdf:intersect(?sWKT, ?cWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "237": {
    "Question": "Which regions are within Greece?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?region  where {     yagok:Greece geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.      ?region rdf:type yagoo:GAG_Region;     geo:hasGeometry ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.      FILTER(strdf:within( strdf:transform(?lWKT,<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),                           strdf:transform(?lcnWKT,<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)))  }",
    "Answer": "region http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Crete http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Attica_(region) http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Peloponnese_(region)"
  },
  "238": {
    "Question": "Which are the forests of England?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?forest  where {     yagok:England geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.      ?forest rdf:type yagoo:OSM_forest;     geo:hasGeometry ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.      FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT))  }",
    "Answer": "forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Saham_Wood_9539000 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mulgrave_Woods_2641993 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Pedlars_Wood_9883765 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Saint_Leonards_Forest_2638755 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Park_Wood_9884080 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kelham_Hills_2645869 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Epping_Forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Hurst_Wood_11071822 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Old_Park_wood_9884706 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Shepherds_Grove_2638042 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Shenley_Wood_8410933 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Holkham_Meals_2646756 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Savernake_Forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hayley_Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Stanton_Wood_8410938 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Greaves's_Wood_9884520 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wayland_Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Clayton_Wood_10245306 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Eight_Acre_Copse_9538943 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Spring_Wood_10245313 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_New_Barn_Wood_9694433 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lovel_Wood_2643551 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Furze_Woods_9973408 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wyre_Forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Paddock_Wood_10109427 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rough_Wood_9884527 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Sandall_Beat_Wood_2638605 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Millisons_Wood_2642509 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Parsonage_Wood_10377846 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bedgebury_Forest"
  },
  "239": {
    "Question": "What parks are in Dublin?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?park  where {     yagok:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.      ?park rdf:type yagoo:OSM_park;     geo:hasGeometry ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.      FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT))  }",
    "Answer": "park http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/St_Stephen's_Green http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ringsend_Park_3289060"
  },
  "240": {
    "Question": "Which counties border Donegal county?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?county WHERE {  yago:County_Donegal geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council .  ?county geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  FILTER(strdf:touches(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": "county http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Leitrim"
  },
  "241": {
    "Question": "Which districts border Warwickshire district?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?district WHERE {  yago:Warwickshire geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?district rdf:type y2geoo:OS_District .  ?district geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  FILTER(strdf:touches(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": "district http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Wychavon_District_7290658 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cherwell_District http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cotswold_District_7290549 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bromsgrove_District http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lichfield_District_7290628 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Hinckley_and_Bosworth_District_7290586 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Daventry_District_7290601 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_West_Oxfordshire_District_7290622 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Redditch_District_7290656 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Blaby_District http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tamworth_District_7290632 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Harborough_District_7290585 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Northamptonshire_District_7290604 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_West_Leicestershire"
  },
  "242": {
    "Question": "Which regions border Central Macedonia region?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?region WHERE {  yago:Central_Macedonia geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?region rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Region .  ?region geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  FILTER(strdf:touches(?geoWKT1, strdf:buffer(?geoWKT2, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": "region http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Thessaly http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Western_Macedonia_6697811"
  },
  "243": {
    "Question": "Which country contains Clondankil ?",
    "Query": "Select  distinct ?region where { yago:Clondalkin geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom. ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT.  ?region rdf:type y2geoo:GADM_1stOrder_AdministrativeUnit  . ?region geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom. ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT. FILTER(geof:sfContains(?xWKT, ?iWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Republic_of_Ireland"
  },
  "244": {
    "Question": "Which are the lakes inside Central Macedonia ?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?lake WHERE{     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Central_Macedonia> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  ?lake <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#type> <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_lake>. ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT1,?geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "245": {
    "Question": "Which parks are within 10km radius in Liverpool ?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?park WHERE{     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Liverpool> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  ?park <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#type> <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_park>.  ?park geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT1,?geoWKT) && geof:distance(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1,uom:metre) <= 10000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "246": {
    "Question": "Which district borders with the Stafford district.",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?district where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Stafford_District_7290631> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcWKT. ?district rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_District>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT. FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?lcWKT, ?cWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "Newcastle-under-Lyme@en Cannock Chase@en South Staffordshire@en Lichfield@en East Staffordshire@en Staffordshire Moorlands@en"
  },
  "247": {
    "Question": "Which counties border County Clare ?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?county WHERE {  yago:County_Clare geo:hasGeometry ?o . ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT .  ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council; geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  FILTER(strdf:touches(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": "county http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Tipperary http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Kerry"
  },
  "248": {
    "Question": "Which districts border Wakefield district?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?district WHERE { yago:City_of_Wakefield geo:hasGeometry ?o . ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . ?district rdf:type y2geoo:OS_District; geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 . FILTER(strdf:touches(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": "district http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Selby_District"
  },
  "249": {
    "Question": "Which regions border Thessaly region?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?region WHERE { yago:Thessaly geo:hasGeometry ?o . ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . ?region rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Region; geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 . FILTER(strdf:touches(?geoWKT, strdf:buffer(?geoWKT1, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": "region http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Central_Greece_(region) http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Central_Macedonia http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Western_Greece_6697810 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Western_Macedonia_6697811"
  },
  "250": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities border municipality of Athens?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?municipality where {  yago:geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876  geo:sfTouches ?municipality.  ?municipality rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality .}",
    "Answer": "municipality http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Galatsi http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Agioi_Anargyroi-Kamatero_8133819 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nea_Ionia http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kallithea http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Vyronas_8133859 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Zografou http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nea_Smyrni http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Aigaleo_8133973 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kaisariani http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Peristeri"
  },
  "251": {
    "Question": "Which metropolitan districts border Liverpool?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?metrdist where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Liverpool> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC.  ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcWKT.  ?metrdist  rdf:type  <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_MetropolitanDistrict>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry>  ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?lcWKT, ?cWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "metrdist http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Borough_of_Sefton http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Borough_of_Knowsley http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Borough_of_Wirral"
  },
  "252": {
    "Question": "Which baronies border Ardee?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?barony where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ardee> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC.  ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcWKT.  ?barony rdf:type  <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_Barony>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry>  ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?lcWKT, ?cWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "barony http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Louth,_County_Louth http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ferrard_Cross_3316431 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE1962910F213A3E055000000000001 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE1962910FF13A3E055000000000001"
  },
  "253": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities border Chania?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?y WHERE{         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Chania_8133762> geo:sfTouches ?y.  }",
    "Answer": "ΔΗΜΟΣ ΑΠΟΚΟΡΩΝΟΥ ΔΗΜΟΣ ΠΛΑΤΑΝΙΑ"
  },
  "254": {
    "Question": "Which forests are contained in the Norfolk?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?l WHERE {    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norfolk> geo:hasGeometry ?mg .    ?mg geo:asWKT ?mw .     ?l a y2geoo:OSM_forest .    ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .    ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .   FILTER(geof:sfContains(?mw,?lw)) }",
    "Answer": "Saham Wood Holkham Meals, Open Access Wayland Wood"
  },
  "255": {
    "Question": "Which forests are contained in the barony of Coshlea?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?l WHERE {    <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629112213A3E055000000000001> geo:hasGeometry ?mg .    ?mg geo:asWKT ?mw .     ?l a y2geoo:OSM_forest .    ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .    ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .     FILTER(geof:sfContains(?mw,?lw)) }",
    "Answer": "Green Wood"
  },
  "256": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities border Municipality of Makrakomi?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Makrakomi> geo:hasGeometry ?geo1. ?geo1 geo:asWKT ?g1wkt. ?x rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/GAG_Municipality>; geo:hasGeometry ?geo2. ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?g2wkt.  FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?g1wkt,?g2wkt)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dorida  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Lamia_8133738  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Karpenisi_8133731  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nafpaktia  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Domokos_8133737  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Sofades_8133794  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Delphi_8133744"
  },
  "257": {
    "Question": "Which counties border the County of Durham?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?place2 { yago:County_Durham geo:sfTouches ?place2. ?place2 rdf:type y2geo:GADM_3rdOrder_AdministrativeUnit.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Hartlepool_3333152  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/City_of_Sunderland  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Stockton-on-Tees_3333203  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Borough_of_Gateshead  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cumbria  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northumberland  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_Yorkshire  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Borough_of_Darlington"
  },
  "258": {
    "Question": "Which county councils border the County of Meath?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?place2 where {                  yago:County_Meath geo:sfTouches ?place2.                 ?place2 rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_County_Council>. }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Kildare  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fingal  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Monaghan  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Offaly  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Louth"
  },
  "259": {
    "Question": "Which streams are near villages in Central Greece?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?stream WHERE { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Central_Greece_(region)> geo:hasGeometry ?geoC . ?geoC geo:asWKT ?cWKT . ?vill rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village . ?vill geo:hasGeometry ?geoL . ?geoL geo:asWKT ?lWKT . ?stream rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream . ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?geoS . ?geoS geo:asWKT ?sWKT . FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?cWKT)  && geof:distance(?lWKT, ?sWKT, uom:metre) < 10000) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Karpenisiótis_Potamós_260890 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lepianítis_Réma_258494 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Frangistanórrema_262248"
  },
  "260": {
    "Question": "Which villages are near forests in Wales?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?vill WHERE { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wales> geo:hasGeometry ?geoC . ?geoC geo:asWKT ?cWKT . ?vill rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village . ?vill geo:hasGeometry ?geoL . ?geoL geo:asWKT ?lWKT . ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest . ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?geoF . ?geoF geo:asWKT ?fWKT . FILTER( geof:sfWithin(?fWKT, ?cWKT) && geof:distance(?lWKT, ?fWKT, uom:metre) < 10000) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bryncethin http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/St_Brides_Major"
  },
  "261": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are near streams in County Mayo?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?lake WHERE { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Mayo> geo:hasGeometry ?geoC . ?geoC geo:asWKT ?cWKT . ?stream rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream . ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?geoS . ?geoS geo:asWKT ?sWKT . ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake . ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?geoL . ?geoL geo:asWKT ?lWKT . FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?sWKT, ?cWKT) && geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?cWKT) && geof:distance(?lWKT, ?sWKT, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Navroony_10129916 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Corryloughaphuill_Lough_3315714 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Dahybaun_2964896 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Scardaun_Lough_3316015 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Adanacleveen_3316021 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_More_2962528 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lough_Carra http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Creggan_Lough_10130145 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Corranabinna_Lough_3315713 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Skahaghadrantan_10129919 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Knappaghmore_Lough_10130137 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Anaffrin_3315704 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Doo_3315929 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Prospect_Lough_10130258 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Fadda_3315732 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Moher_Lough_2962571 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ballynacorrick_Lough_10130148 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Derrintaggart_Lough_3315734 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Ellinore_10129917 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Drumderg_3316023 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lough_Feeagh http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Bunaveela_Lough_3316010 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Nalaghan_3316009 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Carrowmore_Lake_2965679 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Doo_3315764 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Knappaghbeg_Lough_10130147 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Killadangan_Lough_10130257 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Cuagh_3316179 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Namara_3316013 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Gall_3315698 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lough_Pollagowly_10129918 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Furnace_Lough_2964199"
  },
  "262": {
    "Question": "Which beaches are less than 5km far from any lagoon that intersects with Dimos Milos?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?beach WHERE {         yago:geoentity_Dimos_Milos_8133681 geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.           ?lagoon rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lagoon;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.           FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(strdf:buffer(?WKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre)))          ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach;         geo:hasGeometry ?o2.         ?o2 geo:asWKT ?WKT2.           FILTER(geof:distance(?WKT2, ?WKT1, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": "beach http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Paralía_Achivadólimnis_9383287 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Fatoúrena_9612206 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lagkáda_9383293"
  },
  "263": {
    "Question": "Which cities contain forests that are not more than 50km far from Oxford?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?city WHERE {         yago:Oxford geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.           ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.                      ?city rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_city;         geo:hasGeometry ?o2.         ?o2 geo:asWKT ?WKT2.    FILTER(geof:distance(?WKT, ?WKT2, uom:metre) < 50000)        FILTER(geof:sfContains(strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": "city http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/London_Colney"
  },
  "264": {
    "Question": "Which bays intersect with counties that border with County Mayo?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?bay WHERE{         yago:County_Mayo geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.         ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.         FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:buffer(?WKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre)))          ?bay rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_bay;         geo:hasGeometry ?o2.         ?o2 geo:asWKT ?WKT2.         FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre)))  }",
    "Answer": "bay http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Killary_Bay_Little_2963369 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sligo_Bay http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Donegal_Bay http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mannin_Bay_2962711 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Galway_Bay http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumcliff_Bay_2964617 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cashla_Bay_2965657 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Killala_Bay http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ballysadare_Bay_2966413"
  },
  "265": {
    "Question": "Which canals are at most 10000 metres from towns in Birmingham?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?canal WHERE {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Birmingham>     <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?cWKT.     ?canal rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal .     ?canal <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geoPrk.     ?geoPrk geo:asWKT ?canalWKT.     ?town rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_town .     ?town <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?townWKT.     FILTER (geof:sfWithin(?townWKT, ?cWKT) && geof:distance(?townWKT, ?canalWKT, uom:metre)<10000) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Worcester_and_Birmingham_Canal_2633562 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Coventry_Canal_2652220 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Birmingham_and_Fazeley_Canal_2655602"
  },
  "266": {
    "Question": "Which bays are at most 5000 meters from parks in Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?bay WHERE {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin>     <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?cWKT.     ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park .     ?park <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geoPrk.     ?geoPrk geo:asWKT ?parkWKT.     ?bay rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_bay .     ?bay <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?bayWKT.     FILTER (geof:sfWithin(?parkWKT, ?cWKT) && geof:distance(?bayWKT, ?parkWKT, uom:metre)<5000) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin_Bay"
  },
  "267": {
    "Question": "Which beaches are at most 10000 meters from villages in Corfu Island?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?beach where {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Corfu>     <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?cWKT.     ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach .     ?beach <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?beaWKT.     ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village .     ?village <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geoVillage.     ?geoVillage geo:asWKT ?vilWKT.     FILTER (geof:sfWithin(?vilWKT, ?cWKT) && geof:distance(?vilWKT, ?beaWKT, uom:metre)<10000). }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Paramonas_Beach_8643068  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Myrtiotissa_6695193"
  },
  "268": {
    "Question": "Which streams cross the municipalities that are located in the interior region of Thessaly?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?county ?stream WHERE {  yago:Thessaly geo:hasGeometry ?lgeo . ?lgeo geo:asWKT ?lWKT .  ?county rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality. ?county geo:hasGeometry ?geo . ?geo geo:asWKT ?WKT .  ?stream rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream . ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?sgeo . ?sgeo geo:asWKT ?sWKT .  FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:transform(?WKT,<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),strdf:transform(?lWKT,<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))). FILTER (strdf:crosses(strdf:transform(?WKT,<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),strdf:transform(?sWKT,<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) . }",
    "Answer": "stream  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mavronéri_257531  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cholórrema_259948  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cholórrema_259948 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Karitsiótis_Réma_260924  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kerasiótiko_Réma_260222 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kerasiótiko_Réma_260222"
  },
  "269": {
    "Question": "Which streams cross the counties that border Cumbria ?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?stream  WHERE {  yago:Cumbria geo:hasGeometry ?lgeo . ?lgeo geo:asWKT ?lWKT . ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OS_County. ?county geo:hasGeometry ?geo . ?geo geo:asWKT ?WKT . ?stream rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream . ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?sgeo . ?sgeo geo:asWKT ?sWKT . FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?lWKT,?WKT)). FILTER (strdf:crosses(?WKT,?sWKT)) . }",
    "Answer": "stream http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Leck_Beck http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Foss http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Keer http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tosside_Beck_2635617 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Roxby_Beck_2639030"
  },
  "270": {
    "Question": "Which streams cross the county councils that border County Longford?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?stream  WHERE {  yago:County_Longford geo:hasGeometry ?lgeo . ?lgeo geo:asWKT ?lWKT . ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council. ?county geo:hasGeometry ?geo . ?geo geo:asWKT ?WKT . ?stream rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream . ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?sgeo . ?sgeo geo:asWKT ?sWKT . FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?lWKT,?WKT)). FILTER (strdf:crosses(?WKT,?sWKT)) . }",
    "Answer": "stream  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tang_River_2961275"
  },
  "271": {
    "Question": "Which bays are near a reservoir in Marathon?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?bay WHERE {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Marathon,_Greece> geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.     ?reservoir rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_reservoir.     ?reservoir geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT  ?WKT2.     FILTER(strdf:intersects(strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre))).     ?bay rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_bay.     ?bay geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT  ?WKT3.     FILTER(geof:distance(?WKT2, ?WKT3, uom:metre) < 50000) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Órmos_Paloukíon_255962 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Órmos_Anavýssou_265099 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Órmos_Falírou_262518"
  },
  "272": {
    "Question": "Which canals are near a beach in Edinburgh?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?canal WHERE{     yago:Edinburgh geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.     ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach.     ?beach  geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT  ?WKT2.     FILTER(strdf:intersects(strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre)))     ?canal rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal.     ?canal geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT  ?WKT3.     FILTER(geof:distance(?WKT2, ?WKT3, uom:metre) < 6000) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Union_Canal_(Scotland)"
  },
  "273": {
    "Question": "Which localities are in a town that intersect with County Roscommon?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?locality WHERE{     yago:County_Roscommon geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.     ?town rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_town.     ?town geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT  ?WKT2.     FILTER(strdf:intersects(strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre)))     ?locality rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_locality.     ?locality geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT  ?WKT3.     FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:buffer(?WKT3, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Clerragh_3310822 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Derreenannagh_3310848 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Carrickadraan_3310827 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tullytawen_3310825 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Derreenargan_3310839 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Greagh_3310833 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Moyoran_3310844 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tumna_3310852 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Clooncoose_3310847 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mullaun_3310828 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Corglass_3310826 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumbrick_3310845"
  },
  "274": {
    "Question": "Which districts of Suffolk have forests within?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?district ?nature_reserve  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk> geo:hasGeometry ?Suffolk_geo .   ?Suffolk_geo geo:asWKT ?Suffolk_geoWKT .   ?district rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_District> .   ?district geo:hasGeometry ?district_geo .  ?district_geo geo:asWKT ?district_geoWKT .      FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?district_geoWKT,?Suffolk_geoWKT))      ?nature_reserve rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_forest> .   ?nature_reserve geo:hasGeometry ?nature_reserve_geo .   ?nature_reserve_geo geo:asWKT ?nature_reserve_geoWKT.     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?nature_reserve_geoWKT,?district_geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_St._Edmundsbury_District_7290636 Shepherd's Grove"
  },
  "275": {
    "Question": "Which Irish counties that border the Kildare County intersect canals?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?county ?nature_reserve WHERE {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Kildare> geo:hasGeometry ?kildare_geo .  ?kildare_geo geo:asWKT ?kildare_geoWKT .   ?county rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_County_Council> .  ?county geo:hasGeometry ?county_geo .  ?county_geo geo:asWKT ?county_geoWKT .     FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?county_geoWKT,?kildare_geoWKT))   ?nature_reserve rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_canal> .   ?nature_reserve geo:hasGeometry ?nature_reserve_geo .  ?nature_reserve_geo geo:asWKT ?nature_reserve_geoWKT .    FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(?nature_reserve_geoWKT,?county_geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "<http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fingal>  Royal Canal"
  },
  "276": {
    "Question": "Which beaches are within a Civil Parish in England?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?beach where{  ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach .  ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.   ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OS_CivilParish.  ?x geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT1))   yago:England geo:hasGeometry ?oen.  ?oen geo:asWKT ?geoWKToen.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT, ?geoWKToen)) }",
    "Answer": "beach http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Hemmick_Beach_11103023 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Porthgwarra_Beach_11103037"
  },
  "277": {
    "Question": "Which forests intersect with rural areas in Ireland?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?forest where{  ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_Rural_Area .  ?x geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.   ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest .  ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1. yago:Republic_of_Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?i. ?i geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2.   FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT) && FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT,?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": "forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dromana_Forest_2964656 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rehill_Wood_3300935 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Killoughrum_Forest_2963306 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Slish_Wood_2961420 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ballyhourigan_Wood_3306377 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dromillihy_Wood_3296408 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rossmore_Forest_Park_3310609 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tombrick_Wood_3302725 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Boolymore_Wood_3292169 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Carrigatubbria_Wood_3301991 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ballykeefe_Wood_3307085 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Corbally_Wood_3301995 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Scaragh_Wood_3301000 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mountshannon_Woods_3308263 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cratloe_Woods_3310154 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Curraghbinny_Wood_3286433 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Shirsheen_Wood_3304996 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rossacroonaloo_Wood_3290556 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Glengarra_Wood_3300941 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Green_Wood_3300824 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ballyteage_Wood_3314940 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Clonad_Wood_3313803 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Grove_Wood_3306793 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drum_Wood_3306106 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Unugh_Wood_3295240 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumingall_Wood_3304889 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Glenbower_Wood_3299791 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ballyreagh_Wood_3315175 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Roddenagh_Wood_3304967"
  },
  "278": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities intersect with parks in Perifereiakí Enotita Kentrikou Tomea Athinon?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?m where {  ?m rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality ;  geo:hasGeometry ?om . ?om geo:asWKT ?geoWKTm.   yago:geoentity_Perifereiakí_Enótita_Kentrikoú_Toméa_Athinón_8200482 geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.   ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park; geo:hasGeometry ?geomP.  ?geomP geo:asWKT ?geoWKTP.   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKTm, ?geoWKT1))  FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(?geoWKTP, ?geoWKTm)) }",
    "Answer": "mName ΔΗΜΟΣ ΓΑΛΑΤΣΙΟΥ"
  },
  "279": {
    "Question": "Which county council boarding the city of Cork contains the biggest lake?",
    "Query": "Select  DISTINCT  ?County_Council  ?lake (strdf:area(?B) AS ?biggest_lake) Where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cork_City_7778678> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?A.  ?County_Council rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_County_Council>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?C.   ?lake rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_lake>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomB. ?geomB geo:asWKT ?B.   FILTER(strdf:touches(strdf:transform(?C, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?A, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))).  FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:transform(?B, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?C, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))).  }   ORDERBY DESC (?biggest_lake) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Kerry"
  },
  "280": {
    "Question": "Which district wards are within districts in Cambridge ?",
    "Query": "Select distinct ?DistrictWard Where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cambridge> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?coun. ?coun geo:asWKT ?C.  ?District rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_District>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?A.  ?DistrictWard rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_DistrictWard>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geom. ?geom geo:asWKT ?B.  FILTER (strdf:within(strdf:transform(?B, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?A, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)))  FILTER (strdf:within(strdf:transform(?A, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?C, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)))   }",
    "Answer": "District DistrictWard http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Cambridgeshire_District_7290661 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Milton_7297803 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Cambridgeshire_District_7290661 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Melbourn http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Cambridgeshire_District_7290661 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Fulbourn_7298846 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Cambridgeshire_District_7290661 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Barton_7292934 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Cambridgeshire_District_7290661 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Papworth_Everard_7301653 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Cambridgeshire_District_7290661 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Duxford_7298340 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Cambridgeshire_District_7290661 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Swavesey_7298864 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Huntingdonshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Brampton_7299841 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Huntingdonshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_St._Neots_7298797 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Cambridgeshire_District_7290661 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Longstanton"
  },
  "281": {
    "Question": "Which regional unit in the region of Epirus has a lake?",
    "Query": "Select distinct  ?city  Where {          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Epirus_(region)> geo:hasGeometry ?o.           ?city rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/GAG_RegionalUnit>.        ?city <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/GAG_BelongsTo> <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Epirus_(region)> .         ?city <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?C.            ?lake rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_lake>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomB.           ?geomB geo:asWKT ?B.           FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:transform(?B, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?C, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))).  }",
    "Answer": "ΠΕΡΙΦΕΡΕΙΑΚΗ ΕΝΟΤΗΤΑ ΠΡΕΒΕΖΑΣ  ΠΕΡΙΦΕΡΕΙΑΚΗ ΕΝΟΤΗΤΑ ΙΩΑΝΝΙΝΩΝ"
  },
  "282": {
    "Question": "Is there any lagoon near beach in Thasos?",
    "Query": "ASK { yago:Thasos geo:hasGeometry ?o2 . ?o2 geo:asWKT ?xWKT2 . ?x2 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach . ?x2 geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geom. ?x2Geom geo:asWKT ?iWKT2. ?x1 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lagoon . ?x1 geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geom. ?x1Geom geo:asWKT ?iWKT1. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(strdf:transform(?iWKT1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?xWKT2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)) && geof:sfWithin(strdf:transform(?iWKT2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?xWKT2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)) && geof:distance(strdf:transform(?iWKT1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?iWKT2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "283": {
    "Question": "Give me exactly one park of Dublin that is within 10km from a canal.",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?x2 where { yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?o2 . ?o2 geo:asWKT ?xWKT2 . ?x2 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park . ?x2 geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geom. ?x2Geom geo:asWKT ?iWKT2. ?x1 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal . ?x1 geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geom. ?x1Geom geo:asWKT ?iWKT1. FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(strdf:transform(?iWKT1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?xWKT2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)) && geof:sfIntersects(strdf:transform(?iWKT2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?xWKT2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)) && geof:distance(strdf:transform(?iWKT1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?iWKT2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), uom:metre) < 10000) } limit 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Phoenix_Park"
  },
  "284": {
    "Question": "Which villages are up to 50km far away from canals in Birmingham?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?canal ?village where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Birmingham> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?prkWKT. ?canal rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal . ?canal <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geoPrk. ?geoPrk geo:asWKT ?lWKT. ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village . ?village <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?cWKT. FILTER (geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?prkWKT) && geof:distance(?cWKT, ?lWKT, uom:metre)<50000) }",
    "Answer": "canalvillage http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Worcester_and_Birmingham_Canal_2633562http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Sheriff_Hales_2638023 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Worcester_and_Birmingham_Canal_2633562http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Peopleton http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Worcester_and_Birmingham_Canal_2633562http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ratby http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Worcester_and_Birmingham_Canal_2633562http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Newborough,_Staffordshire"
  },
  "285": {
    "Question": "Which islands are near beaches in Naxos?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?beach ?island where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Naxos> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach . ?beach <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. ?island rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island . ?island <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geoIsl. ?geoIsl geo:asWKT ?IslWKT. FILTER (geof:distance(?lcnWKT, ?lWKT, uom:metre)<2000 && geof:distance(?IslWKT, ?lWKT, uom:metre)<20000 && ?island!=<http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Naxos>). }",
    "Answer": "beach island http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mikri_Vigla_-Southern_bay_(Limanaki)_6942749http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Nisí_Irákleia_261746 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Orkos_bay_7731772http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Nisí_Irákleia_261746 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mikri_Vigla_-Southern_bay_(Limanaki)_6942749http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Paros http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Orkos_bay_7731772http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Paros http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kastraki_beach_6942750http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Nisí_Schoinoússa_253651 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mikri_Vigla_-Southern_bay_(Limanaki)_6942749http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Nisída_Káto_Koufonísi_260550 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mikri_Vigla_-Southern_bay_(Limanaki)_6942749http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Koufonísi_259162 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Plaka_beach_6942748http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Paros http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kastraki_beach_6942750http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Koufonísi_259162 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Plaka_beach_6942748http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ani_Jima_2113104 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kastraki_beach_6942750http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Nisí_Irákleia_261746 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kastraki_beach_6942750http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Nisída_Káto_Koufonísi_260550 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Mikri_Vigla_-Southern_bay_(Limanaki)_6942749http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Nisí_Schoinoússa_253651 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kastraki_beach_6942750http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Paros"
  },
  "286": {
    "Question": "Which bays are near parks in Dublin?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?bay where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?prkWKT. ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park . ?park <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geoPrk. ?geoPrk geo:asWKT ?lWKT. ?bay rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_bay . ?bay <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?cWKT. FILTER (geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?prkWKT) && geof:distance(?cWKT, ?lWKT, uom:metre)<10000) }",
    "Answer": "bay http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Scotsmans_Bay_3230523 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin_Bay"
  },
  "287": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are within islands in decentralized administration of Peloponnisos Dytiki Ellada Ionio?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?lake where {         ?island rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island.         ?island geo:hasGeometry ?ig.         ?ig geo:asWKT ?igeoWKT.          geoentity_Apokentroméni_Dioíkisi_Peloponnísou_-_Dytikís_Elládas_-_Ioníou_8200478  geo:hasGeometry ?g2.         ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. FILTER(strdf:within(?igeoWKT, ?geoWKT)).         ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake.         ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?lg.         ?lg geo:asWKT ?lgeoWKT. FILTER(strdf:within(?lgeoWKT, ?igeoWKT)). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "288": {
    "Question": "Which are the city councils in Ireland that have parks in less than 10km?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x where  { ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_City_Council . ?x geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park. ?park geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER(geof:distance(?lcnWKT,?lWKT,uom:metre) < 10000) }",
    "Answer": "x http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Cork http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin"
  },
  "289": {
    "Question": "Which are the unitary authorities of England that border with Scotland?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?d  where {  ?d rdf:type y2geoo:OS_UnitaryAuthority;    geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom.                                         ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT.                                         yago:Scotland geo:hasGeometry ?geom.                                          ?geom geo:asWKT ?iWKT.                                         yago:England geo:hasGeometry ?geom1. ?geom1 geo:asWKT ?iWKT1.                                         FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cWKT,?iWKT1) && geof:sfTouches(?cWKT,?iWKT) )   }",
    "Answer": "d http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northumberland"
  },
  "290": {
    "Question": "Which are the forests and the canals of Edinburgh?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?forest ?canal  where { yago:Edinburgh geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest; geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. ?canal rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal; geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC2. ?geomLC2 geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT2. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT) && geof:sfWithin(?lcnWKT2,?lcnWKT) ) }",
    "Answer": "forest                                                                                                                 canal http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Redford_Wood_6544674  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Union_Canal_(Scotland)"
  },
  "291": {
    "Question": "Which beaches are at most 100 km distance to Ormos Vourkari in Greece?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?beach WHERE {    ?beach a y2geoo:OSM_beach. ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.         ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Órmos_Vourkári_251740> geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.         ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.   FILTER(geof:distance(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT, uom:metre) < 100000) }",
    "Answer": "name Λαούτη Galissa beach@en Παραλία Γαλησσά Άγιος Ρωμανός Халкиада@ru Chalikiada Beach Lotos beach@en Παραλία Λωτό Αγία Θάλασσα Komito Beach@en Παραλία Κόμητο Λιβάδα Αποθήκες Καμπάνες@el Kampanes@en Πλατύς Γιαλός Καμπάνες Blue Lagoon@en Παραλία Φρεαττύδος Pachia Ammos@en Παχιά άμμος Vari Beach@en Παραλία Βάρη Νεροδάφνη@el Nerodafni@en Νεροδάφνη Καλύβια Σάντα Μαργαρίτα Απηγανιά Βοτσαλάκια@el Βοτσαλάκια Άγιος Σώστης@el Agios Sostis@en Άγιος Σώστης Καβαλουρκό Ερωτοσπηλιά"
  },
  "292": {
    "Question": "Is there a lake near a forest in county Wicklow?",
    "Query": "ASK {    ?x1 a y2geoo:OSM_lake.  ?x1 geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.  ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.    ?x2 a y2geoo:OSM_forest.   ?x2 geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.         ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Wicklow>     geo:hasGeometry ?x3Geo.         ?x3Geo geo:asWKT ?x3WKT.     FILTER (geof:sfWithin(?x1WKT, ?x3WKT)).        FILTER (geof:distance(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT, uom:metre) < 10000) }",
    "Answer": "name Luggala Lake Lough Tay"
  },
  "293": {
    "Question": "Is there a lake that borders with an English county?",
    "Query": "ASK {     ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake.     ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     ?county a y2geoo:OS_County.     ?county geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.         FILTER(             geof:sfTouches(      strdf:transform(?wkt1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),      strdf:transform(?wkt2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "294": {
    "Question": "What municipalities are near lakes in Central Macedonia?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?municipality  WHERE {     ?municipality a y2geoo:GAG_Municipality.     ?municipality geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake.     ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Central_Macedonia>  geo:hasGeometry ?g3.     ?g3 geo:asWKT ?wkt3.     FILTER(         geof:sfWithin(      strdf:transform(?wkt2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),      strdf:transform(?wkt3, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))      &&         geof:distance(      strdf:transform(?wkt1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),      strdf:transform(?wkt2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),                            uom:metre) < 5000 ). }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Chalkidona_8133775 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pylaia-Chortiatis http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Aristotelis_(municipality) http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oraiokastro http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Volvi_(municipality) http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Kilkis_8133969 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Lagkadas_8133981"
  },
  "295": {
    "Question": "Is there a village that is next to a nature reserve in England?",
    "Query": "ASK WHERE {     ?village a y2geoo:OSM_village.     ?village geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     ?nature_reserve a y2geoo:OSM_nature_reserve.     ?nature_reserve geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.     yago:England geo:hasGeometry ?g3.     ?g3 geo:asWKT ?wkt3.     FILTER(         geof:sfWithin(     strdf:transform(?wkt2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),     strdf:transform(?wkt3, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))     &&         geof:sfIntersects(     strdf:transform(?wkt1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),     strdf:transform(?wkt2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wicken,_Cambridgeshire"
  },
  "296": {
    "Question": "What streams have one end in a lake in Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?river  WHERE {     ?river a y2geoo:OSM_stream.     ?river geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake.     ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.     yago:Republic_of_Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?g3.     ?g3 geo:asWKT ?wkt3.     FILTER(         geof:sfWithin(     strdf:transform(?wkt2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),     strdf:transform(?wkt3, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))     &&         geof:sfIntersects(     strdf:transform(?wkt1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),     strdf:transform(?wkt2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Loughkip_River_3312421 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Owenmore_River_2962113 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Clady_River_3308564"
  },
  "297": {
    "Question": "Find the 3 least populated islands of Greece.",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?island ?pop  WHERE {     ?island a y2geoo:OSM_island.     ?island y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?pop.     ?island geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     yago:Greece geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.     FILTER(         geof:sfIntersects(     strdf:transform(?wkt2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),     strdf:transform(?wkt1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) } ORDER BY (?pop) LIMIT 3",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Symi 910^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kasos 990^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Astypalaia 1238^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "298": {
    "Question": "What are the 10 smallest towns of Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?town ((strdf:area(?wkt1)) as ?totalArea) WHERE {     ?town a y2geoo:OSM_town.     ?town geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     yago:Republic_of_Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?wkt1, ?wkt2)).     } ORDER BY ?totalArea Limit 10",
    "Answer": "town totalArea disthttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Arklow 2.6045323465950787E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> 56332.5703125^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Ross 5.6296761613339186E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> 109324.4140625^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kilbeggan 8.154781971825287E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> 73169.6796875^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Athy 1.156115104095079E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> 54520.38671875^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kinnegad 1.2146436347393319E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> 48445.26171875^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Athy 1.2471032096073031E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> 54583.96484375^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kilbeggan 1.5954063565004617E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> 72645.296875^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Killaloe,_County_Clare 1.9087672990281135E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> 149734.671875^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Gorey 2.271540288347751E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> 68495.984375^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Ross 2.9404740780591965E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> 108792.7734375^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "299": {
    "Question": "Which forests are within baronies of Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?for  WHERE {     ?for a y2geoo:OSM_forest .   ?for geo:hasGeometry ?o .     ?o geo:asWKT ?forestGeo .      ?barony a y2geoo:OSI_Barony .     ?barony geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .     ?o2 geo:asWKT ?baronyGeo .  yago:Republic_of_Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?ir.     ?ir geo:asWKT ?irWKT.    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?forestGeo , ?baronyGeo ) && geof:sfWithin(?baronyGeo, ?irWKT )) }",
    "Answer": "Drum Wood Carrigatubbrid Wood Glenbower Wood Ballyhourigan Woods Green Wood Ballyreagh Wood Rehill Wood Glengarra Wood Dromhilly Wood Boolymore Wood Rossacroonaloo Wood Killoughrum Forest Tombrick Wood Uragh Wood Drimingall Wood Clonad Wood Ballykeefe Wood Shirsheen Wood Grove Wood Roddenagh Wood Cratloe Woods Mountshannon Wood Rossmore Forest Park Ballyteige Wood"
  },
  "300": {
    "Question": "Which Greek municipalities have at least one beach?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?municipality WHERE {    ?municipality a y2geoo:GAG_Municipality .    ?municipality geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .    ?o1 geo:asWKT ?munWKT .     ?beach a y2geoo:OSM_beach .    ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .    ?o2 geo:asWKT ?beachWKT .     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?beachWKT , ?munWKT )) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Lefkada_8133851 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Agkistri_8133874 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Syros http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Alonnisos_8133938 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tinos http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Skiathos_8133939 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Kissamos_8133753 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Naxos_and_Lesser_Cyclades_8133697 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Parga_8133742 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Loutraki-Agioi_Theodoroi_8133977 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/West_Mani http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chios http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Markopoulo_Mesogaias_8133947 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Igoumenitsa_8133725 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Paxoi_8133911 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Spetses http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rhodes http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mylopotamos,_Crete http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Zagora-Mouresi http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Samos http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Epidaurus_8133804 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Agios_Vasileios,_Rethymno http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Messene_8133986 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Santorini_8133832 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Corfu_8133855 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Milos_8133681 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Malevizi http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Nafplio_8133806 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mykonos"
  },
  "301": {
    "Question": "Which parks are inside counties of England?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?park ?county WHERE {  ?county a y2geoo:OS_County .         ?county geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?countyGeo .          ?park a y2geoo:OSM_park .         ?park geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .         ?o2 geo:asWKT ?parkGeo .          FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?parkGeo , ?countyGeo)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cheluvett_Park_9884142http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Worcestershire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cheluvett_Park_9884142http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Worcestershire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Avisford_9613133http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/West_Sussex http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Avisford_9613133http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/West_Sussex http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Charlecote_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Warwickshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Charlecote_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Warwickshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Christchurch_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Gippeswyk_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Chantry_Park_6301929http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_West_Stow_Country_Park_9883966http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Landseer_Park_6301924http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Holywells_Park_6301923http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Christchurch_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Gippeswyk_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Chantry_Park_6301929http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Holywells_Park_6301923http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Landseer_Park_6301924http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_West_Stow_Country_Park_9883966http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Harlow_Town_Park_6640043http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Essex http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rushcliffe_Country_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nottinghamshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rushcliffe_Country_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nottinghamshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Gildrege_Park_10377109http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/East_Sussex http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Gildrege_Park_10377109http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/East_Sussex http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Highfield_Park_6615331http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hertfordshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rickmansworth_Park_9884670http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hertfordshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Highfield_Park_6615331http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hertfordshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rickmansworth_Park_9884670http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hertfordshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sheringham_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norfolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sheringham_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norfolk http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Gloucster_Park_10377067http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Gloucestershire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Gloucster_Park_10377067http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Gloucestershire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Day's_Park_11071807http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dorset http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Day's_Park_11071807http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dorset http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Boughton_Park_2655113http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northamptonshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Boughton_Park_2655113http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northamptonshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Locko_Park_9319007http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Derbyshire http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mote_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kent http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Central_Park_10377780http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kent http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mote_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kent http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Central_Park_10377780http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kent http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Phillips_Memorial_Park_10109961http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Shalford_Park_9538925http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Merland_Rise_Recreational_Ground_9538934http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bagshot_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Stoke_Park_7116371http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Eyhurst_Park_10104033http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Netley_Park_N_T_9883993http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Phillips_Memorial_Park_10109961http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Shalford_Park_9538925http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Merland_Rise_Recreational_Ground_9538934http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bagshot_Parkhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Stoke_Park_7116371http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Eyhurst_Park_10104033http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Netley_Park_N_T_9883993http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey"
  },
  "302": {
    "Question": "Which towns have lakes in the Kilmacrenan barony?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?town  WHERE{         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kilmacrenan_2963284>  geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?baronyWKT .   ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake .  ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .         ?o2 geo:asWKT ?lakeWKT .          ?town a y2geoo:OSI_Townland .         ?town  geo:hasGeometry ?o3 .       ?o3 geo:asWKT ?townWKT .          FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?townWKT , ?baronyWKT))         FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lakeWKT , ?townWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "CORVEEN (ED Meenaclady) An Chorrmhín@en Lough Nagreenan An Chorrmhín@ga Lough Nagreenan CORVEEN (ED Meenaclady) An Chorrmhín Lough Nagreenan KILLOUGHCARRAN@en Carrick Lough KILLOUGHCARRAN Carrick Lough BROCKAGH (ED Creenasmear)@en Brockagh Lough BROCKAGH (ED Creenasmear)@en Lough Agannive BROCKAGH (ED Creenasmear) Brockagh Lough BROCKAGH (ED Creenasmear) Lough Agannive DRUMNALIFFERNY MOUNTAIN Sliabh Dhroim na Luifearnaí@en Lough Atirrive Little Sliabh Dhroim na Luifearnaí@ga Lough Atirrive Little DRUMNALIFFERNY MOUNTAIN Sliabh Dhroim na Luifearnaí Lough Atirrive Little GLENTORNAN Gleann Tornáin@en Glentornan Lough Gleann Tornáin@ga Glentornan Lough GLENTORNAN Gleann Tornáin Glentornan Lough CASHELNAGOR Caiseal na gCorr@en Lough Agannive Caiseal na gCorr@ga Lough Agannive CASHELNAGOR Caiseal na gCorr Lough Agannive CARROWNAMADDY (ED Creenasmear)@en Lough Naboll CARROWNAMADDY (ED Creenasmear) Lough Naboll STAGHALL MOUNTAIN WEST Cró an Locháin@en Croloughan Lough Cró an Locháin@ga Croloughan Lough STAGHALL MOUNTAIN WEST Cró an Locháin Croloughan Lough BALLYNESS MOUNTAIN Sliabh Bhaile an Easa@en Lough Aluirg Sliabh Bhaile an Easa@ga Lough Aluirg BALLYNESS MOUNTAIN Sliabh Bhaile an Easa Lough Aluirg GARTAN MOUNTAIN@en Lough Nambraddan GARTAN MOUNTAIN Lough Nambraddan GLASSAN Glasán@en Lough Agarrowen Glasán@ga Lough Agarrowen GLASSAN Glasán Lough Agarrowen DERRYREEL Doire Uí Fhríl@en Derryreel Lough Doire Uí Fhríl@ga Derryreel Lough DERRYREEL Doire Uí Fhríl Derryreel Lough TULLYCONNELL Tulaigh Chonaill@en Lough Naglea Tulaigh Chonaill@ga Lough Naglea TULLYCONNELL Tulaigh Chonaill Lough Naglea KEELDRUM UPPER Caoldroim Uachtarach@en Lough Adinn Caoldroim Uachtarach@ga Lough Adinn KEELDRUM UPPER Caoldroim Uachtarach Lough Adinn"
  },
  "303": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities south of Kastoria have a lake?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?municipality WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kastoria> geo:hasGeometry ?o3 .    ?o3 geo:asWKT ?kastoriaWKT .       ?municipality a y2geoo:GAG_Municipality .    ?municipality geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .    ?o1 geo:asWKT ?munWKT .     ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake .    ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .    ?o2 geo:asWKT ?lakeWKT .     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lakeWKT , ?munWKT ))    FILTER(strdf:below(?munWKT  , ?kastoriaWKT )) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Aktio-Vonitsa http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Límni_Saltíni_254132 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Zacharo http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Límni_Kaïáfa_261690 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pogoni http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Límni_Zaravínas_252498 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Agrinio_8133845 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lake_Lysimachia http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Vari-Voula-Vouliagmeni http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Límni_Vouliagménis_11045660 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lemnos http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Límni_Alykí_265329 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ziros,_Preveza http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Límni_Ziroú_251199 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Aspropyrgos http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Límni_Koumoundoúrou_259065"
  },
  "304": {
    "Question": "Which is the area of the park in Essex?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?park((strdf:area(?parkGeo)) as ?parkArea) WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Essex> geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?countyGeo .          ?park a y2geoo:OSM_park .         ?park geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .         ?o2 geo:asWKT ?parkGeo .           FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?parkGeo, ?countyGeo)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Harlow_Town_Park_6640043 5.8351619372842833E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "305": {
    "Question": "Which localities are near lakes in county Cavan ?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?locality WHERE {  yago:County_Cavan geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?locality rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_locality .  ?locality geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake .  ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o3 .  ?o3 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT3 .  FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:within(?geoWKT3, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:distance(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT3, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": "locality http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Moneynure_3311685 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lisduff_3309530 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Treehog_Cross_Roads_3309566 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumliff_3309565 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drutamon_3309628 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kilsob_3309399 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Gowlan_3311680 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Claragh_3309567 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Toberlyan_3309372 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Bellville_3309525 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Derry_3309499 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Bursan_3311662 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Aghalackan_3309544 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Glasstown_3309488 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumgor_3309515 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Teeboy_3311691 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Corraneary_3311396 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Erraran_3311689 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ballynahaia_3309610 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Plush_3309459 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Killyvally_3309516 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Derrydamph_3309642 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Glen_3309416 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumroe_3309508 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Nolagh_3309689 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cornahaw_3311636 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Derryna_3309482 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Snakeel_3309491 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Inishconnell_3309524 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Beglieve_3309648 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Corraweelis_3309541 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Legnagrow_3311659 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Killycluggin_3309378 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rakane_3309614 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Culliagh_3311698 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Glasleck_3309686 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cullentragh_3309551 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Straheglin_3309427 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kilmacaran_3309678 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Raheelan_3309425 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Edergole_3309851 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Killyvanny_3309553 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Aghadreenagh_3309564 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumhillagh_3309573 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumane_3309381 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Lisnamandra_3309528 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Fartrin_Cross_Roads_3309383 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rivory_3309469 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumlane_3309574 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Finaghoo_3309402 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kilcrossduff_3309692 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Greaghrahan_3309413 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumcondra_3309660 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Altateskin_3311679 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Callaghs_3309385 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Binbane_3309623 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Killykeen_3309521 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cornagee_3311631 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Duneena_3309647 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ledonigan_3309637 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Corick_Bridge_3309611 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drummany_3309367 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Stragelliff_3309548 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Carricknashoke_3309627 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Greaghagibney_3309636 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kinagha_3309443 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Leck_3311616 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumconnick_3309533 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Poles_3309547 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Gortnavreghan_3309401 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Oggal_3311633 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Drumcrow_South_3309505 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kilnacrew_3309654 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rinn_3309483 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Corraneary_3309653 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cornafean_3309509 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ouley_3309552 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Latsey_3309643 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Moher_3309394 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Crossmakeelan_3309690"
  },
  "306": {
    "Question": "Which forests are near streams in Breckland district?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?forest WHERE {  yago:Breckland_District geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest .  ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  ?stream rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream .  ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?o3 .  ?o3 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT3 .  FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:within(?geoWKT3, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:distance(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT3, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": "forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Saham_Wood_9539000"
  },
  "307": {
    "Question": "Which villages are near beaches in Thessaly region?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?village WHERE {  yago:Thessaly geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village .  ?village geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach .  ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?o3 .  ?o3 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT3 .  FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:within(?geoWKT3, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:distance(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT3, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": "village http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Alonissos_265263"
  },
  "308": {
    "Question": "All the district that has forest south of Staffordshire",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?district  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Staffordshire> geo:hasGeometry ?Staffordshire_geo . ?Staffordshire_geo geo:asWKT ?Staffordshire_geoWKT . ?district rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_District> . ?district geo:hasGeometry ?district_geo .   ?district_geo geo:asWKT ?district_geoWKT .    FILTER(strdf:below(?district_geoWKT,?Staffordshire_geoWKT))    ?forest rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_forest> . ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?forest_geo . ?forest_geo geo:asWKT ?forest_geoWKT . FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?forest_geoWKT,?district_geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Borough_of_Tunbridge_Wells_6945811Parsonage Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tendring_District_7290546Pedlars Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Elmbridge_District_2650079New Barn Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Cambridgeshire_District_7290661Hayley Wood NR http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Forest_of_Dean_District_7290550Old Park Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_South_Northamptonshire_District_7290604Lovel Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_St._Edmundsbury_District_7290636Shepherd's Grove http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Epping_Forest_District_7290543Epping Forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Horsham_District_7290651St Leonard's Forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Borough_of_Tunbridge_Wells_6945811Hurst Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Epping_Forest_District_7290543Furze Woods"
  },
  "309": {
    "Question": "All the rural area that has forest south of Longford",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?Rural_Area  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Longford> geo:hasGeometry ?Longford_geo . ?Longford_geo geo:asWKT ?Longford_geoWKT . ?Rural_Area rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_Rural_Area> . ?Rural_Area geo:hasGeometry ?Rural_Area_geo .   ?Rural_Area_geo geo:asWKT ?Rural_Area_geoWKT .    FILTER(strdf:below(?Rural_Area_geoWKT,?Longford_geoWKT))    ?forest rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_forest> . ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?forest_geo . ?forest_geo geo:asWKT ?forest_geoWKT .   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?forest_geoWKT,?Rural_Area_geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629441F13A3E055000000000001Clonad Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dangan_2964884Dromana Forest http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629444013A3E055000000000001Shirsheen Wood http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629444C13A3E055000000000001Drimingall Wood http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629443F13A3E055000000000001Tombrick Wood http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629446013A3E055000000000001Corbally Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Meelick_Bridge_3310146Cratloe Woods http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/SkibbereenDromhilly Woodhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/KillimerMountshannon Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rathmore_2961892Ballyteige Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Clogheen,_County_TipperaryGlengarra Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Clogheen,_County_TipperaryRehill Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/KilgarvanRossacroonaloo Wood http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629445713A3E055000000000001Uragh Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kilmihil_3291425Green Wood http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629443F13A3E055000000000001Killoughrum Forest http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629442A13A3E055000000000001Drum Wood http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629444A13A3E055000000000001Ballyreagh Wood http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Connagh_3312874Ballyhourigan Woods"
  },
  "310": {
    "Question": "All the rural area that has forest northern side of Cork County",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?Rural_Area  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cork_City_7778678> geo:hasGeometry ?Longford_geo . ?Longford_geo geo:asWKT ?Longford_geoWKT . ?Rural_Area rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_Rural_Area> . ?Rural_Area geo:hasGeometry ?Rural_Area_geo .   ?Rural_Area_geo geo:asWKT ?Rural_Area_geoWKT .    FILTER(strdf:above(?Rural_Area_geoWKT,?Longford_geoWKT))    ?forest rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_forest> . ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?forest_geo . ?forest_geo geo:asWKT ?forest_geoWKT .    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?forest_geoWKT,?Rural_Area_geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629441F13A3E055000000000001Clonad Woodhttp://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629444013A3E055000000000001Shirsheen Woodhttp://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629444C13A3E055000000000001Drimingall Woodhttp://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629443F13A3E055000000000001Tombrick Woodhttp://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629441B13A3E055000000000001Rossmore Forest Parkhttp://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629442613A3E055000000000001Slishwoodhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Meelick_Bridge_3310146Cratloe Woodshttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/KillimerMountshannon Woodhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rathmore_2961892Ballyteige Woodhttp://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629443F13A3E055000000000001Killoughrum Foresthttp://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629442A13A3E055000000000001Drum Woodhttp://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629444A13A3E055000000000001Ballyreagh Woodhttp://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Connagh_3312874Ballyhourigan Woods"
  },
  "311": {
    "Question": "Which forests are near streams in Wicklow county?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?forest WHERE { yago:County_Wicklow geo:hasGeometry ?o . ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest; geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 . ?stream rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream; geo:hasGeometry ?o2 . ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 . FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT) &&  strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT) &&  strdf:distance(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": "forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ballyreagh_Wood_3315175"
  },
  "312": {
    "Question": "Which villages are near lakes in Cumbria county?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?village WHERE { yago:Cumbria geo:hasGeometry ?o . ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village; geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 . ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake; geo:hasGeometry ?o2 . ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 . FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT) &&  strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT) &&  strdf:distance(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": "village http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Boot,_Cumbria"
  },
  "313": {
    "Question": "Which villages are near beaches in Corfu Island?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?village WHERE { yago:Corfu geo:hasGeometry ?o . ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village; geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 . ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach; geo:hasGeometry ?o2 . ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 . FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT) &&  strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT) &&  strdf:distance(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": "village http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Agios_Onoúfrios_9165971"
  },
  "314": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are entirely contained in one Greek municipality?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?l WHERE {    ?m rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality.    ?m geo:hasGeometry ?mg .    ?mg geo:asWKT ?mw .     ?l a y2geoo:OSM_lake .    ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .    ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lw,?mw)) }",
    "Answer": "Πικρολίμνη Λίμνη Ζηρού Λίμνη Βουλιαγμένης Λίμνη Κουμουνδούρου Λίμνη Καστοριάς Λίμνη Ορεστιάδα Λίμνη Σαλτίνη Λίμνη Λυσιμαχία Λίμνη Καϊάφα Νιζερός Λίμνη Ζαραβίνα Λίμνη Αλυκή Λίμνη Ζάζαρη"
  },
  "315": {
    "Question": "Which forests are entirely contained in an English County?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?l WHERE {    ?m a y2geoo:OS_County.    ?m geo:hasGeometry ?mg .    ?mg geo:asWKT ?mw .     ?l a y2geoo:OSM_forest .    ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .    ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lw,?mw)) }",
    "Answer": "Saham Wood Mulgrave Woods Pedlars Wood St Leonard's Forest Kelham Hills Epping Forest Hurst Wood Old Park Wood Shepherd's Grove Holkham Meals, Open Access Hayley Wood NR Greaves Wood Wayland Wood New Barn Wood Lovel Wood Furze Woods Paddock Wood Rough Wood Parsonage Wood"
  },
  "316": {
    "Question": "Which forests are entirely contained in an Irish Barony?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?l WHERE {    ?m a y2geoo:OSI_Barony.    ?m geo:hasGeometry ?mg .    ?mg geo:asWKT ?mw .     ?l a y2geoo:OSM_forest.    ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .    ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lw,?mw)) }",
    "Answer": "Rehill Wood Killoughrum Forest Ballyhourigan Woods Dromhilly Wood Rossmore Forest Park Tombrick Wood Boolymore Wood Carrigatubbrid Wood Ballykeefe Wood Mountshannon Wood Cratloe Woods Shirsheen Wood Rossacroonaloo Wood Glengarra Wood Green Wood Ballyteige Wood Clonad Wood Grove Wood Drum Wood Uragh Wood Drimingall Wood Glenbower Wood Ballyreagh Wood Roddenagh Wood"
  },
  "317": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are entirely contained in Greek municipality which is east of the Chania ?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?ln WHERE {   ?m rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Chania_8133762> geo:hasGeometry ?cg.    ?m geo:hasGeometry ?mg.    ?cg geo:asWKT ?cw.    ?mg geo:asWKT ?mw.    FILTER(strdf:right(?cw,?mw))     ?l a y2geoo:OSM_lake .    ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .    ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lw,?mw)).  }",
    "Answer": "Πικρολίμνη Λίμνη Ζηρού Λίμνη Βουλιαγμένης Λίμνη Κουμουνδούρου Λίμνη Καστοριάς Λίμνη Ορεστιάδα Λίμνη Σαλτίνη Λίμνη Λυσιμαχία Λίμνη Καϊάφα Νιζερός Λίμνη Ζαραβίνα Λίμνη Ζάζαρη"
  },
  "318": {
    "Question": "Which forests are entirely contained in counties that are west of the Norfolk County?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?l WHERE {    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norfolk> geo:hasGeometry ?ng .    ?ng geo:asWKT ?nw .        ?m a y2geoo:OS_County.    ?m geo:hasGeometry ?mg .    ?mg geo:asWKT ?mw .     FILTER(strdf:right(?nw, ?mw)).     ?l a y2geoo:OSM_forest .    ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .    ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lw,?mw)) }",
    "Answer": "Mulgrave Woods St Leonard's Forest Kelham Hills Old Park Wood Hayley Wood NR Greaves Wood New Barn Wood Lovel Wood Paddock Wood Rough Wood"
  },
  "319": {
    "Question": "Which forests are entirely contained in baronies east of Coshlea?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?l WHERE {    <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629112213A3E055000000000001> geo:hasGeometry ?ng .    ?ng geo:asWKT ?nw .        ?m a y2geoo:OSI_Barony.    ?m geo:hasGeometry ?mg .    ?mg geo:asWKT ?mw .     FILTER(strdf:left(?nw, ?mw)).     ?l a y2geoo:OSM_forest .    ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .    ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .      FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lw,?mw)) }",
    "Answer": "Killoughrum Forest Rossmore Forest Park Tombrick Wood Carrigatubbrid Wood Ballykeefe Wood Shirsheen Wood Ballyteige Wood Clonad Wood Grove Wood Drimingall Wood Ballyreagh Wood Roddenagh Wood"
  },
  "320": {
    "Question": "Which region of Greece has the biggest population?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?region WHERE { ?region rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Region . ?region y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population } ORDER BY DESC (?population) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Attica_(region)"
  },
  "321": {
    "Question": "Which county is the smallest by area ?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?county ((strdf:area(?cWKT)) as ?totalArea) WHERE { ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OS_County . ?county geo:hasGeometry ?geoC . ?geoC geo:asWKT ?cWKT } ORDER BY (?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_Somerset 0.05121792107820511^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "322": {
    "Question": "Which county council has the least townlands?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?county (COUNT(?town) AS ?num) WHERE { ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council . ?town rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_Townland . ?county geo:hasGeometry ?geoc . ?geoc geo:asWKT ?cWKT . ?town geo:hasGeometry ?geot . ?geot geo:asWKT ?tWKT . FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?tWKT, ?cWKT)) } GROUP BY ?county ORDER BY (?num) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dún_Laoghaire–Rathdown 103^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "323": {
    "Question": "Which 10 municipalities west of Athens have the lowest population?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?municipality WHERE {         yago:geoentity_Dimos_Athens_8133876 geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.         ?municipality rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality;         y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.          FILTER(strdf:left(?WKT1, ?WKT)) } ORDER BY ?population LIMIT 10",
    "Answer": "municipality http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Skiathos_8133939 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Elafonisos http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Agkistri_8133874 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Meganisi http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Paxoi_8133911 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Prespes http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Perama http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Hydra_8133769 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Ithaca_8133849 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kythira_8133702"
  },
  "324": {
    "Question": "Which is the smallest forest areas that intersects with Essex?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?forest WHERE{  yago:Essex geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.          ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.          FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT, 0, uom:metre)))  } ORDER BY (strdf:area(?WKT1)) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "forest http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Pedlars_Wood_9883765"
  },
  "325": {
    "Question": "Which are the 2 Baronies with biggest area that Intersect with Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?barony WHERE {          yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.          ?barony rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_Barony;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.          FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT, 0, uom:metre)))  } ORDER BY DESC (strdf:area(?WKT1)) LIMIT 2",
    "Answer": "barony http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dubber_Cross_7838912 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Hartstown_3315332"
  },
  "326": {
    "Question": "Which is the largest forest by area in England?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?forest ((strdf:area(?fWKT)) AS ?totalArea) WHERE {     ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest;     <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?fGeom.     ?fGeom geo:asWKT ?fWKT.     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/England> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?lcGeom.     ?lcGeom geo:asWKT ?lcWKT.     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?fWKT, ?lcWKT)) }  ORDER BY DESC(?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wyre_Forest"
  },
  "327": {
    "Question": "Which is the largest park by area in Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?park ((strdf:area(?pWKT)) AS ?totalArea) WHERE {         ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park.         ?park   <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?pGeom.         ?pGeom geo:asWKT ?pWKT.         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?lcGeom.         ?lcGeom geo:asWKT ?lcWKT.         FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?pWKT, ?lcWKT))     } ORDER BY DESC(?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ringsend_Park_3289060"
  },
  "328": {
    "Question": "Which is the smallest beach by area in Naxos?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?beach ((strdf:area(?bWKT)) AS ?totalArea) WHERE {         ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach.         ?beach   <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?bGeom.         ?bGeom geo:asWKT ?bWKT.         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Naxos> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?lcGeom.         ?lcGeom geo:asWKT ?lcWKT.         FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?bWKT, ?lcWKT))     } ORDER BY ASC(?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Orkos_bay_7731772"
  },
  "329": {
    "Question": "Which Region that borders Thessaly has the largest population ?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?rg ?pop where  { yago:Thessaly geo:hasGeometry ?tgeo . ?tgeo geo:asWKT ?tWKT . ?rg rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Region . ?rg geo:hasGeometry ?rggeo . ?rggeo geo:asWKT ?rgWKT . ?rg y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?pop . FILTER (strdf:touches(?rgWKT,?tWKT)) . } order by desc (?pop) limit 1",
    "Answer": "rg pop http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Central_Macedonia 1759533^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "330": {
    "Question": "Which is the smallest Metropolitan District that border Manchester?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?Mdistrict WHERE { yago:Manchester geo:hasGeometry ?egeo . ?egeo geo:asWKT ?eWKT . ?Mdistrict rdf:type y2geoo:OS_MetropolitanDistrict . ?Mdistrict geo:hasGeometry ?cgeo . ?cgeo geo:asWKT ?cWKT . FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?eWKT,?cWKT)) . BIND (strdf:area(?cWKT) as ?area) . } order by ?area limit 1",
    "Answer": "Mdistrict http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/City_of_Salford"
  },
  "331": {
    "Question": "Which is the biggest lake in County Kerry ?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?lake  WHERE {  yago:County_Kerry geo:hasGeometry ?lgeo . ?lgeo geo:asWKT ?lWKT .  ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake. ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?sgeo . ?sgeo geo:asWKT ?sWKT .  FILTER (strdf:within(?sWKT,?lWKT)) . BIND (strdf:area(?sWKT) as ?area) . }  order by desc (?area) limit 1",
    "Answer": "lake http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lough_Leane"
  },
  "332": {
    "Question": "Which 3 municipalities in Epirus have the biggest population?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?municipality WHERE {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Epirus_(region)> geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.     ?municipality rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality.     ?municipality geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT2.     FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre))).     ?municipality y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population } ORDER BY DESC (?population) LIMIT 3",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Ioannina_7303595 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Arta,_Greece http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Preveza_8133743"
  },
  "333": {
    "Question": "Which is the biggest district that border Greater London?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?district  WHERE {     yago:Greater_London geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.     ?district rdf:type y2geoo:OS_District.     ?district geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT2.     FILTER(strdf:touches(strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre))). } ORDER BY DESC (strdf:area(?WKT2)) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Sevenoaks_District_6945814"
  },
  "334": {
    "Question": "Which is the biggest forest in County Wexford?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?forest WHERE {     yago:County_Wexford geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.     ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest.     ?forest geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT2.     FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre))) } ORDER BY DESC (strdf:area(?WKT2)) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Killoughrum_Forest_2963306"
  },
  "335": {
    "Question": "What are the official names of the  Municipalities that belong  to Periferiaki Enotita Nison and have population  less than 3000, contain islands?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?dimos  WHERE {   ?dimos <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/GAG_BelongsTo> <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Perifereiakí_Enótita_Níson_8200487> .   ?dimos geo:hasGeometry ?dimos_geo .   ?dimos_geo geo:asWKT ?dimos_geoWKT .  ?dimos <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/hasGAG_Population> ?dimos_pop .   FILTER( ?dimos_pop < 3000 )   ?island rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_island> .    ?island geo:hasGeometry ?island_geo .   ?island_geo geo:asWKT ?island_geoWKT .  FILTER( geof:sfIntersects(?island_geoWKT,?dimos_geoWKT) )  }",
    "Answer": "ΔΗΜΟΣ ΑΓΚΙΣΤΡΙΟΥ  Αγκίστρι@el ΔΗΜΟΣ ΑΓΚΙΣΤΡΙΟΥ  Κυρά@el ΔΗΜΟΣ ΥΔΡΑΣ Ύδρα@el ΔΗΜΟΣ ΥΔΡΑΣ Πλατονήσι@el ΔΗΜΟΣ ΥΔΡΑΣ Τρικέρι@el ΔΗΜΟΣ ΥΔΡΑΣ Δοκός@el"
  },
  "336": {
    "Question": "What is the name and the area of the parks that are in Wards of Northern Ireland that are east of Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?locality ((strdf:area(?locality_geoWKT)) as ?parkArea)   WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin> geo:hasGeometry ?city_geometry .  ?city_geometry geo:asWKT ?geoWKT .  ?ward rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSNI_Ward> .   ?ward geo:hasGeometry ?ward_geo .  ?ward_geo geo:asWKT ?ward_geoWKT .  FILTER(strdf:right(?ward_geoWKT,?geoWKT))   ?locality rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_park> .  ?locality geo:hasGeometry ?locality_geo .    ?locality_geo geo:asWKT ?locality_geoWKT .   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?locality_geoWKT,?ward_geoWKT) )  } ORDER BY DESC(?parkArea)",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Castlewellan CASTLEWELLAN Castlewellan Forest Park 6.380659760907292E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osnientity_ORMEAU_N08000342 ORMEAU Ormeau Park 5.61912456760183E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "337": {
    "Question": "What are the largest parks that  belong to counties north of Budgebury Forest?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?locality WHERE {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bedgebury_Forest> geo:hasGeometry ?for_geo .  ?for_geo geo:asWKT ?for_geoWKT .   ?county rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_County> .  ?county geo:hasGeometry ?county_geo .  ?county_geo geo:asWKT ?county_geoWKT .  FILTER(strdf:below(?for_geoWKT,?county_geoWKT))   ?locality rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_park> .   ?locality geo:hasGeometry ?locality_geo .  ?locality_geo geo:asWKT ?locality_geoWKT .  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?locality_geoWKT,?county_geoWKT))  } ORDER BY DESC(?parkarea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "West Stow Country Park2.466369478497654E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Suffolk County Boughton Park2.1087867207825184E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Northamptonshire County Sheringham Park1.9976946350652725E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Norfolk County Locko Park1.805583160603419E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Derbyshire County Rushcliffe Country Park1.1112676293123513E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Nottinghamshire County Charlecote Deer Park1.0595294588711113E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Warwickshire County Chantry Park6.723453407175839E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Suffolk County Harlow Town Park5.8351619372842833E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Essex County Christchurch Park4.449619518709369E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Suffolk County Highfield Park3.654313331935555E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Hertfordshire County Landseer Park3.1556646717945114E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Suffolk County Holywells Park2.9920069209765643E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Suffolk County Gippeswyk Park2.6190600692643784E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Suffolk County Gloucester Park9.161124580714386E-6^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Gloucestershire County Gheluvelt Park9.159805813396815E-6^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Worcestershire County Rickmansworth Park2.5035051294253208E-6^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Hertfordshire County"
  },
  "338": {
    "Question": "Which lakes in England are also west of Manchester?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?lake where{  ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake .  ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?ol.  ?ol geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.   yago:England geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Manchester> geo:hasGeometry ?o2.  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2.    FILTER(strdf:left(?geoWKT,?geoWKT2))  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": "lake http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Coniston_Water http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bassenthwaite_Lake http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wast_Water http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Windermere http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Grasmere_(lake) http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rydal_Water http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ullswater http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ennerdale_Water http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tindale_Tarn_2635798 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Brothers_Water_2654536"
  },
  "339": {
    "Question": "Which villages in Northumberland also border Alnwick?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?village where{  yago:Northumberland geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.   ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village .  ?village geo:hasGeometry ?ov.  ?ov geo:asWKT ?geoWKTv.   yago:Alnwick geo:hasGeometry ?o2.  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2.    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKTv, ?geoWKT1))  FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?geoWKTv, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": "village http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Edlingham http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lesbury"
  },
  "340": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities in Central Macedonia have a population of more than 50.000 people?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?municipality where{  ?municipality rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality ;   y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population ;  geo:hasGeometry ?om . ?om geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.   yago:Central_Macedonia geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT1))  FILTER(?population > 50000) }",
    "Answer": "municipality  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pella_(municipality) http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Neapoli-Sykies http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Veroia_8133932 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Kilkis_8133969 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pavlos_Melas_(municipality) http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Katerini_8133847 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Serres_8133866 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kordelio-Evosmos"
  },
  "341": {
    "Question": "Which municipality bordering Agia Paraskevi has the largest population ?",
    "Query": "Select distinct ?dimos Where { <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Agia_Paraskevi> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  ?dimos rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT. ?dimos y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?pop.  FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:transform(?geoWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/2100>), strdf:transform(?cWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/2100>))) } ORDER BY DESC(?pop)  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chalandri"
  },
  "342": {
    "Question": "Which county council bordering the city of Cork has the largest area?",
    "Query": "Select distinct ?CountryCouncil  (strdf:area(?cWKT) AS ?area) Where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cork_City_7778678> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  ?CountryCouncil rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT.  FILTER(strdf:touches(strdf:transform(?geoWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?cWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) } ORDER BY DESC(?area) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Kerry"
  },
  "343": {
    "Question": "Give me the population of islands located in Greece.",
    "Query": "select distinct ?pop where { ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island. ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom. ?x y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?pop. ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT. yago:Greece geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?iWKT . FILTER(geof:sfWithin(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?iWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": "564267^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "344": {
    "Question": "Give me the names of the forests that are in radius of 10km from Lincolnshire.",
    "Query": "select distinct ?name where { ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest. ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom. ?x y2geoo:hasOSM_Name ?name. ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT. yago:Lincolnshire geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?iWKT . FILTER(geof:distance(?xWKT, ?iWKT, uom:metre) <= 10000) }",
    "Answer": "Kelham Hills"
  },
  "345": {
    "Question": "Is the area of any canal that intersect with Dublin is more than zero?",
    "Query": "ASK { ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal. ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom. ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT. yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?iWKT . FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?iWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))  && FILTER(strdf:area(?xWKT) > 0 ) }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "346": {
    "Question": "Which village in Rhodes has the biggest population?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x ?property where {         ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village.    ?x y2geoo:GAG_BelongsTo <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rhodes>.    ?x y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?property .                         }  ORDER BY ASC(?property) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Afantou 1027^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "347": {
    "Question": "Which village in england has the largest area?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?village ((strdf:area(?cWKT))as ?totalArea) where {  ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC.  ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT. <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/England> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomE. ?geomE geo:asWKT ?eWKT. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cWKT, ?eWKT)) } ORDER BY DESC(?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Welford,_Northamptonshire 0.013535902835428715^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "348": {
    "Question": "Which park within Dublin is the smallest in area?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?park ((strdf:area(?cWKT))as ?totalArea) where {  ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park. ?park   <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC.  ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT. <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomE. ?geomE geo:asWKT ?eWKT. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cWKT, ?eWKT))  } ORDER BY ASC(?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "1.3450117876345757E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "349": {
    "Question": "Which is the largest region in Greece?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?region ((strdf:area(?rWKT)) AS ?totalArea) WHERE {   ?region rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Region;   geo:hasGeometry ?geomR.   ?geomR geo:asWKT ?rWKT. }  ORDER BY DESC(?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Central_Macedonia  2.0089643001556396^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "350": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities in Greece have a population less than 30000?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x  where{     ?x y2geoo:hasGADM_Description Dímos.   ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.     ?x y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?pop.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Greece> geo:hasGeometry ?grgeo.     ?grgeo geo:asWKT ?grWKT.      FILTER(?pop <30000 && strdf:contains(strdf:buffer(?grWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?xWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>))) }",
    "Answer": "n Τυρνάβου Konitsa@en Καρπάθου Leros@en Ιθάκης Molos-Agios Konstantinos@en Μαρκοπούλου Μεσογαίας Μήλου Vrilissia@en Thermi@en Syros-Ermoupoli@en Βέλου - Βοχας Filothei-Psychiko@en Μεταμορφώσεως Αμφίπολης Arriana@en Chersonisos@en Gortyna@en Γόρτυνας Πλατανιά Dytiki Mani@en Spata-Artemida@en Pylos-Nestor@en Deskati@en Πηνειού Dytiki Achaia@en Nikolaos Skoufas@en Kimolos@en Σουλίου Ικαριάς Megara@en Oropedio Lasithiou@en Ιάσμου Prosotsani@en Παξών Maroneia-Sapes@en Tanagra@en Kalavryta@en Monemvasia@en Ζαγορίου Ζίτσας Kassandra@en Αρριανών Αγιάς Ψαρών Aliartos@en Iasmos@en Ελαφονήσου Aegina@en Φυλής Σίφνου Αστυπαλαίας Νεστορίου Θήρας Ηρακλείας Domokos@en Kaisariani@en Τοπείρου Κάτω Νευροκοπίου Πολυγύρου Οινουσσών Erymanthos@en Amaroussio@en Makrakomi@en Καλαμπάκας Souli@en Chalki@en Alexandria@en Leipsoi@en Σπάτων - Αρτέμιδος Φολεγάνδρου Faistos@en Αλοννήσου Λυκόβρυσης - Πεύκης Αποκορώνου Tilos@en Μεσσήνης Pineios@en Skydra@en Σικίνου Μάνδρας - Ειδυλλίας Andritsaina-Krestena@en Σκύρου Xiromero@en Παρανεστίου Ερυμάνθου Μεγαλόπολης Epidaurus@en Kythnos@en Χάλκης Filiates@en Viannos@en Mykonos@en Mandra-Eidyllia@en Ύδρας Σικυωνίων Κύθνου Zitsa@en Agios Efstratios@en Αλιάρτου Σύμης Sitia@en Voreia Tzoumerka@en Ios@en Symi@en Προσοτσάνης Στυλίδος Paros@en Καρπενησίου Σύρου - Ερμούπολης Λειψών Thira@en Paxi@en Folegandros@en Limni Plastiras@en Μεγανησίου Πάρου Andravida-Kyllini@en Kasos@en Agios Vasileios@en Myki@en Μύκης Almyros@en Kalambaka@en Ασπροπύργου Ithaca@en Psara@en Abdera@en Dionysos@en Πύλης Νάξου και Μικρών Κυκλάδων Skopelos@en Σφακίων Κασσάνδρας Malevizi@en Καισαριανής Βισαλτίας Visaltia@en Sintiki@en Dodoni@en Έδεσσας Pydna-Kolindros@en Amorgos@en Loutraki-Agioi Theodoroi@en Gortynia@en Pyli@en Δωδώνης Άνδρου Lemnos@en Κέας Ορχομενού Γεωργίου Καραϊσκάκη Νέστου Αγκιστρίου Μαλεβιζίου Καλαβρύτων Κρωπίας Amphipolis@en Amari@en Κιμώλου Parga@en Voio@en Anogeia@en Aspropyrgos@en Αλμωπίας Samothrace@en Gavdos@en Διδυμοτείχου Εμμανουήλ Παππά Βόρειας Κυνουρίας Antiparos@en Σιντικής Καλαμάτας Τεμπών Agistri@en Spetses@en Μώλου - Αγίου Κωνσταντίνου Agios Nikolaos@en Ηγουμενίτσας Αμάριου Servia-Velventos@en Mantoudi-Limni-Agia Anna@en Αγίου Ευστρατίου Σαρωνικού Κω Zagori@en Ρήγα Φεραίου Ηλίδας Καλυμνίων Thermo@en Paiania@en Πύλου - Νέστορος Platanias@en Κισσάμου Dorida@en Γαύδου Skiathos@en Τήλου Βριλησσίων Άργους - Μυκηνών Καντάνου - Σελίνου Αρχανών - Αστερουσίων Διστόμου - Αράχοβας - Αντικύρας Polygyros@en Νοτίου Πηλίου Ορεστίδος Σιθωνίας Igoumenitsa@en Περάματος Kea@en Κάσου Κυθήρων Doxato@en Φαρσάλων Λέρου Ikaria@en Xylokastro-Evrostina@en Νότιας Κυνουρίας Παλαμά Andros@en Zacharo@en Agrafa@en Μακρακώμης Αγίου Νικολάου Φούρνων Κορσεών Sofades@en Επιδαύρου Hydra@en Saronikos@en Amyntaio@en Νισύρου Σπετσών Alonnisos@en Kantanos-Selino@en Metsovo@en Lavreotiki@en Georgios Karaiskakis@en Agia@en Τροιζηνία-Μέθανα Amfikleia-Elateia@en Patmos@en Μαντουδίου - Λίμνης Μυλοποτάμου Ermionida@en Αγίου Βασιλείου Kissamos@en Farsala@en Anatoliki Mani@en Ανωγείων Almopia@en Σοφάδων Σκιάθου Emmanouil Pappas@en Πάργας Μαρώνειας - Σαπών Χερσονήσου Fyli@en Δεσκάτης Preveza@en Φιλιατών Ξυλοκάστρου - Ευρωστίνης Αργιθέας Elefsina@en Οιχαλίας Agathonisi@en Kalymnos@en Perama@en Μαραθώνος Troizinia-Methana@en Astypalaia@en Mylopotamos@en Αλεξάνδρειας Αντιπάρου Πωγωνίου Ζαγοράς - Μουρεσίου Tempi@en Λήμνου Rafina-Pikermi@en Διονύσου Ναυπακτίας Nestos@en Αλμυρού Γορτυνίας Dio-Olympos@en Paranesti@en Velo-Vocha@en Edessa@en Βοΐου Βιάννου Θέρμης Palamas@en Karystos@en Διρφύων - Μεσσαπίων Anafi@en Serifos@en Ανατολικής Μάνης Λοκρών Λαυρεωτικής Tyrnavos@en Αβδήρων Sikyona@en Πάτμου Τήνου Tripoli@en Oinousses@en Nafpaktia@en Μινώα Πεδιάδας Σερβίων - Βελβεντού Αμφιλοχίας Oraiokastro@en Marathon@en Thasos@en Rigas Feraios@en Καρύστου Tinos@en Αμαρουσίου Σκύδρας Kropia@en Μεγαρέων Kentrika Tzoumerka@en Άκτιου - Βόνιτσας Ερμιονίδας Archanes-Asterousia@en Oichalia@en Prespes@en Meganisi@en Nemea@en Istiaia-Aidipsos@en Ανάφης Φαρκαδόνας Λευκάδας Θάσου Kalamata@en Πύδνας - Κολινδρού Ζηρού Νέας Ζίχνης Δίου - Ολύμπου Δυτικής Αχαΐας Πρεσπών Σουφλίου Nestorio@en Sithonia@en Μουζακίου Ραφήνας - Πικερμίου Δοξάτου Μυκόνου Οροπεδίου Λασιθίου Nea Zichni@en Eretria@en Distomo-Arachova-Antikyra@en Λουτρακίου - Αγίων Θεοδώρων Τρίπολης Topeiros@en Μετσόβου Lefkada@en Πρέβεζας Δυτικής Μάνης Κυλλήνης Evrotas@en Aristotelis@en Sfakia@en Αμυνταίου Markopoulo Mesogaias@en Ευρώτα Αγράφων Naxos and Mikres Kyklades@en Argithea@en Voria Kynouria@en Aktio-Vonitsa@en Cythera@en Θέρμου Ilida@en Ιστιαίας - Αιδηψού Apokoronas@en Soufli@en Αριστοτέλη Δωρίδος Αμφίκλειας - Ελάτειας Δομοκού Κιλελέρ Ιητών Αρχαίας Ολυμπίας Minoa Pediada@en South Kynouria@en Karpenisi@en Lokroi@en Notios Pilios@en Αίγινας Ωραιοκάστρου Messini@en Megalopolis@en Νεμέας Φαιστού Mouzaki@en Λίμνης Πλαστήρα Κεντρικών Τζουμέρκων Poros@en Τανάγρας Elafonisos@en Ανδριτσαίνας - Κρεστένων Σκοπέλου Orestida@en Didymoteicho@en Παιανίας Dirfys-Messapia@en Ξηρομέρου Olympia@en Kato Nevrokopi@en Ερέτριας Skyros@en Ζαχάρως Ierapetra@en Βορείων Τζουμέρκων Σερίφου Metamorfosi@en Ziros@en Μονεμβασιάς Ελευσίνας Νικολάου Σκουφά Κόνιτσας Pogoni@en Farkadona@en Nisyros@en Πόρου Kileler@en Sikinos@en Irakleia@en Argos-Mykines@en Amfilochia@en Zagora-Mouresi@en Karpathos@en Volvi@en Βόλβης Σητείας Αγαθονησίου Ιεράπετρας Lykovrysi-Pefki@en Stylida@en Kos@en Αμοργού Σαμοθράκης Φιλοθέης - Ψυχικού Sifnos@en Milos@en Orchomenus@en Fournoi Korseon@en"
  },
  "351": {
    "Question": "Which 5 counties in the United Kingdom above City of London have the biggest area?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?y ((strdf:area(?yWKT))as ?totalArea) where{      ?y a y2geoo:OS_County.     ?y geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.     ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_City_of_London_2643744> geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.   FILTER (strdf:above(strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)))   }ORDER BY DESC(?totalArea) LIMIT 5",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_Yorkshire    1.109086275100708^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_Yorkshire    1.1087838411331177^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cumbria    0.9984490275382996^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cumbria    0.9392470121383667^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lincolnshire    0.8192595839500427^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "352": {
    "Question": "Which are the 3 most densely populated municipalities of Crete Island?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?Dimos ?pop WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Crete> geo:hasGeometry ?CreteGeo. ?CreteGeo geo:asWKT ?CreteWKT.  ?Dimos rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality. ?Dimos y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?pop. ?Dimos geo:hasGeometry ?DimosGeo. ?DimosGeo geo:asWKT ?DimosWKT.  FILTER (geof:sfWithin(?CreteWKT, ?DimosWKT)).  } ORDER BY DESC (?pop) Limit 3",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Heraklion_8133920 132361^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Chania_8133762 95456^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Rethymno_8133759 46558^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "353": {
    "Question": "Which is the perimeter and the name of some nature reserves, which are on the left of some townlands?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?perim WHERE {   ?nr rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_nature_reserve. ?nr geo:hasGeometry ?nrGeo. ?nrGeo geo:asWKT ?nrWKt.  ?Townland y2geoo:hasOSNI_Perimeter ?perim. ?Townland geo:hasGeometry ?TownlandGeo. ?TownlandGeo geo:asWKT ?TownlandWKt.  FILTER( strdf:distance(?nrWKt, ?TownlandWKt,uom:metre) < 20000) ) } LIMIT 10",
    "Answer": "Derryloughan 4347.434^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>  Lisnabraugh4154.534^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Aghacarnaghan(Detached-portion)1950.125^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> Carrickbwee Glebe5293.169^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double Tullydraw3289.522^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double Ballylesson7861.257^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>  …………. …………. …………."
  },
  "354": {
    "Question": "Which is the biggest park in Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?park ?lWKT(strdf:area(?lWKT) AS ?area)  WHERE { yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park; geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT)) } ORDER BY DESC(?area) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "park                                                                                                                     lWKT                                                                                                                                                                                            area http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ringsend_Park_3289060  POLYGON ((-6.2164685 53.3428643, -6.2164836 53.342831200000006, -6.216532300000001 53.3427032, -6....   more  1.3450117876345757E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "355": {
    "Question": "Which regional units of Peloponnese are south of Xylokastro Evrostina municipality and have population more than 30.000?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?x1 WHERE {   ?x1 a y2geoo:GAG_RegionalUnit.   ?x1 <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/GAG_BelongsTo> <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Peloponnese_(region)>.   ?x1 <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/hasGAG_Population> ?p.     ?x1 geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.         ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.        <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Xylokastro-Evrostina> geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.         ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.         FILTER(strdf:below(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT)).            FILTER (?p > 30000) }",
    "Answer": "name ΠΕΡΙΦΕΡΕΙΑΚΗ ΕΝΟΤΗΤΑ ΛΑΚΩΝΙΑΣ ΠΕΡΙΦΕΡΕΙΑΚΗ ΕΝΟΤΗΤΑ ΑΡΚΑΔΙΑΣ ΠΕΡΙΦΕΡΕΙΑΚΗ ΕΝΟΤΗΤΑ ΑΡΓΟΛΙΔΑΣ ΠΕΡΙΦΕΡΕΙΑΚΗ ΕΝΟΤΗΤΑ ΜΕΣΣΗΝΙΑΣ"
  },
  "356": {
    "Question": "Which counties north of Oxford are comprised of more than 5 districts?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?x1 (COUNT(?x3) AS ?c)  WHERE {                ?x1 a y2geoo:OS_County.               ?x1 geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.                     ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.              ?x3 a y2geoo:OS_District.              ?x3 geo:hasGeometry ?x3Geo.                     ?x3Geo geo:asWKT ?x3WKT.     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oxfordshire>  geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.              ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.    FILTER(strdf:above(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT)).          FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?x3WKT,?x1WKT)).  } GROUP BY(?x1) HAVINV(?c > 5)",
    "Answer": "name name3 Cumbria@en Barrow-in-Furness@en Cumbria@en Allerdale@en Cumbria@en South Lakeland@en Cumbria@en Copeland@en Cumbria@en Carlisle@en Derbyshire@en Chesterfield@en Derbyshire@en Bolsover@en Derbyshire@en Derbyshire Dales@en Derbyshire@en South Derbyshire@en Derbyshire@en Erewash@en Derbyshire@en Amber Valley@en Derbyshire@en North East Derbyshire@en Derbyshire@en High Peak@en Lancashire@en Preston@en Lancashire@en Ribble Valley@en Lancashire@en South Ribble@en Lancashire@en Burnley@en Lancashire@en Fylde@en Lancashire@en Rossendale@en Lancashire@en Chorley@en Lancashire@en Lancaster@en Lancashire@en Pendle@en Lancashire@en Wyre@en Lancashire@en Hyndburn@en Lancashire@en West Lancashire@en Leicestershire@en Harborough@en Leicestershire@en Hinckley and Bosworth@en Leicestershire@en North West Leicestershire@en Leicestershire@en Blaby@en Leicestershire@en Oadby and Wigston@en Leicestershire@en Charnwood@en Norfolk@en Norwich@en Norfolk@en Broadland@en Norfolk@en North Norfolk@en Norfolk@en Great Yarmouth@en Norfolk@en South Norfolk@en Norfolk@en Breckland@en Norfolk@en King's Lynn and West Norfolk@en North Yorkshire@en Scarborough@en North Yorkshire@en Ryedale@en North Yorkshire@en Richmondshire@en North Yorkshire@en Hambleton@en North Yorkshire@en Craven@en North Yorkshire@en Harrogate@en Nottinghamshire@en Ashfield@en Nottinghamshire@en Rushcliffe@en Nottinghamshire@en Newark and Sherwood@en Nottinghamshire@en Broxtowe@en Nottinghamshire@en Mansfield@en Nottinghamshire@en Gedling@en Nottinghamshire@en Bassetlaw@en Staffordshire@en Cannock Chase@en Staffordshire@en Lichfield@en Staffordshire@en Newcastle-under-Lyme@en Staffordshire@en Tamworth@en Staffordshire@en East Staffordshire@en Staffordshire@en South Staffordshire@en Staffordshire@en Staffordshire Moorlands@en Staffordshire@en Stafford@en"
  },
  "357": {
    "Question": "Which local government districts of Northern Ireland that are north of Belfast, have area of more than 1.000.000 m2?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?x1  WHERE {    ?x1 a y2geoo:OSNI_LocalGovermentDistrict.   ?x1 <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/hasOSNI_Area> ?area.    ?x1 geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.         ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_City_of_Belfast_3333223>     geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.         ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.    FILTER (strdf:above(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT)).     FILTER (?area > 1000000) }",
    "Answer": "name Causeway Coast and Glens Mid and East Antrim"
  },
  "358": {
    "Question": "What is the area of each forest in the Scarawalsh Barony?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?forest ((strdf:area(?forestWKT)) as ?forestArea) WHERE{         <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Scarawalsh_Bridge_3304299> geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?baronyWKT .          ?forest a y2geoo:OSM_forest .         ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?o3 .         ?o3 geo:asWKT ?forestWKT .          FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?forestWKT, ?baronyWKT))      }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Scarawalsh_Bridge_3304299 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Killoughrum_Forest_2963306 8.170903311111033E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Scarawalsh_Bridge_3304299 http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tombrick_Wood_3302725 6.069708615541458E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "359": {
    "Question": "Which is the population of the municipalities that border Kastoria?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?municipality ?population WHERE {    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kastoria> geo:hasGeometry ?o3 .    ?o3 geo:asWKT ?kastoriaWKT .       ?municipality a y2geoo:GAG_Municipality .    ?municipality geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .    ?o1 geo:asWKT ?munWKT .    ?municipality y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population .     FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?kastoriaWKT, ?munWKT )) }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Eordaia_8133857 44497^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer> http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Prespes 2511^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer> http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Florina_8133716 33282^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer> http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nestorio 3542^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer> http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Argos_Orestiko 6571^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer> http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Amyntaio_8133871 17976^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "360": {
    "Question": "Which parks are in Suffolk and above Ipswich district?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?park WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Suffolk>  geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?countyGeo .    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ipswich_District_7290634>   geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .         ?o2 geo:asWKT ?districtGeo .          ?park a y2geoo:OSM_park .         ?park geo:hasGeometry ?o3 .         ?o3 geo:asWKT ?parkGeo .           FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?parkGeo , ?countyGeo))         FILTER(strdf:above(?parkGeo , ?districtGeo ))  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_West_Stow_Country_Park_9883966"
  },
  "361": {
    "Question": "Show me the biggest park in Liverpool",
    "Query": "SELECT ?park ?parkArea WHERE{  yago:Liverpool geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?lWKT.  ?park a y2geoo:OSM_park;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?pWKT.   FILTER(strdf:inside(?pWKT, ?lWKT)). BIND(strdf:area(?pWKT) AS ?parkArea). }ORDER BY DESC(?parkArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "Sefton Park                                  1.1577826080610976E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "362": {
    "Question": "Which county councils of Ireland has the most nature reserves?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?county (COUNT(?lake) AS ?numLakes) WHERE {  ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_nature_reserve .  ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council .  ?county geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  FILTER (strdf:mbbWithin(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2)) } GROUP BY ?county  ORDER BY DESC(?numLakes) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "county  numReserves http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cork_City_7778678  2^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "363": {
    "Question": "Which district of the United Kingdom has the most villages?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?district (COUNT(?village) AS ?numVillages) WHERE {  ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village .  ?village geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?district rdf:type y2geoo:OS_District .  ?district geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  FILTER (strdf:mbbWithin(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2)) } GROUP BY ?district  ORDER BY DESC(?numVillages) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "district  numVillages http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_Kesteven  89^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "364": {
    "Question": "Which region of Greece has the biggest area?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?region ?regionArea WHERE {  ?region rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Region .  ?region geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT .  BIND(strdf:area(?geoWKT) AS ?regionArea) . }  ORDER BY DESC(?regionArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "region  regionArea http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Peloponnese_(region)  2.9823663234710693^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "365": {
    "Question": "Which are the Top Periferiakes enothtes with the less population that belongs to South Aegean and intersects with beaches?",
    "Query": "select ?makari ?forest where{  ?makari <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/GAG_BelongsTo> <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/South_Aegean>. ?makari geo:hasGeometry ?dhmo_geo .   ?dhmo_geo geo:asWKT ?dhmo_geoWKT . ?makari <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/hasGAG_Population> ?pop.  ?forest rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_beach> . ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?forest_geo . ?forest_geo geo:asWKT ?forest_geoWKT . #?beach <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/hasOSM_Name> ?beach_name .    FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(?forest_geoWKT,?dhmo_geoWKT))  }  ORDER BY ASC(?pop)  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Perifereiakí_Enótita_Tínou_8139378 8574^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "366": {
    "Question": "Which Rural Area south of Longford have the smallest forest?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?rural_areas ((strdf:area(?geoWKT)as ?totalArea) where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Longford> geo:hasGeometry ?Suffolk_geo .   ?Suffolk_geo geo:asWKT ?Suffolk_geoWKT .      ?rural_areas rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_Rural_Area> .    ?rural_areas geo:hasGeometry ?rural_areas_geo .      ?rural_areas_geo geo:asWKT ?rural_areas_geoWKT .  FILTER(strdf:below(?rural_areas_geoWKT,?Suffolk_geoWKT))    ?forest rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_forest> .   ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .   ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT2, ?rural_areas_geoWKT)) } ORDER BY ASC(?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "rural_areastotalArea http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kilgarvan1.7238386135431938E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "367": {
    "Question": "Which county has inside the biggest area forest?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?county ((strdf:area(?geoWKT)as ?totalArea) where {  ?county rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_County>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC.  ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT.    ?forest rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_forest> .   ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .   ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT2, ?cWKT)) } ORDER BY DESC(?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Essex7.697400287725031E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "368": {
    "Question": "Which county of Ireland has the highest number of lakes?",
    "Query": "PREFIX geo: <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#> PREFIX rdf: <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#> PREFIX strdf: <http://strdf.di.uoa.gr/ontology#> PREFIX y2geoo: <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/>  SELECT DISTINCT ?county (COUNT(?lake) AS ?numLakes) WHERE {  ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake; geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT .  ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council; geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT1)) } GROUP BY ?county  ORDER BY DESC(?numLakes) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "county  numLakes http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/County_Mayo 161^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer"
  },
  "369": {
    "Question": "Which district of the United Kingdom has the biggest area?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?district (strdf:area(?geoWKT) AS ?totalArea) WHERE {  ?district rdf:type y2geoo:OS_District; geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . } ORDER BY DESC(?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "district  totalArea http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Eden_District_7290666 0.3000527322292328^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double"
  },
  "370": {
    "Question": "Which island of Greece has the highest number of beaches?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?island (COUNT(?beach) AS ?numBeaches) WHERE {  yago:Greece geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT .  ?island rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island; geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach; geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT) && strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT1)) } GROUP BY ?island  ORDER BY DESC(?numBeaches) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "island numBeaches http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Crete 3^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer"
  },
  "371": {
    "Question": "Which region has the biggest population in Greece?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?region ?population  where {    ?region  rdf:type  y2geoo:GAG_Region .    ?region  y2geoo:hasGAG_Population  ?population .}  ORDER BY DESC(?population )LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "name populationΠΕΡΙΦΕΡΕΙΑ ΑΤΤΙΚΗΣ 3526379^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "372": {
    "Question": "Which county of England has the biggest number of lakes?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?county (count (?lWKT) as ?numberOfLakes) where { ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OS_County . ?county geo:hasGeometry  ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake. ?lake geo:hasGeometry  ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT)) }GROUP BY (?county) ORDER BY DESC(?numberOfLakes)LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "name numberOfLakesCumbria County 20^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "373": {
    "Question": "Which lake of Amintaio covers the greatest area?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?l (strdf:area(?lw) AS ?area) WHERE {    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Amyntaio_8133871>  geo:hasGeometry ?cg .    ?cg geo:asWKT ?cw .     ?l a y2geoo:OSM_lake .    ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .    ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lw,?cw)) } ORDER BY DESC(?area) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "Λίμνη Ζάζαρη              1.750225346768275E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "374": {
    "Question": "Which forest of Norfolk covers the largest area?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?l (strdf:area(?lw) AS ?area) WHERE {    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norfolk> geo:hasGeometry ?mg .    ?mg geo:asWKT ?mw .     ?l a y2geoo:OSM_forest .    ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .    ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lw,?mw)) } ORDER BY DESC(?area) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "Holkham Meals, Open Access  5.050938489148393E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "375": {
    "Question": "Which 5 counties have the most forests?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?county (COUNT(?forest) AS ?num)  WHERE { ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OS_County . ?county geo:hasGeometry ?geoC . ?geoC geo:asWKT ?cWKT . ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest . ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?geoF . ?geoF geo:asWKT ?fWKT . FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?fWKT, ?cWKT)) } GROUP BY ?county ORDER BY DESC (?num) LIMIT 5",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Essex 6^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer> http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norfolk 5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer> http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kent 4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer> http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lancashire 2^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer> http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cambridge 2^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "376": {
    "Question": "Find the number of forests in England.",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(distinct ?x) as ?forests) WHERE {     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/England>     <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.     ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest .     ?x <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "30^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "377": {
    "Question": "How many Localities are in County Roscommon and which is their total and average area?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(DISTINCT ?locality) AS ?total) (AVG(strdf:area(?WKT1)) AS ?avg) (SUM(strdf:area(?WKT1)) AS ?sum) WHERE {     yago:County_Roscommon geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WKT1.     ?locality rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_locality.     ?locality geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT  ?WKT2.     FILTER(strdf:intersects(strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": "total 24^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer> avg 0.3469096792086972^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> sum 8.325832301008733^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "378": {
    "Question": "What is the average number of beaches in the municipalities west of Dimos Pyrgos?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?reg_unit (AVG(?no_of_beaches) AS ?avg_no_of_beaches) WHERE {  SELECT  ?reg_unit (COUNT(?locality) AS ?no_of_beaches)  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pyrgos,_Elis>  geo:hasGeometry ?pirgos_geo .   ?pirgos_geo geo:asWKT ?pirgos_geoWKT .    ?reg_unit rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/GAG_Municipality> .   ?reg_unit geo:hasGeometry ?reg_unitgeo .   ?reg_unitgeo geo:asWKT ?reg_unitgeoWKT .   FILTER(strdf:left(?reg_unitgeoWKT,?pirgos_geoWKT))    ?locality rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_beach> .    ?locality geo:hasGeometry ?locality_geo .   ?locality_geo geo:asWKT ?locality_geoWKT .    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?locality_geoWKT,?reg_unitgeoWKT))  } GROUP BY (?reg_unit) }",
    "Answer": "9.6^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#decimal>"
  },
  "379": {
    "Question": "Which Civil Parishes in Ireland have more that 10 townlands?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?civilParish WHERE {         ?civilParish rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_Civil_Parish .         ?townland rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_Townland .         ?townland geo:sfWithin ?civilParish . } GROUP BY ?civilParish HAVING (COUNT(?townland) > 10)",
    "Answer": "civilParish http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kilquane_3290669 http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE19629420413A3E055000000000001"
  },
  "380": {
    "Question": "How many lakes and how many streams are there in the city of Cork?",
    "Query": "Select   (count(distinct ?lake) as ?total_lakes)  (count(distinct ?stream ) as ?total_streams) (count(distinct ?forest) as ?total_forests) Where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cork_City_7778678> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?A.  ?lake rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_lake>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomB. ?geomB geo:asWKT ?B.  ?stream rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_stream>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?C.  ?forest rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_forest>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomD. ?geomD geo:asWKT ?D.  FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:transform(?B, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?A, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))).  FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:transform(?C, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?A, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))).  FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:transform(?D, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?A, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))).  }",
    "Answer": "19^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>    39^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "381": {
    "Question": "How many parks and how many streams are there in the Essex?",
    "Query": "Select  (count(distinct ?park) as ?total_parks) (count(distinct ?stream) as ?total_streams)  Where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Essex> geo:hasGeometry ?o. ?o geo:asWKT ?A.  ?park rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_park>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomB. ?geomB geo:asWKT ?B.  ?stream rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_stream>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?C.  FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:transform(?B, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?A, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))).  FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:transform(?C, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?A, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))).  }",
    "Answer": "1^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>    3^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "382": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities have more than 5 beaches?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?mun  (count(?beach ) as ?beaches) WHERE{   { SELECT DISTINCT ?mun  ?beach  WHERE { ?mun rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality . ?mun geo:hasGeometry ?a . ?a geo:asWKT ?A .  ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach . ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?b . ?b geo:asWKT ?B .  FILTER(strdf:contains(strdf:transform(?A,<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),strdf:transform(?B,<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) . }  }  }group by ?mun having(?beaches>5)",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Milos_8133681  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Zagora-Mouresi  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Alonnisos_8133938  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chios  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tinos  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Dimos_Paxoi_8133911"
  },
  "383": {
    "Question": "How many lakes does Greece have?",
    "Query": "select (count(?x) as ?cnt) where { ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake . ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom. ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT. yago:Greece geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?iWKT . FILTER(geof:sfWithin(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?iWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>) )) }",
    "Answer": "17^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "384": {
    "Question": "Which is the closest forest to Manchester",
    "Query": "select ?x where { ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest . ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom. ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT. yago:Manchester geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?iWKT . } order by geof:distance(?xWKT, ?iWKT, uom:metre) limit 1",
    "Answer": "POLYGON ((8.9476215 55.193613400000004, 8.9469496 55.1942333, 8.944543300000001 55.1943715, 8.9434 4965 55.1941575, 8.9429808 55.193386000000004, 8.9422542 55.19363130000001, 8.9419725 55.194281200000006, 8.9421523 55.194396100000006, 8.942645800000001 55.194319500000006, 8.9429105 55.1947015, 8.9419027 55.194960200000004, 8.941168300000001 55.1942734, 8.9395589 55.194790700000006, 8.9399206 55.195248600000006, 8.940553600000001 55.1956811, 8.9370168 55.1963896, 8.936617700000001 55.2095269, 8.935558700000001 55.209802700000004, 8.9355937 55.2103017, 8.9366876 55.2104033, 8.9367003 55.211172600000005, 8.9378388 55.2112089, 8.938468400000001 55.2119183, 8.939963 55.2114647, 8.9408141 55.2113469, 8.9409737 55.2114265, 8.9417832 55.212378400000006, 8.942435300000001 55.2118717, 8.9514826 55.215461700000006, 8.962740700000001 55.2124152, 8.962348 55.212184900000004, 8.9618692 55.212409, 8.961263 55.211989700000004, 8.9616707 55.211797700000005, 8.961162400000001 55.21151690000001, 8.960976 55.2114939, 8.9593975 55.211846300000005, 8.9591025 55.2115571, 8.959778400000001 55.2113535, 8.9594109 55.2109985, 8.9600117 55.2107888, 8.9601995 55.2109633, 8.960540100000001 55.2108531, 8.959840100000001 55.2102226, 8.960934400000001 55.2096992, 8.9651267 55.2088758, 8.9659448 55.208820700000004, 8.9669909 55.2080326, 8.967023000000001 55.2077357, 8.9665081 55.207140300000006, 8.9665429 55.206249500000006, 8.966964 55.2058837, 8.967004300000001 55.2053924, 8.966690400000001 55.205245500000004, 8.966217 55.20524090000001, 8.9661755 55.204547500000004, 8.9661174 55.203751100000005, 8.9660962 55.2029884, 8.966129200000001 55.2011619, 8.9669016 55.197561500000006, 8.967002500000001 55.1958836, 8.9668284 55.195197900000004, 8.9662556 55.194304300000006, 8.9653843 55.193484000000005, 8.964747500000001 55.19289740000001, 8.9633558 55.191670300000006, 8.9476215 55.193613400000004), (8.9530188 55.1950147, 8.9527289 55.194571800000006, 8.9507087 55.19402710000001, 8.9506332 55.193946100000005, 8.9503071 55.1939926, 8.9506604 55.194511500000004, 8.952593 55.1950354, 8.9530188 55.1950147), (8.9571559 55.211837900000006, 8.9563395 55.2109486, 8.9570153 55.2107213, 8.957847300000001 55.211652900000004, 8.9571559 55.211837900000006), (8.945820300000001 55.2124238, 8.9472695 55.212270700000005, 8.95041 55.210993300000005, 8.9518778 55.2129891, 8.949512200000001 55.213573600000004, 8.9487596 55.213560900000004, 8.9477948 55.212987000000005, 8.9468783 55.21289350000001, 8.9463679 55.212608700000004, 8.9458687 55.2124875, 8.945820300000001 55.2124238), (8.937971600000001 55.2050307, 8.940921600000001 55.204425400000005, 8.9417503 55.205686400000005, 8.9427283 55.205858400000004, 8.943228300000001 55.20574250000001, 8.9435486 55.206259700000004, 8.945822 55.2064425, 8.943165800000001 55.2077174, 8.938314100000001 55.2084173, 8.936751600000001 55.208185500000006, 8.9368376 55.2066743, 8.9379001 55.206718800000004, 8.937971600000001 55.2050307))^^<http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#wktLiteral>"
  },
  "385": {
    "Question": "What is the county with the max area?",
    "Query": "select distinct (MAX(?area1) as ?a1) where { ?x1 rdf:type y2geoo:OS_County . ?x1 geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geom. ?x1Geom geo:asWKT ?iWKT1. BIND(strdf:area(?iWKT1) as ?area1). }",
    "Answer": "1.109086275100708^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "386": {
    "Question": "How many lakes are there in England?",
    "Query": "select (count(distinct ?x) as ?lakes) where {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/England> <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake . ?x <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "lakes 22^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "387": {
    "Question": "Which civil parish bordering Killinane occupies the smallest area?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x ((strdf:area(?xWKT)) as ?area) where {      ?x a y2geoo:OSI_Civil_Parish.     ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Kilkieran_3302356> geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.     ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.  FILTER(strdf:touches(strdf:buffer(?xWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?yWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>)))  }ORDER BY ASC(?area) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "n area WELLS 1.9070686221311917E-6^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "388": {
    "Question": "How many parks does Dublin have and what is the sum of their total area?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT (?park) AS ?count) (SUM(strdf:area(?lWKT)) AS ?total_area_of_parks) WHERE { yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park; geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "count                                                                                  total_area_of_parks 2^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>  2.5658256989994583E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "389": {
    "Question": "Which are the 5 smallest District Wards that are north of Liverpool?",
    "Query": "select ?District_Ward ?cWKT(strdf:area(?cWKT) AS ?area)  where { yago:Liverpool geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcWKT. ?District_Ward rdf:type y2geoo:OS_DistrictWard; geo:hasGeometry ?geomC. ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT. FILTER(strdf:below(?lcWKT, ?cWKT)) } ORDER BY (?area) LIMIT 5",
    "Answer": "District_Ward                                                                            cWKT                                                                                                                                                                                     area http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Overton,_Lancashire  POLYGON ((-2.8602980000000002 54.0151345, -2.8594678 54.0151167, -2.8592962 54.015025300000005, -2...   more  5.012941983295605E-6^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Ulverston_Town_Ward_38971  POLYGON ((-3.08868749468513 54.1925905725936, -3.0895261918861 54.1924886424471, -3.0902538753229 ...   more  4.246982280164957E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Kendal_Kirkland_Ward_38970  POLYGON ((-2.75318904593649 54.3168019995101, -2.75324292856586 54.3168097493625, -2.7532172318866...   more  5.790539216832258E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Central_Ward_21102  POLYGON ((-0.409878895606006 54.2856303245886, -0.409672113473407 54.2856123221645, -0.40919974845...   more  6.354247307172045E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double> http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osentity_Peel_Ward_4639  POLYGON ((-2.36568436170931 53.7565568762175, -2.36568290017425 53.7565613734294, -2.3650099423438...   more  6.411132926587015E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "390": {
    "Question": "Which region of Greece has biggest population?",
    "Query": "select  ?region ?p  where {                                          ?region  rdf:type  <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/GAG_Region>.  ?region <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/hasGAG_Population>  ?p.  } ORDER BY DESC(?p) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "MaxPop 3526379^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "391": {
    "Question": "What is the total area of lakes in Monaghan?",
    "Query": "SELECT (sum(?lakeArea) as ?oSum) WHERE {   {     SELECT ((strdf:area(?lakeWKT)) as ?lakeArea)     WHERE{          <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/osientity_2AE1962941E413A3E055000000000001> geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .           ?o1 geo:asWKT ?baronyWKT .               ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake .             ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .             ?o2 geo:asWKT ?lakeWKT.              FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lakeWKT, ?baronyWKT ))     }   } }",
    "Answer": "8.118686747593529E-5^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "392": {
    "Question": "From the top 10 most populated municipalities of Greece is there anyone with at least one beach?",
    "Query": "PREFIX rdf: <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#> PREFIX strdf: <http://strdf.di.uoa.gr/ontology#> PREFIX geof: <http://www.opengis.net/def/function/geosparql/> PREFIX geo: <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#> PREFIX y2geoo: <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/>  ASK WHERE {     {         SELECT ?municipality ?munWKT ?population         WHERE          {             ?municipality a y2geoo:GAG_Municipality .             ?municipality y2geoo:hasGAG_Population ?population .             ?municipality geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .             ?o1 geo:asWKT ?munWKT .         }         ORDER BY DESC(?population)         LIMIT 10     }       ?beach a y2geoo:OSM_beach .     ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .     ?o2 geo:asWKT ?beachWKT .      FILTER(         geof:sfWithin(             strdf:transform(?beachWKT,<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),              strdf:transform(?munWKT,<http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)         )     )  }",
    "Answer": 0
  },
  "393": {
    "Question": "Which county of England has the most parks ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county (COUNT(?park) as ?parkCount) WHERE {    ?county a y2geoo:OS_County .    ?county geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .    ?o1 geo:asWKT ?countyWKT .     ?park a y2geoo:OSM_park .    ?park geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .    ?o2 geo:asWKT ?parkWKT .     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?parkWKT , ?countyWKT)) } GROUP BY ?county ORDER BY DESC(?parkCount) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey 14^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer>"
  },
  "394": {
    "Question": "How many lakes each county with lakes has?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?county (COUNT(?lake) AS ?lake_count) where {     ?county rdf:type yagoo:OS_County.     ?county geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcWKT.      ?lake rdf:type yagoo:OSM_lake;     geo:hasGeometry ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.      FILTER(strdf:intersects(strdf:envelope(?lWKT), strdf:envelope(?lcWKT)))  } GROUP BY ?county",
    "Answer": "countylake_count http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cambridge4^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Norfolk6^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lancashire4^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cumbria22^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_Yorkshire4^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Surrey4^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Buckinghamshire2^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hertfordshire2^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northamptonshire2^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer"
  },
  "395": {
    "Question": "Which region of Greece has the biggest area?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?region ?regionArea WHERE {  ?region rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Region .  ?region geo:hasGeometry ?o .  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT .  BIND(strdf:area(?geoWKT) AS ?regionArea) . }  ORDER BY DESC(?regionArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "region  regionArea http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Peloponnese_(region)  2.9823663234710693^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "396": {
    "Question": "What is the maximum lake area among lakes located in county Cavan?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT (MAX(?lakeArea) AS ?maxLakeArea) WHERE {  yago:County_Cavan geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake .  ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  BIND(strdf:area(?geoWKT2) AS ?lakeArea) .  FILTER (strdf:mbbWithin(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": "maxLakeArea 0.004357675090432167^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "397": {
    "Question": "Which are the min max and avg forest area that is within a district which placed south of Staffordshire county?",
    "Query": "SELECT (MIN(strdf:area(?forest_geoWKT)) AS ?areas_min) (MAX(strdf:area(?forest_geoWKT)) AS ?areas_max) (AVG(strdf:area(?forest_geoWKT)) AS ?areas_avg)  WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Staffordshire> geo:hasGeometry ?Suffolk_geo .   ?Suffolk_geo geo:asWKT ?Suffolk_geoWKT .   ?district rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_District> .   ?district geo:hasGeometry ?district_geo .   ?district_geo geo:asWKT ?district_geoWKT .      FILTER(strdf:below(?district_geoWKT,?Suffolk_geoWKT))      ?forest rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_forest> .   ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?forest_geo .   ?forest_geo geo:asWKT ?forest_geoWKT .       FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?forest_geoWKT,?district_geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": "1.8218561900008097E-6^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>7.697400551350172E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>1.9105149607361504E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "398": {
    "Question": "What is the average area of the forests that are within Rural Area south of County Longford ?",
    "Query": "SELECT (AVG(?areas) AS ?areas_avg) WHERE {   SELECT ((strdf:area(?forest_geoWKT)) AS ?areas) WHERE {   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Cork_City_7778678> geo:hasGeometry ?Cork_geo .   ?Cork_geo geo:asWKT ?Cork_geoWKT .   ?rural_area rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_Rural_Area> .   ?rural_area geo:hasGeometry ?rural_area_geo .     ?rural_area_geo geo:asWKT ?rural_area_geoWKT .      FILTER(strdf:above(?rural_area_geoWKT,?Cork_geoWKT))      ?forest rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_forest> .   ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?forest_geo .   ?forest_geo geo:asWKT ?forest_geoWKT .      FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?forest_geoWKT,?rural_area_geoWKT)) } }",
    "Answer": "2.239826457158555E-4^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "399": {
    "Question": "What is the maximum area between Ireland's counties?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT (MAX(?area) AS ?maxArea) WHERE { ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council; geo:hasGeometry ?o . ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . BIND(strdf:area(?geoWKT) as ?area) . }",
    "Answer": "maxArea 0.9745895862579346^^http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double"
  },
  "400": {
    "Question": "Which villages are near lakes?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?village WHERE { ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village . ?village geo:hasGeometry ?geoV . ?geoV geo:asWKT ?vWKT . ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake . ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?geoL . ?geoL geo:asWKT ?lWKT . FILTER(geof:distance(?lWKT, ?vWKT, uom:metre) < 2000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "401": {
    "Question": "Which streams cross forests?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?stream WHERE { ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest . ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?geoF . ?geoF geo:asWKT ?fWKT . ?stream rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream . ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?geoS . ?geoS geo:asWKT ?sWKT . FILTER(geof:sfCrosses(?sWKT, ?fWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "402": {
    "Question": "Which cities have beaches?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?city WHERE { ?city rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_city . ?city geo:hasGeometry ?geoC . ?geoC geo:asWKT ?cWKT . ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach . ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?geoB . ?geoB geo:asWKT ?bWKT . FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?bWKT, ?cWKT) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "403": {
    "Question": "Which islands are within a region?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?island WHERE{         ?region rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Region;         geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.         ?island rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.         FILTER(geof:sfWithin(strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT, 0, uom:metre)))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "404": {
    "Question": "Which Districts contain Parks?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?district WHERE{         ?district rdf:type y2geoo:OS_District;         geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.         ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.         FILTER(geof:sfContains(strdf:buffer(?WKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre)))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "405": {
    "Question": "Which townlands intersect with lakes?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?townland WHERE{         ?townland rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_Townland;         geo:hasGeometry ?o.         ?o geo:asWKT ?WKT.         ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake;         geo:hasGeometry ?o1.         ?o1 geo:asWKT ?WKT1.         FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(strdf:buffer(?WKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre)))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "406": {
    "Question": "Which forests are at most 2500 meters from lakes?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?forest WHERE {     ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest.     ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.     ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.     ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake.     ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.     ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.     FILTER(geof:distance(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT, uom:metre) <= 2500). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "407": {
    "Question": "Which parks are in cities?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?park WHERE {     ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park.     ?park geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.     ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.     ?city rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_city.     ?city geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.     ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT)). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "408": {
    "Question": "Which bays are at most 20000 meters from villages?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?bay WHERE {     ?bay rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_bay.     ?bay <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?x1Geo.     ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.     ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village.     ?village <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?x2Geo.     ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.     FILTER(geof:distance(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT, uom:metre) <= 20000). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "409": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities contain at least 1 lake ?",
    "Query": "SELECT Distinct ?mun  WHERE {  ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake . ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?vgeo . ?vgeo geo:asWKT ?vWKT . ?mun rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality. ?mun geo:hasGeometry ?mgeo . ?mgeo geo:asWKT ?mWKT . FILTER(strdf:contains(?mWKT,?vWKT)). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "410": {
    "Question": "Which counties contain at least one reservoir ?",
    "Query": "SELECT Distinct ?county WHERE {  ?res rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_reservoir. ?res geo:hasGeometry ?vgeo . ?vgeo geo:asWKT ?vWKT .  ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OS_County. ?county geo:hasGeometry ?mgeo . ?mgeo geo:asWKT ?mWKT .  FILTER(strdf:contains(?mWKT,?vWKT)). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "411": {
    "Question": "Which Irish counties are less than 2km far from any beach ?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?county ?beach WHERE {  ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_County_Council . ?county geo:hasGeometry ?cgeo . ?cgeo geo:asWKT ?cWKT . ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach. ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?bgeo . ?bgeo geo:asWKT ?bWKT . FILTER(strdf:distance(?cWKT,?bWKT,uom:metre)<2000.0). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "412": {
    "Question": "Which regions have a beach?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?region WHERE {      ?region rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Region.     ?region geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WRT1.       ?beach rdf:type  y2geoo:OSM_beach.      ?beach geo:hasGeometry / geo:asWKT ?WRT2.      FILTER(strdf:within(strdf:buffer(?WRT2, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WRT1, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "413": {
    "Question": "Which counties intersect with a lake?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?county WHERE {      ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OS_County.     ?county geo:hasGeometry ?geomc. ?geomc geo:asWKT ?WKT1.       ?forest rdf:type  y2geoo:OSM_lake.      ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?geomf. ?geomf geo:asWKT ?WKT2.      FILTER(strdf:intersects(strdf:buffer(?WKT2, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?WKT1, 0, uom:metre))) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "414": {
    "Question": "Which baronies have nature reserve?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x where { ?x rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_Barony>; geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom1. ?cGeom1 geo:asWKT ?cWKT1. ?y rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_nature_reserve>; geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom2. ?cGeom2 geo:asWKT ?cWKT2.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cWKT2,?cWKT1)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "415": {
    "Question": "Which nature reserves have forests  within 5km?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?nature_reserve WHERE {   ?nature_reserve rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_nature_reserve> .   ?nature_reserve geo:hasGeometry ?nature_reserve_geo .   ?nature_reserve_geo geo:asWKT ?nature_reserve_geoWKT .  ?forest rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_forest> .   ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?forest_geo .   ?forest_geo geo:asWKT ?forest_geoWKT .  FILTER(geof:distance(?forest_geoWKT,?nature_reserve_geoWKT,uom:metre) <= 5000)   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "416": {
    "Question": "Which Admin. Level 3 entities have  Oxbows?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?order3adm  WHERE {    ?order3adm <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/hasGADM_NationalLevel> 3rdOrder  .   ?order3adm geo:hasGeometry ?order3adm_geo .  ?order3adm_geo geo:asWKT ?order3adm_geoWKT .  ?oxbow rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_oxbow> .  ?oxbow geo:hasGeometry ?oxbow_geo .  ?oxbow_geo geo:asWKT ?oxbow_geoWKT .  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?oxbow_geoWKT,?order3adm_geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "417": {
    "Question": "Which islands have lakes?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?island WHERE {   ?island rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_island> .   ?island geo:hasGeometry ?island_geo .  ?island_geo geo:asWKT ?island_geoWKT .    ?lake rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_lake> .   ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?lake_geo .  ?lake_geo geo:asWKT ?lake_geoWKT .    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lake_geoWKT,?island_geoWKT))   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "418": {
    "Question": "Which nature reserve regions intersect with towns?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?natureReserve where{  ?town rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_town .  ?town geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.   ?natureReserve rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_nature_reserve.  ?natureReserve geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.    FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(strdf:buffer(?geoWKT, 0,    <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?geoWKT1, 0,    <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>))) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "419": {
    "Question": "Which villages border towns?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?village where{  ?town rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_town .  ?town geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.   ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village .  ?village geo:hasGeometry ?o2.  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2.   FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:buffer(?geoWKT1, 0,   <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?geoWKT2, 0,   <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>))) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "420": {
    "Question": "Which beaches are near cities?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?beach where{  ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach .  ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.   ?city rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_city .  ?city geo:hasGeometry ?o2.  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2.   FILTER((geof:distance(strdf:transform(?geoWKT1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?geoWKT2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>) < 5000)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "421": {
    "Question": "Which district wards are within districts ?",
    "Query": "Select distinct ?DistrictWard Where {  ?District rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_District>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?A.  ?DistrictWard rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_DistrictWard>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geom. ?geom geo:asWKT ?B.    FILTER (strdf:within(strdf:transform(?B, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?A, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)))    }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "422": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are within  county councils?",
    "Query": "Select distinct ?lake Where {  ?CountyCouncil rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_County_Council>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?A.  ?lake rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_lake>; <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?geom. ?geom geo:asWKT ?B.   FILTER (strdf:within(strdf:transform(?B, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?A, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)))    }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "423": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are connected to a forest?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?x where { ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake . ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom. ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT. ?o rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest . ?o geo:hasGeometry ?oGeom. ?oGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT. FILTER(geof:sfIntersects(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?iWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>) )) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "424": {
    "Question": "Which Baronies border with City Councils?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?o where { ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_City_Council . ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom. ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT. ?o rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_Barony . ?o geo:hasGeometry ?oGeom. ?oGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT. FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?iWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>) )) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "425": {
    "Question": "Which forests are near lakes?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {          ?x1 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest.            ?x1 geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.         ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.        ?x2 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake.             ?x2 geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.           ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.             FILTER(geof:distance(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT, uom:metre) <= 2500). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "426": {
    "Question": "Which parks are within cities?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {          ?x1 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park.            ?x1 geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo.         ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.        ?x2 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_city.             ?x2 geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.           ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.             FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT)). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "427": {
    "Question": "Which bays are near 10 kms of villages?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {          ?x1 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_bay.       ?x1 <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?x1Geo.         ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.        ?x2 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village.              ?x2 <http://www.opengis.net/ont/geosparql#hasGeometry> ?x2Geo.           ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.       FILTER(geof:distance(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT, uom:metre) <= 10000).    }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "428": {
    "Question": "Which streams are close to lakes?",
    "Query": "SELECT  DISTINCT ?p1 WHERE {   ?p1 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream;   geo:hasGeometry ?p1geo.   ?p1geo geo:asWKT ?p1WKT.   ?p2 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake;   geo:hasGeometry ?p2geo.   ?p2geo geo:asWKT ?p2WKT.    FILTER(geof:distance(?p1WKT, ?p2WKT, uom:metre) < 2000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "429": {
    "Question": "Which nature reserves contain forests?",
    "Query": "SELECT  DISTINCT ?p1 WHERE {   ?p1 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_nature_reserve;   geo:hasGeometry ?p1geo.   ?p1geo geo:asWKT ?p1WKT.   ?p2 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest;   geo:hasGeometry ?p2geo.   ?p2geo geo:asWKT ?p2WKT.    FILTER(geof:sfContains(?p1WKT, ?p2WKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "430": {
    "Question": "Which villages are on islands?",
    "Query": "SELECT  DISTINCT ?p1 WHERE {   ?p1 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village;   geo:hasGeometry ?p1geo.   ?p1geo geo:asWKT ?p1WKT.   ?p2 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island;   geo:hasGeometry ?p2geo.   ?p2geo geo:asWKT ?p2WKT.    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?p1WKT, ?p2WKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "431": {
    "Question": "Which nature reserved areas are within islands?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?nature_reserve WHERE {          ?nature_reserve rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_nature_reserve.          ?nature_reserve geo:hasGeometry ?g.          ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.          ?islands rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island.          ?islands geo:hasGeometry ?g2.          ?g2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "432": {
    "Question": "Which beaches border forests?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?beach WHERE {          ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach.          ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?g.          ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.          ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest.          ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?g2.          ?g2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2. FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "433": {
    "Question": "Which lakes cross parks?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?lake WHERE {          ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake.          ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?g.          ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.          ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park.          ?park geo:hasGeometry ?g2.          ?g2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2. FILTER(strdf:crosses(?geoWKT, ?geoWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "434": {
    "Question": "Which lakes border forests?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x where{      ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake.     ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.      ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.        ?y rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest.     ?y geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.    ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.  FILTER(strdf:touches(strdf:buffer(?xWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?yWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>))) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "435": {
    "Question": "Which villages are north of forests?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x where{      ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village.     ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.      ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.        ?y rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest.     ?y geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.    ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.  FILTER (strdf:above(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "436": {
    "Question": "Which canals are east of villages?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x where{      ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal.     ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.      ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.        ?y rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village.     ?y geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.    ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.  FILTER (strdf:right(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "437": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities contain at least one forest?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?M WHERE{ ?M rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality. ?M geo:hasGeometry ?MGeo. ?MGeo geo:asWKT ?MPolygon.  ?Forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest. ?Forest geo:hasGeometry ?ForestGeo. ?ForestGeo geo:asWKT ?ForestPolygon .  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?ForestPolygon, ?MPolygon))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "438": {
    "Question": "Which Lakes overlap with metropolitan districts?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?Lake WHERE{ ?MD rdf:type y2geoo:OS_MetropolitanDistrict. ?MD geo:hasGeometry ?MDGeo. ?MDGeo geo:asWKT ?MDPolygon.  ?Lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake. ?Lake geo:hasGeometry ?LakeGeo. ?LakeGeo geo:asWKT ?LakePolygon .  FILTER(strdf:strdf:overlaps(?MDPolygon,?LakePolygon)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "439": {
    "Question": "Which villages are close to cities?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?village WHERE{  ?City rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_city. ?City geo:hasGeometry ?CityGeo. ?CityGeo geo:asWKT ?CityPolygon.  ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village. ?village geo:hasGeometry ?villageGeo. ?villageGeo geo:asWKT ?villagePolygon .  FILTER (geof:distance(?villagePolygon, ?CityPolygon, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>) < 500 ) . }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "440": {
    "Question": "Which parks are north of streams?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?park where{   ?park a y2geoo:OSM_park.   ?park  geo:hasGeometry ?parkGeometry .   ?parkGeometry geo:asWKT ?parkWKT .    ?stream a y2geoo:OSM_stream.   ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?streamGeometry .   ?streamGeometry geo:asWKT ?streamWKT .      FILTER(strdf:above(strdf:buffer(?parkWKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?streamWKT , 0,uom:metre))). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "441": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are south of canals?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?lake where{   ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake.   ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?lakeGeometry .   ?lakeGeometry geo:asWKT ?lakeWKT .    ?canal a y2geoo:OSM_canal.   ?canal geo:hasGeometry ?canalGeometry .   ?canalGeometry geo:asWKT ?canalWKT .      FILTER(strdf:below(strdf:buffer(?lakeWKT,0,uom:metre),strdf:buffer(?canalWKT,0,uom:metre))). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "442": {
    "Question": "Which localities are near forests?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?locality where{   ?locality a y2geoo:OSM_locality.   ?locality geo:hasGeometry ?localityGeometry .   ?localityGeometry geo:asWKT ?localityWKT .    ?forest a y2geoo:OSM_forest.   ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?forestGeometry .   ?forestGeometry geo:asWKT ?forestWKT .      FILTER(geof:distance(strdf:buffer(?localityWKT,0,uom:metre),strdf:buffer(?forestWKT,0,uom:metre), uom:metre) <= 15000). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "443": {
    "Question": "Which are the municipalities that have beaches?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?municipality  where { ?municipality rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality . ?municipality geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach; geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "444": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities have canals?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?municipality  where { ?municipality rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality . ?municipality geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?canal rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal; geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "445": {
    "Question": "Which counties are north of lakes?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?county  where { ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OS_County . ?county geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake; geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.  FILTER(strdf:above(?lcnWKT,?lWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "446": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are inside a forest?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?forest ?lake WHERE {       ?forest a y2geoo:OSM_forest .   ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?forestGeom .   ?forestGeom geo:asWKT ?forestWKT .       ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake .   ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?lakeGeom .   ?lakeGeom geo:asWKT ?lakeWKT .       FILTER(geof:sfWithin(strdf:envelope(?lakeWKT), strdf:envelope(?forestWKT))) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "447": {
    "Question": "Which rivers are inside an island?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?island ?river WHERE {       ?island a y2geoo:OSM_island .   ?island geo:hasGeometry ?islandGeom .   ?islandGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .       ?river a y2geoo:OSM_stream .   ?river geo:hasGeometry ?riverGeom .   ?riverGeom geo:asWKT ?yWKT .       FILTER(geof:sfWithin(strdf:envelope(?yWKT), strdf:envelope(?xWKT))) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "448": {
    "Question": "Which villages are near a lake?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?island ?river WHERE {       ?village a y2geoo:OSM_village .   ?village geo:hasGeometry ?villageGeom .   ?villageGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .       ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake .   ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?lakeGeom .   ?lakeGeom geo:asWKT ?yWKT .       FILTER(geof:distance(strdf:envelope(?yWKT), strdf:envelope(?xWKT), uom:metre) < 2000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "449": {
    "Question": "Which beaches are in regions?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?beach WHERE {  ?beach a y2geoo:OSM_beach. ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo. ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.           ?region a y2geoo:GAG_Region.           ?region geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.         ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.        FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT))}",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "450": {
    "Question": "Which parks are in counties?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?park WHERE {  ?park a y2geoo:OSM_park. ?park geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo. ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.           ?county a y2geoo:OS_County.          ?county geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.         ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.        FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT))}",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "451": {
    "Question": "Which nature reserves are in rural areas?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?nature_reserve WHERE {  ?nature_reserve a y2geoo:OSM_nature_reserve. ?nature_reserve geo:hasGeometry ?x1Geo. ?x1Geo geo:asWKT ?x1WKT.           ?rural_area a y2geoo:OSI_Rural_Area.          ?rural_area geo:hasGeometry ?x2Geo.         ?x2Geo geo:asWKT ?x2WKT.        FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?x1WKT, ?x2WKT))}",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "452": {
    "Question": "What regional units are far from islands?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?ru WHERE { ?ru a y2geoo:GAG_RegionalUnit. ?ru geo:hasGeometry ?g1. ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1. ?island a y2geoo:OSM_island. ?island geo:hasGeometry ?g2. ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2. FILTER(geof:distance(?wkt1, ?wkt2, uom:metre) > 10000 ) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "453": {
    "Question": "What rivers cross Irish Townlands?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?river  WHERE {     ?river a y2geoo:OSM_stream.     ?river geo:hasGeometry ?g1.     ?g1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.     ?county a y2geoo:OSI_Townland.     ?county geo:hasGeometry ?g2.     ?g2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.     FILTER(         geof:sfCrosses(     strdf:transform(?wkt1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),     strdf:transform(?wkt2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "454": {
    "Question": "Which cities are in a 10km distance from a beach?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?city WHERE{ ?city a y2geoo:OSM_city;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?cWKT.  ?park a y2geoo:OSM_beach;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?bWKT.  FILTER(strdf:distance(?cWKT, ?bWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>) < 10000).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "455": {
    "Question": "Which streams cross a nature reserve?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?stream WHERE{ ?stream a y2geoo:OSM_stream;   geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?sWKT.  ?reserve a y2geoo:OSM_nature_reserve;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?rWKT .   FILTER(strdf:crosses(?sWKT, ?rWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "456": {
    "Question": "Which forests have a lagoon inside them?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?forest WHERE{ ?forest a y2geoo:OSM_forest;    geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?fWKT.  ?lagoon a y2geoo:OSM_lagoon;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?lWKT .   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?fWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "457": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities contain beaches?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?municipality  where {      ?municipality a yagoo:GAG_Municipality.     ?municipality geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.      ?beach rdf:type yagoo:OSM_beach;             geo:hasGeometry ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.      FILTER(geof:sfContains(?lcnWKT, ?lWKT))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "458": {
    "Question": "Which counties border with forests?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?county where {     ?county rdf:type yagoo:OS_County.     ?county geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcWKT.       ?forest rdf:type yagoo:OSM_forest;             geo:hasGeometry ?geomL.     ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.      FILTER(strdf:touches(?lWKT, ?lcWKT))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "459": {
    "Question": "Which parks have lakes in or as parts of them?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?park where {      ?park rdf:type yagoo:OSM_park;           geo:hasGeometry ?geomP.     ?geomP geo:asWKT ?lWKT_P.      ?lake rdf:type yagoo:OSM_lake;           geo:hasGeometry ?geomF.     ?geomF geo:asWKT ?lWKT_F.      FILTER(strdf:intersects(?lWKT_P, ?lWKT_F))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "460": {
    "Question": "Which counties has lakes inside them?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?counties WHERE{  ?counties <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#type> <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_County>.   ?counties geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.   ?lake <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#type> <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_lake>.  ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT1,?geoWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "461": {
    "Question": "Which parks are 10 km near from streams?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?park WHERE{  ?park <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#type> <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_park>.   ?park geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.   ?stream <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#type> <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_stream>.  ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  FILTER(geof:distance(?geoWKT,?geoWKT1,uom:metre) <= 10000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "462": {
    "Question": "Which islands have a forest?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?island ?iWKT where { ?island rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island. ?island geo:hasGeometry ?geomI. ?geomI geo:asWKT ?iWKT.  ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest. ?forest geo:hasGeometry  ?geomB. ?geomB geo:asWKT ?bWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?bWKT, ?iWKT))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "463": {
    "Question": "Which towns are near a beach?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?town ?fWKT where {  ?town rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_town. ?town geo:hasGeometry ?geomT. ?geomT geo:asWKT ?fWKT. ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach. ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER(geof:distance(?lWKT, ?fWKT, uom:metre)<=10000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "464": {
    "Question": "Which towns are near a canal?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?town ?fWKT  where {  ?town rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_town. ?town geo:hasGeometry ?geomT. ?geomT geo:asWKT ?fWKT. ?canal rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal. ?canal geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER(geof:distance(?lWKT, ?fWKT, uom:metre)<=10000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "465": {
    "Question": "Which streams are close to lakes in Scotland?",
    "Query": "SELECT  DISTINCT ?p1 WHERE {   ?p1 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream;   geo:hasGeometry ?p1geo.   ?p1geo geo:asWKT ?p1WKT.   ?p2 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake;   geo:hasGeometry ?p2geo.   ?p2geo geo:asWKT ?p2WKT.    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Scotland> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.   ?o1 geo:asWKT ?sWKT.   FILTER(geof:distance(?p1WKT, ?p2WKT, uom:metre) < 2000 && geof:sfWithin(?pWKT, ?sWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "466": {
    "Question": "Which nature reserves of Ireland contain forests?",
    "Query": "SELECT  DISTINCT ?p1 WHERE {   ?p1 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_nature_reserve;   geo:hasGeometry ?p1geo.   ?p1geo geo:asWKT ?p1WKT.   ?p2 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest;   geo:hasGeometry ?p2geo.   ?p2geo geo:asWKT ?p2WKT.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Republic_of_Ireland> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.   ?o1 geo:asWKT ?iWKT.   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?p1WKT, ?iWKT) && geof:sfContains(?p1WKT, ?p2WKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "467": {
    "Question": "Which villages are in islands in Greece?",
    "Query": "SELECT  DISTINCT ?p1 WHERE {   ?p1 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village;   geo:hasGeometry ?p1geo.   ?p1geo geo:asWKT ?p1WKT.   ?p2 rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island;   geo:hasGeometry ?p2geo.   ?p2geo geo:asWKT ?p2WKT.    <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Greece> geo:hasGeometry ?o1.   ?o1 geo:asWKT ?gWKT.   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?p2WKT, ?gWKT) && geof:sfWithin(?p1WKT, ?p2WKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "468": {
    "Question": "Which forests intersects with villages in County Kent?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?forest where {         ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village.         ?village geo:hasGeometry ?vg.         ?vg geo:asWKT ?vgeoWKT.         yago:Kent geo:hasGeometry ?g2.         ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. FILTER(strdf:within(?vgeoWKT, ?geoWKT)).         ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest.         ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?fg.         ?fg geo:asWKT ?fgeoWKT. FILTER(strdf:intersects(?vgeoWKT, ?fgeoWKT)). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "469": {
    "Question": "Which parks are within cities in county Longford?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?park WHERE {  ?park rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park.  ?park geo:hasGeometry ?pg.  ?pg geo:asWKT ?pgeoWKT.   ?city rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_city.  ?city geo:hasGeometry ?cg.  ?cg geo:asWKT ?cgeoWKT.  yago:County_Longford geo:hasGeometry ?g.  ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. FILTER(strdf:within(?cgeoWKT, ?geoWKT)). FILTER(strdf:within(?pgeoWKT, ?cgeoWKT)). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "470": {
    "Question": "Which islands are east of villages in Greece?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x where{        ?y rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village.     ?y geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.      ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.       ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_island.     ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.      ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Greece> geo:hasGeometry ?grgeo.     ?grgeo geo:asWKT ?grWKT.  FILTER(strdf:contains(strdf:buffer(?grWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?xWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>)) && strdf:contains(strdf:buffer(?grWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?yWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>)) && FILTER (strdf:right(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "471": {
    "Question": "Which canals are north of forests in the UK?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?y where{        ?y rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal.     ?y geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.   ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.       ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest.     ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.  ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/United_Kingdom> geo:hasGeometry ?ukgeo.     ?ukgeo geo:asWKT ?ukWKT.  FILTER(strdf:contains(strdf:buffer(?ukWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?xWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>)) && strdf:contains(strdf:buffer(?ukWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?yWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>)) && FILTER (strdf:below(strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "472": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are west of forests in Ireland?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?y where{        ?y rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake.     ?y geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.     ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.       ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest.     ?x geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.  ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Republic_of_Ireland>  geo:hasGeometry ?irgeo.     ?irgeo geo:asWKT ?irWKT.  FILTER(strdf:contains(strdf:buffer(?irWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?xWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>)) && strdf:contains(strdf:buffer(?irWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>), strdf:buffer(?yWKT,0.0, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>)) && FILTER (strdf:left(strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>))))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "473": {
    "Question": "Which municipalities of Attica are close to at least one beach?",
    "Query": "SELECT distinct ?Municip WHERE {   ?Municip geo:sfWithin <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Attica_(region)>.  ?Municp rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality. ?Municp geo:hasGeometry ?MunicpGeo. ?MunicpGeo geo:asWKT ?MunicpPolygon.  ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach. ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?beachGeo. ?beachGeo geo:asWKT ?beachPolygon .  FILTER(geof:distance(?beachPolygon , ?MunicpPolygon, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>) < 500 ) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "474": {
    "Question": "Which parks in the UK engulf at least one lake inside them?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?prk WHERE{  yago:United_Kingdom geo:hasGeometry ?UkGeo. ?UkGeo geo:asWKT ?UkPolygon.  ?prk rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_park. ?prk geo:hasGeometry ?prkGeo. ?prkGeo geo:asWKT ?prkPolygon.  ?lk rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake. ?lk geo:hasGeometry ?lkGeo. ?lk geo:asWKT ?lkPolygon.  FILTER( geof:sfWithin(?prkPolygon, ?UkPolygon) && geof:sfWithin(?lkPolygon, ?UkPolygon) && geof:sfWithin(?prkPolygon, ?lkPolygon) ) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "475": {
    "Question": "Can you give me some villages in rural areas above Dublin ?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?vil WHERE{  yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?dblnGeo. ?dblnGeo geo:asWKT ?dblnPolygon.  ?vil rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village. ?vil geo:hasGeometry ?vilGeo. ?vilGeo geo:asWKT ?vilPolygon.  ?ra rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_Rural_Area. ?ra geo:hasGeometry ?raGeo. ?ra geo:asWKT ?raPolygon.  FILTER( strdf:above(?dblnGeometry,?vilGeometry) && strdf:above(?dblnGeometry,?raGeometry) && geof:sfWithin(?raPolygon, ?vilPolygon) ) } LIMIT 10",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "476": {
    "Question": "Which parks are north of a stream in Attiki?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?park where{   ?park a y2geoo:OSM_park.   ?park  geo:hasGeometry ?parkGeometry .   ?parkGeometry geo:asWKT ?parkWKT .    ?stream a y2geoo:OSM_stream.   ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?streamGeometry .   ?streamGeometry geo:asWKT ?streamWKT .    yago:geoentity_Apokentroméni_Dioíkisi_Attikís_8200474  geo:hasGeometry ?attikiGeo .   ?attikiGeo geo:asWKT ?attikiWKT .      FILTER(strdf:above(strdf:buffer(?parkWKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?streamWKT , 0,uom:metre))  && geof:sfWithin(strdf:buffer(?parkWKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?attikiWKT, 0,uom:metre)) && geof:sfWithin(strdf:buffer(?streamWKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?attikiWKT, 0,uom:metre)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "477": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are south of a canal in London?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?lake where{   ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake.   ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?lakeGeometry .   ?lakeGeometry geo:asWKT ?lakeWKT .    ?canal a y2geoo:OSM_canal.   ?canal geo:hasGeometry ?canalGeometry .   ?canalGeometry geo:asWKT ?canalWKT .    yago:Greater_London geo:hasGeometry ?londonGeometry .   ?londonGeometry geo:asWKT ?wktLondon .      FILTER(strdf:above(strdf:buffer(?canalWKT,0,uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?lakeWKT,0,uom:metre)) && geof:sfWithin(strdf:buffer(?canalWKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?wktLondon, 0,uom:metre)) && geof:sfWithin(strdf:buffer(?lakeWKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?wktLondon, 0,uom:metre))). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "478": {
    "Question": "Which localities are near forests in Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?locality where{   ?locality a y2geoo:OSM_locality.   ?locality geo:hasGeometry ?localityGeometry .   ?localityGeometry geo:asWKT ?localityWKT .    ?forest a y2geoo:OSM_forest.   ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?forestGeometry .   ?forestGeometry geo:asWKT ?forestWKT .    yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?dublinGeometry .   ?dublinGeometry geo:asWKT ?wktDublin .      FILTER(geof:distance(strdf:buffer(?localityWKT,0,uom:metre),strdf:buffer(?forestWKT,0,uom:metre), uom:metre) <= 15000 && geof:sfWithin(strdf:buffer(?localityWKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?wktDublin , 0,uom:metre)) && geof:sfWithin(strdf:buffer(?forestWKT, 0, uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?wktDublin , 0,uom:metre))). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "479": {
    "Question": "Which reservoirs are inside a 3rd Order Administrative Units in Greece?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?reservoir WHERE {   yago:Greece geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .    ?regUnit a y2geoo:GADM_3rdOrder_AdministrativeUnit .   ?regUnit geo:hasGeometry ?regUnitGeom .   ?regUnitGeom geo:asWKT ?regWKT .   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(strdf:envelope(?regWKT), strdf:envelope(?xWKT)))    ?reservoir a y2geoo:OSM_reservoir .   ?reservoir geo:hasGeometry ?resGeom .   ?resGeom geo:asWKT ?resWKT .    FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?resWKT,strdf:envelope(?regWKT))) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "480": {
    "Question": "Which reservoirs are less than 100km far from a 3rd order administrative units in Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?res WHERE {   yago:Republic_of_Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .       ?res a y2geoo:OSM_reservoir .   ?res geo:hasGeometry ?resGeom .   ?resGeom geo:asWKT ?resWKT .       FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?resWKT, ?xWKT)) # town is in england    ?town a y2geoo:GADM_4thOrder_AdministrativeUnit .   ?town geo:hasGeometry ?townGeom .   ?townGeom geo:asWKT ?townWKT .       FILTER(geof:distance(strdf:envelope(?resWKT), strdf:envelope(?townWKT), uom:metre) < 100000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "481": {
    "Question": "Which streams cross a town in England?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?river WHERE {   yago:England geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .       ?town a y2geoo:OSM_town .   ?town geo:hasGeometry ?townGeom .   ?townGeom geo:asWKT ?townWKT .       FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?townWKT, ?xWKT))    ?river a y2geoo:OSM_stream .   ?river geo:hasGeometry ?rivGeom .   ?rivGeom geo:asWKT ?rivWKT .       FILTER(geof:sfCrosses(?rivWKT, ?townWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "482": {
    "Question": "Which Greek cities are in a 10km distance from a beach?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?city WHERE{ yago:Greece geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?gWKT.  ?city a y2geoo:OSM_city;    geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?cWKT.  FILTER(strdf:contains(?gWKT, ?cWKT)).  ?park a y2geoo:OSM_beach;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?bWKT.   FILTER(strdf:distance(?cWKT, ?bWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>) < 10000).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "483": {
    "Question": "Which streams cross a nature reserve in Wales?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?stream WHERE{ yago:Wales geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?wWKT.  ?reserve a y2geoo:OSM_nature_reserve;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?rWKT.  FILTER(strdf:contains(?wWKT, ?rWKT)).  ?stream a y2geoo:OSM_stream;  geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?sWKT.  FILTER(strdf:crosses(?sWKT, ?rWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "484": {
    "Question": "Which forests have a lagoon inside them in 50km distance from Cork?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?forest WHERE{ ?forest a y2geoo:OSM_forest;  geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?fWKT.  ?lagoon a y2geoo:OSM_lagoon;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?lWKT;  y2geor:gadmentity_Cork_IRL.4_1 geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?cWKT.  FILTER(strdf:distance(?cWKT, ?fWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>) < 50000). FILTER(strdf:inside(?lWKT, ?fWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "485": {
    "Question": "Which towns are near lakes in West Macedonia?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?town  where {     yagok:geoentity_Western_Macedonia_6697811 geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.      ?town rdf:type yagoo:OSM_town;             geo:hasGeometry ?geomP.     ?geomP geo:asWKT ?lWKT_P.      ?lake rdf:type yagoo:OSM_lake;             geo:hasGeometry ?geomF.     ?geomF geo:asWKT ?lWKT_F.      FILTER(geof:sfWithin(strdf:envelope(?lWKT_P),                          strdf:envelope(?lcnWKT))          && (strdf:distance(?lWKT_P, ?lWKT_F, uom:metre) < 5000))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "486": {
    "Question": "What streams cross a forest south of Oxford?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?stream  where {     yagok:Oxford geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.      ?stream rdf:type yagoo:OSM_stream;             geo:hasGeometry ?geomP.     ?geomP geo:asWKT ?lWKT_P.      ?forest rdf:type yagoo:OSM_forest;             geo:hasGeometry ?geomF.     ?geomF geo:asWKT ?lWKT_F.      FILTER(strdf:below(?lWKT_F, ?lcnWKT)          && strdf:crosses(?lWKT_P, ?lWKT_F))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "487": {
    "Question": "What parks intersect with forests in Dublin?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?park  where {     yagok:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC.     ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.      ?park rdf:type yagoo:OSM_park;     geo:hasGeometry ?geomP.     ?geomP geo:asWKT ?lWKT_P.      ?forest rdf:type yagoo:OSM_forest;     geo:hasGeometry ?geomF.     ?geomF geo:asWKT ?lWKT_F.      FILTER(strdf:within(?lWKT_F, ?lcnWKT)          && strdf:intersects(?lWKT_P, ?lWKT_F))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "488": {
    "Question": "Which localities are near lakes in Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?locality WHERE {  yago:Republic_of_Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?locality rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_locality .  ?locality geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake .  ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o3 .  ?o3 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT3 .  FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:within(?geoWKT3, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:distance(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT3, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "489": {
    "Question": "Which forests are near streams in the United Kingdom?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?forest WHERE {  yago:United_Kingdom geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest .  ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  ?stream rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream .  ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?o3 .  ?o3 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT3 .  FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:within(?geoWKT3, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:distance(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT3, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "490": {
    "Question": "Which villages are near beaches in Greece?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?village WHERE {  yago:Greece geo:hasGeometry ?o1 .  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 .  ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_city .  ?village geo:hasGeometry ?o2 .  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 .  ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach .  ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?o3 .  ?o3 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT3 .  FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:within(?geoWKT3, ?geoWKT1) &&     strdf:distance(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT3, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "491": {
    "Question": "Which lakes are near streams in Cambridge?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?lake WHERE{  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cambridge> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.   ?lake <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#type> <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_lake>.   ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.   #FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT1,?geoWKT))   ?stream <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#type> <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_stream>.   ?stream geo:hasGeometry ?o2.  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2.   #FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT2,?geoWKT))   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT1,?geoWKT) && geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT2,?geoWKT) && geof:distance(?geoWKT1,?geoWKT2,uom:metre) <= 30000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "492": {
    "Question": "All municipalities that has a nearby beach, in Greece ?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?dhmoi WHERE{     <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Greece> geo:hasGeometry ?o.  ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.  ?lake <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#type>  <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_beach>.   ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?o1.  ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1.  #FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?geoWKT1,?geoWKT)).  ?dhmoi <http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#type>  <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/GAG_Municipality>.   ?dhmoi geo:hasGeometry ?o2.  ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(strdf:transform(?geoWKT1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),strdf:transform(?geoWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)) && geof:sfWithin(strdf:transform(?geoWKT2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),strdf:transform(?geoWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)) && geof:distance(strdf:transform(?geoWKT1, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),strdf:transform(?geoWKT2, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>),uom:metre)<=10000).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "493": {
    "Question": "Which forests are near streams in Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?forest WHERE { yago:Republic_of_Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?o . ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest; geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 . ?river rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream; geo:hasGeometry ?o2 . ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 . FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT) &&  strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT) &&  strdf:distance(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "494": {
    "Question": "Which villages are near lakes in the United Kingdom?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?village WHERE { yago:United_Kingdom geo:hasGeometry ?o . ?o geo:asWKT ?geoWKT . ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village; geo:hasGeometry ?o1 . ?o1 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT1 . ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake; geo:hasGeometry ?o2 . ?o2 geo:asWKT ?geoWKT2 . FILTER (strdf:within(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT) &&  strdf:within(?geoWKT2, ?geoWKT) &&  strdf:distance(?geoWKT1, ?geoWKT2, uom:metre) < 5000) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "495": {
    "Question": "Which villages are near bays in Peloponnese region?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?village ?vWKT  where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Peloponnese_(region)> geo:hasGeometry ?geom1 .  ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village. ?village geo:hasGeometry ?geomV. ?geomV geo:asWKT ?vWKT.  ?bay rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_bay. ?bay  geo:hasGeometry ?geomB. ?geomB geo:asWKT ?bWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?vWKT, ?geom1) && geof:distance(?vWKT, ?bWKT, uom:metre)<=5000))  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "496": {
    "Question": "Which forest in Essex county are near a lake?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?forest  where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Essex> geo:hasGeometry  ?geomLC. ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.   ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest. ?forest geo:hasGeometry  ?geomF. ?geomF geo:asWKT ?fWKT.   ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake.  ?lake geo:hasGeometry  ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?fWKT, ?lcnWKT)  && (geof:distance(?lWKT, ?fWKT, uom:metre)<=10000) ) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "497": {
    "Question": "Which forest in TULLYHAW Barony are near a town?",
    "Query": "select DISTINCT ?forest where {  <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Tully_2635377> geo:hasGeometry  ?geomLC.  ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT.   ?forest rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_forest. ?forest geo:hasGeometry ?geomF. ?geomF geo:asWKT ?fWKT.  ?town rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_town. ?town geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT.   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?fWKT, ?lcnWKT)  && (geof:distance(?lWKT, ?fWKT, uom:metre)<=5000) ) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "498": {
    "Question": "Which is the smallest county of Wales?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?county ((strdf:area(?cWKT)) AS ?cArea) WHERE {   ?county rdf:type y2geoo:OS_County;   geo:hasGeometry ?geomC.   ?geomC geo:asWKT ?cWKT.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wales> geo:hasGeometry ?geomW.   ?geomW geo:asWKT ?wWKT.   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cWKT, ?wWKT)). }  ORDER BY (?cArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "499": {
    "Question": "Which is the largest bay in Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?bay ((strdf:area(?bWKT)) AS ?bArea) WHERE {   ?bay rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_bay;   geo:hasGeometry ?geomB.   ?geomB geo:asWKT ?bWKT.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Republic_of_Ireland> geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom.          ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT.   FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?bWKT, ?iWKT)). } ORDER BY DESC(?bArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "500": {
    "Question": "Which municipality in Crete region have population over 20000?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?m WHERE{         yago:Crete geo:hasGeometry ?g.         ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT.         ?m rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality.         ?m geo:hasGeometry ?mg.         ?cg geo:asWKT ?mgeoWKT. FILTER(strdf:within(?mgeoWKT, ?geoWKT)).         ?m y2geoo:GAG_Population ?p. FILTER(?p > 20000). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "501": {
    "Question": "Is there a village in Scotland with area smaller than 0.05?",
    "Query": "ASK{  ?village rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village.  ?village geo:hasGeometry ?vg.  ?vg geo:asWKT ?vgeoWKT.  yago:Scotland geo:hasGeometry ?g.  ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. FILTER(strdf:within(?vgeoWKT, ?geoWKT)). FILTER(strdf:area(?geoWKT) < 0.05). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "502": {
    "Question": "Which towns in County Longford with area bigger than 0.01 are west of Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?town WHERE {  ?town rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_town.  ?town geo:hasGeometry ?tg.  ?tg geo:asWKT ?tgeoWKT.  yago:County_Longford geo:hasGeometry ?g.  ?g geo:asWKT ?geoWKT. FILTER(strdf:within(?tgeoWKT, ?geoWKT)). FILTER(strdf:area(?tgeoWKT) > 0.01).  yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?dg.  ?dg geo:asWKT ?dgeoWKT. FILTER(strdf:left(?geoWKT, ?dgeoWKT)). }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "503": {
    "Question": "Which are the smallest 5 lakes north of Dublin?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?y ((strdf:area(?yWKT))as ?totalArea) where{      ?y a y2geoo:OSM_lake.    ?y geo:hasGeometry ?ygeo.     ?ygeo geo:asWKT ?yWKT.   <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/resource/gadmentity_Dublin_IRL.6_1> geo:hasGeometry ?xgeo.     ?xgeo geo:asWKT ?xWKT.  FILTER (strdf:above(strdf:transform(?yWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>), strdf:transform(?xWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/crs/EPSG/0/4326>)))  }ORDER BY ASC(?totalArea) LIMIT 5",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "504": {
    "Question": "Which are the name of the villages and the cities which are in less than 500 meters?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?cityName ?vilgName WHERE {   ?city rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_city. ?city y2geoo:hasOSM_Name ?cityName. ?city geo:hasGeometry ?cityGeo. ?cityGeo geo:asWKT ?cityWKT.  ?vilg rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_village ?vilg y2geoo:hasOSM_Name ?vilgName. ?vilg geo:hasGeometry ?vilgGeo. ?vilgGeo geo:asWKT ?vilgWKt.  yago:Republic_of_Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?IrGeo. ?IrGeo geo:asWKT ?IrWKt.  FILTER(geo:sfContains(?IrWKT,?cityWKT) && geo:sfContains(?IrWKT,?vilgWKT) &&   (strdf:distance(?cityWKT, ?vilgWKt,uom:metre) < 500) )  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "505": {
    "Question": "Which of the regional Units that border Thessaloniki has the biggest area?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?neighboring (strdf:area(?yWKT)as ?totalArea) WHERE {   y2geor:gagentity_202 geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .    ?neighboring a y2geoo:GAG_RegionalUnit .   ?neighboring geo:hasGeometry ?yGeom .   ?yGeom geo:asWKT ?yWKT .       FILTER(geof:sfTouches(strdf:buffer(?xWKT,0,uom:metre), strdf:buffer(?yWKT ,0,uom:metre))) } ORDER BY DESC(?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "506": {
    "Question": "Which village is closest to a lake?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?island ?river (geof:distance(strdf:envelope(?yWKT), strdf:envelope(?xWKT), uom:metre) as ?distance) WHERE {       ?village a y2geoo:OSM_village .   ?village geo:hasGeometry ?villageGeom .   ?villageGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .       ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_stream .   ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?lakeGeom .   ?lakeGeom geo:asWKT ?yWKT . } ORDER BY DESC(?distance) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "507": {
    "Question": "Which of the towns in England that have a river crossing them has the biggest area?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?river ?town (strdf:area(?townWKT) as ?totalArea) WHERE {   yago:United_Kingdom geo:hasGeometry ?xGeom .   ?xGeom geo:asWKT ?xWKT .       ?town a y2geoo:OSM_town .   ?town geo:hasGeometry ?townGeom .   ?townGeom geo:asWKT ?townWKT .       FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?townWKT, ?xWKT)) # town is in england    ?river a y2geoo:OSM_stream .   ?river geo:hasGeometry ?rivGeom .   ?rivGeom geo:asWKT ?rivWKT .       FILTER(geof:sfCrosses(?rivWKT, ?townWKT)) } ORDER BY DESC(?totalArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "508": {
    "Question": "Which is the largest forest in a 10km radius from Kastanas beach?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?forest ?forestArea WHERE{  yago:geoentity_Paralía_Kastanás_10277719 geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?kWKT.  ?forest a y2geoo:OSM_forest;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?fWKT.  FILTER(strdf:distance(?kWKT, ?fWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>) < 10000). BIND(strdf:area(?fWKT) AS ?forestArea).  }ORDER BY DESC(?forestArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "509": {
    "Question": "Which is the largest stream that intersects with Cork?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?stream ?steamArea WHERE{  y2geor:gadmentity_Cork_IRL.4_1 geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?cWKT.  ?stream a y2geoo:OSM_stream;     geo:hasGeometry/geo:asWKT ?sWKT .   FILTER(strdf:intersect(?sWKT, ?cWKT)). BIND(strdf:area(?sWKT) AS ?streamArea) }ORDER BY DESC(?streamArea) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "510": {
    "Question": "Which barony of Ireland has the biggest number of lakes?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?barony (count (?lake) as ?numberOfLakes) where { ?barony rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_Barony. ? barony geo:hasGeometry ?geomLC.  ?geomLC geo:asWKT ?lcnWKT. ?lake rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_lake. ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?geomL. ?geomL geo:asWKT ?lWKT. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lWKT, ?lcnWKT)) }GROUP BY (?barony) ORDER BY DESC(?numberOfLakes)LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "511": {
    "Question": "How many canals are there in Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT  (COUNT(DISTINCT ?canal) AS ?numCanals) WHERE {   ?canal rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_canal;   geo:hasGeometry ?cgeo.   ?cgeo geo:asWKT ?cWKT.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Republic_of_Ireland> geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom.          ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT.   FILTER (geof:sfWithin(?cWKT,?iWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "512": {
    "Question": "How many beaches are there in England and what is their total area?",
    "Query": "SELECT  (COUNT(DISTINCT ?beach) AS ?numBeaches) (SUM((strdf:area(?bWKT))) AS ?totalArea) WHERE {   ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach;   geo:hasGeometry ?bgeo.   ?bgeo geo:asWKT ?bWKT.   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/England> geo:hasGeometry ?eGeom.          ?eGeom geo:asWKT ?eWKT.   FILTER (geof:sfWithin(?bWKT,?eWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "513": {
    "Question": "How many beaches are 500 meters away from the municipalities of Greece?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?Municp (COUNT (?beach) AS ?NoOfBeaches) WHERE {   ?Municp rdf:type y2geoo:GAG_Municipality. ?Municp geo:hasGeometry ?MunicpGeo. ?MunicpGeo geo:asWKT ?MunicpWKT.  ?beach rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_beach. ?beach geo:hasGeometry ?beachGeo. ?beachGeo geo:asWKT ?beachWKT .  FILTER(geof:distance(?beachWKT , ?MunicpWKT, <http://www.opengis.net/def/uom/OGC/1.0/metre>) < 500 )  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "514": {
    "Question": "Find the 10 British Counties having the most forests.",
    "Query": "SELECT ?m (COUNT(?l) AS ?count) WHERE {    ?m rdf:type y2geoo:OS_County.    ?m geo:hasGeometry ?mg .    ?mg geo:asWKT ?mw .    ?l a y2geoo:OSM_forst .    ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .    ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lw,?mw)) } GROUP BY (?m) ORDER BY DESC(?count) LIMIT 10",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "515": {
    "Question": "Find the 10 Irish Baronies with the most forests and at least 2 lakes.",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mname (COUNT(?f) AS ?count_f) WHERE {     SELECT ?mname ?mw (COUNT(?l) AS ?count_inner)    WHERE    {     ?m rdf:type y2geoo:OSI_Barony.     ?m geo:hasGeometry ?mg .     ?mg geo:asWKT ?mw .     ?m y2geoo:hasGAG_Name ?mname.      ?l a y2geoo:OSM_lake .     ?l geo:hasGeometry ?lg .     ?lg geo:asWKT ?lw .         FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lw,?mw)).    } GROUP BY ( ?mw).     FILTER(?count_inner>1).     ?f a y2geoo:OSM_forest .    ?f geo:hasGeometry ?fg .    ?fg geo:asWKT ?fw .     FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?fw,?mw)). } GROUP BY (?mname) ORDER BY DESC(?count_f) LIMIT 10",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "516": {
    "Question": "What is the capital of California?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?capital  WHERE {      yago:California yago:hasCapital ?capital.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Los_Angeles  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sacramento,_California"
  },
  "517": {
    "Question": "What is the elevation of Ben Nevis?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?elevation  WHERE {        yago:Ben_Nevis yagoinfobox:elevationm ?elevation.  }",
    "Answer": 1344
  },
  "518": {
    "Question": "What is the population of the UK?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population  WHERE {        yago:United_Kingdom yagoinfobox:populationcensus ?population.  }",
    "Answer": 63181775
  },
  "519": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Northern Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population  WHERE {      yago:Northern_Ireland yagoinfobox:populationcensus ?population.  }",
    "Answer": 1810863
  },
  "520": {
    "Question": "Which is the capital of Northern Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?capital  WHERE {      yago:Northern_Ireland yago:hasCapital ?capital.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Belfast"
  },
  "521": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Derry?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population  WHERE {      yago:Derry yagoinfobox:populationref ?population.  }",
    "Answer": "Derry 85,016  [[Derry Urban Area|Urban]] 93,512  [[Metropolitan area|Metro]] 237,000  [http://www.nisra.gov.uk/archive/demography/population/small_area/SAPE_Settlement_08.xls 2008 est.]"
  },
  "522": {
    "Question": "What is the currency of USA?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?currency  WHERE {      yago:United_States yago:hasCurrency ?currency.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/United_States_dollar"
  },
  "523": {
    "Question": "What type of Government does Los Angeles have?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?gtype  WHERE {       yago:Los_Angeles yagoinfobox:governmenttype ?gtype.  }",
    "Answer": "[[Mayor-council government|Mayor-Council]]"
  },
  "524": {
    "Question": "What is the dept of Loch Ness ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?depth  WHERE {      yago:Loch_Ness yagoinfobox:maxdepth ?depth.  }",
    "Answer": "226.96 m"
  },
  "525": {
    "Question": "What type of Goverment does Republic of Ireland have?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?gtype  WHERE {      yago:Republic_of_Ireland yagoinfobox:governmenttype ?gtype.  }",
    "Answer": "[[Unitary state|Unitary]] [[parliamentary system|parliamentary]] [[constitutional republic]]"
  },
  "526": {
    "Question": "Which is the website of the Dublin Zoo?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?website  WHERE {      yago:Dublin_Zoo yagoinfobox:website ?website.  }",
    "Answer": "{{URL|http://www.dublinzoo.ie}}"
  },
  "527": {
    "Question": "Which is the length of River Liffey?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?o  WHERE {      yago:River_Liffey yago:hasLength ?o.  }",
    "Answer": "125000^^<http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/m>"
  },
  "528": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population  WHERE {    yago:Dublin yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?population.  }",
    "Answer": 527612
  },
  "529": {
    "Question": "Where is Galway located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?lat ?lon  WHERE {      yago:geoentity_Galway_2964180 yago:hasLatitude ?lat.      yago:geoentity_Galway_2964180 yago:hasLongitude ?lon.  }",
    "Answer": "53.27194^^<http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/degrees>        -9.04889^^<http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/degrees>"
  },
  "530": {
    "Question": "What is the elevation of Carrauntoohil?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?height  WHERE {      yago:Carrauntoohil yagoinfobox:elevationm ?height.  }",
    "Answer": 1038
  },
  "531": {
    "Question": "What is the total area of Cork?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?area  WHERE {      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cork_(city)> yagoinfobox:areatotalkm ?area.  }",
    "Answer": 37.3
  },
  "532": {
    "Question": "Where is Edinburgh located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?lat ?lon  WHERE {      yago:geoentity_Edinburgh_2650225 yago:hasLatitude ?lat.      yago:geoentity_Edinburgh_2650225 yago:hasLongitude ?lon.  }",
    "Answer": "55.95^^<http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/degrees>    -3.2^^<http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/degrees>"
  },
  "533": {
    "Question": "Where is Waterford located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?lat ?lon  WHERE {      yago:County_Waterford yago:hasLatitude ?lat.      yago:County_Waterford yago:hasLongitude ?lon.  }",
    "Answer": "52.25^^<http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/degrees>    -7.5^^<http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/degrees>"
  },
  "534": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Scotland?",
    "Query": "SELECT  ?y  WHERE {      yago:Scotland yagoinfobox:populationcensus ?y  }",
    "Answer": 5313600
  },
  "535": {
    "Question": "Where are the Victoria Falls located?",
    "Query": "SELECT  ?y  WHERE {      yago:Victoria_Falls yagoinfobox:location ?y  }",
    "Answer": "[[Livingstone, Zambia]] [[Victoria Falls, Zimbabwe]]"
  },
  "536": {
    "Question": "What is the area that the Greenwich Park covers?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?area  WHERE {      yago:Greenwich_Park yagoinfobox:area ?area.  }",
    "Answer": "74 ha"
  },
  "537": {
    "Question": "Where is Bath located?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?bath_loc  WHERE {          <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bath,_Somerset> yago:isLocatedIn ?bath_loc  }  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/England"
  },
  "538": {
    "Question": "Where is Skye located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?loc  WHERE{  yago:Skye yago:isLocatedIn ?loc.  }  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Scotland"
  },
  "539": {
    "Question": "Where is MoMA museum located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?loc  WHERE{    yago:MoMA_PS1 yago:isLocatedIn ?loc  }  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_York_City"
  },
  "540": {
    "Question": "What is the capital of Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?capital  WHERE {      yago:Republic_of_Ireland yago:hasCapital ?capital.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin"
  },
  "541": {
    "Question": "Where is Key Largo located ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?loc  WHERE{    yago:Key_Largo yago:isLocatedIn ?loc.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Florida  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Florida_Keys  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Monroe_County,_Florida"
  },
  "542": {
    "Question": "Who is the monarch of Scotland?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE{     yago:Scotland  yagoinfobox:governmenttype ?o.     FILTER regex(?o, monarchy, i)  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "543": {
    "Question": "Who is the Senator of California?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?senator  WHERE{        yago:California yagoinfobox:senators ?senator  }",
    "Answer": "[[Dianne Feinstein]] (D) [[Barbara Boxer]] (D)"
  },
  "544": {
    "Question": "Where Glasgow is located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?loc  WHERE{         yago:Glasgow yago:isLocatedIn ?loc.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Scotland  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lanarkshire  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/G_postcode_area"
  },
  "545": {
    "Question": "When Glasgow was founded?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?loc  WHERE{         yago:Glasgow yagoinfobox:yearadopted ?loc.  }",
    "Answer": 1866
  },
  "546": {
    "Question": "Where is Loch Ness lake located?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?loc   WHERE{    yago:Loch_Ness yago:isLocatedIn ?loc   }   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Scotland"
  },
  "547": {
    "Question": "What is the capital of Scotland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?capital  WHERE {      yago:Scotland yago:hasCapital ?capital.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Edinburgh"
  },
  "548": {
    "Question": "What is the total area of United Kingdom?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?area   WHERE {    yago:United_Kingdom yagoinfobox:areakm ?area.   }",
    "Answer": 243610
  },
  "549": {
    "Question": "What is the length of Missouri River?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?length  WHERE {      yago:Missouri_River yagoinfobox:length ?length.  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "550": {
    "Question": "Which are the primary inflows of Lake Michigan?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?inflow  WHERE {      yago:Lake_Michigan yagoinfobox:inflow ?inflow.  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "551": {
    "Question": "Where is the mouth of river Bann?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mouth  WHERE {      yago:River_Bann yagoinfobox:mouth ?mouth.  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "552": {
    "Question": "Which is the length of River Severn?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?length  WHERE {      yago:River_Severn yagoinfobox:length ?length.  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "553": {
    "Question": "What is the length of the Shannon River?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?length  WHERE {      yago:River_Shannon yagoinfobox:length ?length.  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "554": {
    "Question": "What is the height of Mount Rushmore ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?height  WHERE{   yago:Mount_Rushmore_National_Memorial  yagoinfobox:elevationm  ?height.       }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "555": {
    "Question": "What is the population of Lincoln in Montana?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population   WHERE {    yago:Lincoln yagoinfobox:populationcensus ?population.   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "556": {
    "Question": "What is the area of the Grand Canyon ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?area   WHERE{    yago:Grand_Canyon yago:hasArea ?area   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "557": {
    "Question": "What is the population of San Francisco?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?population   WHERE {    yago:San_Francisco yagoinfobox:populationcensus ?population.   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "558": {
    "Question": "What is the elevation of Grand Teton ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?height   WHERE {    yago:Grand_Teton yagoinfobox:elevationm ?height.   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "559": {
    "Question": "Is Albany north of New York city?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {      <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Albany_County,_New_York> geo:hasGeometry ?albanyGeom.      ?albanyGeom geo:asWKT ?albanyWKT.            yago:New_York_City geo:hasGeometry ?newYorkGeom.      ?newYorkGeom geo:asWKT ?newYorkWKT.            FILTER(strdf:above(?albanyWKT, ?newYorkWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "560": {
    "Question": "Is Wales east of Cambridge?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {    yago:Wales geo:hasGeometry ?wGeom.    ?wGeom geo:asWKT ?wWKT.      yago:Cambridge geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom.    ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT.      FILTER(strdf:right(?wWKT, ?cWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "561": {
    "Question": "What is the distance between Glasgow and Edinburgh?",
    "Query": "SELECT  ?y  WHERE {      yago:Glasgow yagoinfobox:edinburghdistancemi ?y  }",
    "Answer": 49
  },
  "562": {
    "Question": "Is Cardiff north of Manchester?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {      yago:Cardiff geo:hasGeometry ?geom1.      ?geom1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.        yago:Manchester geo:hasGeometry ?geom2.      ?geom2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.        FILTER(strdf:above(?wkt1, ?wkt2)).  }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "563": {
    "Question": "Is Alabama west of Louisiana?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {      yago:Alabama geo:hasGeometry ?geom1.      ?geom1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.        yago:Louisiana geo:hasGeometry ?geom2.      ?geom2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.        FILTER(strdf:right(?wkt1, ?wkt2)).  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "564": {
    "Question": "Is Texas north of Kentucky?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {    yago:Kentucky geo:hasGeometry ?kGeom.    ?kGeom geo:asWKT ?kWKT.      yago:Texas geo:hasGeometry ?tGeom.    ?tGeom geo:asWKT ?tWKT.      FILTER(strdf:above(?tWKT, ?kWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "565": {
    "Question": "Is Lake Como in England?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE{  yago:Lake_Como yago:isLocatedIn yago:England.  }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "566": {
    "Question": "How close is Dublin to Scotland?",
    "Query": "SELECT (geof:distance(?dWKT, ?sWKT, uom:metre) AS ?distance)  WHERE{  yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?dGeom.  ?dGeom geo:asWKT ?dWKT.    yago:Scotland geo:hasGeometry ?sGeom.  ?sGeom geo:asWKT ?sWKT.      }",
    "Answer": "159308.875^^<http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#double>"
  },
  "567": {
    "Question": "Is Manchester eastern of Liverpool?",
    "Query": "ASK   WHERE {    yago:Manchester geo:hasGeometry ?mgeom.    ?mgeom geo:asWKT ?mwkt.       yago:Liverpool geo:hasGeometry ?lgeom.    ?lgeom geo:asWKT ?lwkt.       FILTER(strdf:right(?mwkt, ?lwkt)).   }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "568": {
    "Question": "Does the Mississippi pass through Nevada?",
    "Query": "ASK   WHERE{    yago:Mississippi yago:isLocatedIn yago:Nevada   }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "569": {
    "Question": "Is Dublin north of County Cork?",
    "Query": "ASK   WHERE {    yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?dublinGeom.    ?dublinGeom geo:asWKT ?dublinWKT.        yago:Cork geo:hasGeometry ?corkGeom.    ?corkGeom geo:asWKT ?corkWKT.        FILTER(strdf:above(?dublinWKT, ?corkWKT)).   }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "570": {
    "Question": "Is the Ladis north of Dublin?",
    "Query": "ASK   WHERE {    yago:Ladis geo:hasGeometry ?ladisGeom.    ?ladisGeom geo:asWKT ?ladisWKT.        yago:Dublin geo:hasGeometry ?dublinGeom.    ?dublinGeom geo:asWKT ?dublinWKT.        FILTER(strdf:above(?ladisWKT, ?dublinWKT)).   }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "571": {
    "Question": "Is the Whitehall west of the Trafalgar Square?",
    "Query": "ASK WHERE{    ?yago:Whitehall geo:hasGeometry ?a . ?a geo:asWKT ?A .  yago:Trafalgar_Square geo:hasGeometry ?b . ?b geo:asWKT ?B .  FILTER(strdf:left(?A,?B)) .     }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "572": {
    "Question": "What is the distance between Big Ben and London eye?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT (geof:distance(?A,?B, uom:meter) as ?distance) WHERE{    yago:Big_Ben geo:hasGeometry ?a . ?a geo:asWKT ?A .  yago:London_Eye geo:hasGeometry ?b . ?b geo:asWKT ?B .   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "573": {
    "Question": "How far is Milwaukee from Chicago?",
    "Query": "SELECT (geof:distance(?cWKT, ?mWKT, uom:metre) AS ?distance)   WHERE{   yago:Chicago geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom.   ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT.      yago:Milwaukee geo:hasGeometry ?mGeom.   ?mGeom geo:asWKT ?mWKT.   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "574": {
    "Question": "How far is mountain Skiddaw to Birmingham?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT (geof:distance(?A,?B, uom:meter) as ?distance) WHERE{    yago:Skiddaw geo:hasGeometry ?a . ?a geo:asWKT ?A .  yago:Birmingham geo:hasGeometry ?b . ?b geo:asWKT ?B .   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "575": {
    "Question": "How far is Nevada to the Niagara Falls?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT (geof:distance(?A,?B, uom:meter) as ?distance) WHERE{    yago:Nevada geo:hasGeometry ?a . ?a geo:asWKT ?A .  yago:Niagra_Falls geo:hasGeometry ?b . ?b geo:asWKT ?B .   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "576": {
    "Question": "Which islands are in New York City?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?island  WHERE {      ?island a y2geoo:OSM_island.      ?island geo:hasGeometry ?islandGeom.      ?islandGeom geo:asWKT ?islandWKT.            yago:New_York_City geo:hasGeometry ?newYorkGeom.      ?newYorkGeom geo:asWKT ?newYorkWKT.            FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?islandWKT, ?newYorkWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Ruffle_Bar_5134602  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Canarsie_Pol  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Yellow_Bar_Hassock_5145200  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rikers_Island  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Belmont_Island_5108730  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Rulers_Bar_Hassock_5134599  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Manhattan_8479493  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Roosevelt_Island  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rat_Island,_New_York  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_City_Island_7155386  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chimney_Sweeps_Islands"
  },
  "577": {
    "Question": "Which universities are in Oxford?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?u  WHERE {      ?u a yago:wordnet_university_108286569.      ?u yago:isLocatedIn yago:Oxford.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/University_of_Oxford  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oxford_Brookes_University  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Department_of_Biochemistry,_University_of_Oxford  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sally_McDonnell_Barksdale_Honors_College  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oxford-Man_Institute  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/School_of_Architecture,_Oxford_Brookes_University  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oxford_Aviation_Academy  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/College_of_International_Education  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/fr/École_de_management_de_Normandie  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/fr/CAE_Oxford_Aviation_Academy_Amsterdam"
  },
  "578": {
    "Question": "Does Liverpool have a stadium?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {      ?stadium a yago:wordnet_stadium_104295881.      ?stadium yago:isLocatedIn yago:Liverpool.  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "579": {
    "Question": "In which state the Los Angeles belongs to?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?state  WHERE {       ?state a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.       yago:Los_Angeles yago:isLocatedIn ?state.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/California"
  },
  "580": {
    "Question": "Which island is located south of island Hoy?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?island  WHERE {      yago:geoentity_Hoy_2646475 geo:hasGeometry ?geo1.      ?geo1 geo:asWKT ?wkt1.        ?island a y2geoo:OSM_island.      ?island geo:hasGeometry ?geo2.      ?geo2 geo:asWKT ?wkt2.        FILTER(strdf:below(?wkt2, ?wkt1)).  }  ORDER BY strdf:distance(?wkt1, ?wkt2)  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nauru"
  },
  "581": {
    "Question": "What are all the churches in Oklahoma City?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?church  WHERE {    ?church a yago:wordnet_church_103028079.    ?church yago:isLocatedIn yago:Glasgow.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Monastery_of_Our_Lady_of_the_Annunciation_of_Clear_Creek  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/First_Presbyterian_Church_(Coweta,_Oklahoma)  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/St._James_Episcopal_Church_(Wagoner,_Oklahoma)"
  },
  "582": {
    "Question": "What Province does the County of Cork belong to?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?province  WHERE {       ?province a yago:wordnet_state_108654360.       yago:County_Cork yago:isLocatedIn ?province  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Münster  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Munster"
  },
  "583": {
    "Question": "Which cities are within north of Miami?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?cities  WHERE {        ?cities a y2geoo:OSM_city.      ?cities geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom.      ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT.              <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Miami_4398117> geo:hasGeometry ?miGeom.      ?miGeom geo:asWKT ?miWKT.        FILTER( strdf:above(?cWKT, ?miWKT)).       }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Clifton_Hill,_Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hale,_Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bogard,_Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mendon,_Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/De_Witt,_Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Salisbury,_Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Marceline,_Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_Triplett_4412053  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Laclede,_Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Brunswick,_Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_W_B_Junction_4413206  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bosworth,_Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Brookfield,_Missouri"
  },
  "584": {
    "Question": "What memorials can I visit in Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mon  WHERE{    ?mon a yago:wordnet_memorial_103743902;     yago:isLocatedIn yago:Dublin.    }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Saint_Stephen's_Green  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kilmainham_Gaol  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Garden_of_Remembrance_(Dublin)  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Áras_an_Uachtaráin  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/St_Stephen's_Green  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wellington_Monument,_Dublin  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Irish_National_War_Memorial_Gardens  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Stardust_Memorial_Park"
  },
  "585": {
    "Question": "What museums can I visit in New York?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mus  WHERE{    ?mus a yago:wordnet_museum_103800563;       yago:isLocatedIn yago:New_York_City.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Metropolitan_Museum_of_Art  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_York_Public_Library  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_Modern_Art  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_the_City_of_New_York  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Solomon_R._Guggenheim_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/American_Museum_of_Natural_History  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dahesh_Museum_of_Art  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_York_Botanical_Garden  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ellis_Island  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Statue_of_Liberty_National_Monument  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Whitney_Museum_of_American_Art  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Intrepid_Sea,_Air_&amp;_Space_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Castle_Clinton  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fifth_Avenue  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Frick_Collection  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Anthology_Film_Archives  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/The_Cloisters  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/African_Burial_Ground_National_Monument  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/MoMA_PS1  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_York_Transit_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hall_of_Fame_for_Great_Americans  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chelsea_Art_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Brooklyn_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/American_Folk_Art_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_the_Moving_Image_(New_York_City)  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hamilton_Grange_National_Memorial  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/International_Center_of_Photography  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Grant's_Tomb  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/The_Art_of_This_Century_gallery  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/South_Street_Seaport  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Staten_Island_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Jewish_Museum_(Manhattan)  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_for_African_Art  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/El_Museo_del_Barrio  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Floyd_Bennett_Field  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Noguchi_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Socrates_Sculpture_Park  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Brooklyn_Botanic_Garden  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Schuyler  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Jacques_Marchais_Museum_of_Tibetan_Art  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New-York_Historical_Society  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hayden_Planetarium  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cooper–Hewitt,_National_Design_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Art_in_General  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Neue_Galerie_New_York  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Queens_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Van_Cortlandt_House_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_York_City_Police_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Drawing_Center  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Morgan_Library_&_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Africa_Center  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Studio_Museum_in_Harlem  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sailors'_Snug_Harbor  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Washington_Crossing_Historic_Park  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hispanic_Society_of_America  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Brooklyn_Children's_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tibet_House  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Theodore_Roosevelt_Birthplace_National_Historic_Site  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lower_East_Side_Tenement_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fisher_Landau_Center  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_Sex  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/China_Institute  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_Biblical_Art  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/American_Numismatic_Society  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rubin_Museum_of_Art  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_American_Finance  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ukrainian_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/SculptureCenter  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Brooklyn_Historical_Society  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/MoCADA  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Yeshiva_University_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Merchant's_House_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dyckman_House  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nicholas_Roerich_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/United_Nations_Art_Collection  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Alice_Austen_House  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/King_Manor  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bronx_Museum_of_the_Arts  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Historic_House_Trust  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/FusionArts_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/International_Print_Center_New_York  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kingsland_Homestead  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Newhouse_Center_for_Contemporary_Art  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Derfner_Judaica_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/American_Museum_of_Immigration  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_York_Tattoo_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Japan_Society_(Manhattan)  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_York_Yankees_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/The_Encyclopedic_Palace_of_the_World  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Grey_Art_Gallery  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Culture_Shed  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/The_Morgan_Library_&amp;_Museum"
  },
  "586": {
    "Question": "Does a river cross London?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE{       ?river a yago:wordnet_river_109411430;        yago:isLocatedIn yago:London.  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "587": {
    "Question": "What states does the Mississippi river flow through ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?state  WHERE{    yago:Mississippi_River yago:isLocatedIn ?state.    ?state a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States    }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Arkansas  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Minnesota  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Illinois  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Louisiana  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mississippi  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tennessee  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Iowa  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kentucky  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wisconsin"
  },
  "588": {
    "Question": "Which highways pass from Texas ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?highw  WHERE{    ?highw a yago:wordnet_highway_103519981;       yago:isLocatedIn yago:Texas.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Interstate_820  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Interstate_610_(Texas)  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Interstate_410  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Interstate_635_(Texas)"
  },
  "589": {
    "Question": "Which river crosses Northern Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?river  WHERE{     ?river a yago:wordnet_river_109411430;           yago:isLocatedIn yago:Northern_Ireland.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Bann  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Erne  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Foyle  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Finn  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rivers_of_Ireland  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Farset  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Shimna_River  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Blackstaff_River  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Duff_River  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Moyola  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Saint_Columbs_Rill"
  },
  "590": {
    "Question": "Is there a river that crosses Scotland?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE{     ?river a yago:wordnet_river_109411430;           yago:isLocatedIn yago:Scotland.  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "591": {
    "Question": "Find all the museums in Dublin",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county  WHERE{     ?county a yago:wordnet_museum_103800563;             yago:isLocatedIn yago:Dublin.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Chester_Beatty_Library  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Irish_Museum_of_Modern_Art  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/National_Wax_Museum_(Ireland)  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Guinness_Storehouse  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/National_Library_of_Ireland  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kilmainham_Gaol  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin_City_Gallery_The_Hugh_Lane  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/National_Museum_of_Ireland  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ashtown_Castle  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/National_Print_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Áras_an_Uachtaráin  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/State_Heraldic_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Royal_Hibernian_Academy  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/National_Gallery_of_Ireland  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/The_Douglas_Hyde_Gallery  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Irish_Jewish_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Weingreen_Museum_of_Biblical_Antiquities  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Natural_History_Museum_(Ireland)  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/James_Joyce_Centre  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin_Writers_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Drimnagh_Castle  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Marsh's_Library  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kerlin_Gallery  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Irish_Music_Hall_of_Fame  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_Irish_Industry  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Science_Gallery  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/National_Photographic_Archive  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/National_Leprechaun_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/National_Museum_of_Ireland_–_Archaeology  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/An_Post_Museum  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/The_Little_Museum_of_Dublin  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublinia  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Old_Jameson_Distillery"
  },
  "592": {
    "Question": "Find the airports that belong to Scotland",
    "Query": "SELECT ?airport  WHERE{     ?airport a yago:wordnet_airport_102692232;             yago:isLocatedIn yago:Scotland.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sumburgh_Airport  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/RAF_Lossiemouth  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tingwall_Airport  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/RAF_Machrihanish  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/RAF_Drem  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/RAF_Montrose  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/RAF_Errol  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/RAF_Grangemouth  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/RM_Condor  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/RAF_Dumfries"
  },
  "593": {
    "Question": "Is there a river that crosses California?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE{        ?canal a yago:wordnet_river_109411430;               yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Georgia_(country)>.  }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "594": {
    "Question": "In which state does Dallas belongs to?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?state  WHERE{        ?state a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.        yago:Dallas yago:isLocatedIn ?state.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Texas"
  },
  "595": {
    "Question": "Are there any waterfalls in Dublin?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE{        ?water a yago:wordnet_waterfall_109475292;               yago:isLocatedIn yago:Dublin.  }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "596": {
    "Question": "Which rivers cross Glasgow?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?rivers  WHERE{        ?rivers a yago:wordnet_river_109411430;               yago:isLocatedIn  yago:Glasgow.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Levern  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/de/White_Cart_Water"
  },
  "597": {
    "Question": "Which mountains exist in Dublin?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mount  WHERE{        ?mount a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803;               yago:isLocatedIn  yago:Dublin.  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Larch_Hill"
  },
  "598": {
    "Question": "In which state is Detroit?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?state   WHERE {    ?state a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.    yago:Detroit yago:isLocatedIn ?state.   }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Michigan"
  },
  "599": {
    "Question": "Which are the districts of Greater Manchester?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x where { ?x rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OS_District>; geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom. ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT. <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Greater_Manchester> geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom. ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cWKT,?iWKT)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "600": {
    "Question": "How many universities there are in Houston?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?university) AS ?numUniversities)   WHERE {    ?university a yago:wordnet_university_108286569.    ?university yago:isLocatedIn yago:Houston.   }",
    "Answer": 28
  },
  "601": {
    "Question": "Is there a hospital in Galway?",
    "Query": "ASK    WHERE{    ?hospital a yago:wordnet_hospital_103540595;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:Galway.   }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "602": {
    "Question": "Which are the states of the United States?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?state   WHERE {    ?state a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.   }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Delaware  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Alaska  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Iowa  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Texas  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Louisiana  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rhode_Island  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ohio  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kansas  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wyoming  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Maryland  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tennessee  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Utah  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Illinois  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pennsylvania  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Virginia  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/California  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/West_Virginia  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_Dakota  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Arkansas  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Mexico  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Jersey  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hawaii  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Vermont  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Montana  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Colorado  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Michigan  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Georgia_(U.S._state)  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oklahoma  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Idaho  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_Carolina  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Connecticut  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Alabama  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/South_Carolina  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Maine  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Hampshire  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wisconsin  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Washington_(state)  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Florida  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Indiana  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Arizona  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kentucky  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mississippi  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nevada  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Missouri  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Massachusetts  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nebraska  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oregon  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/geoentity_New_York_5128638  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/South_Dakota  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Minnesota"
  },
  "603": {
    "Question": "Has Athlone a university?",
    "Query": "ASK   WHERE {   ?university a yago:wordnet_university_108286569.   ?university yago:isLocatedIn yago:Athlone   }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "604": {
    "Question": "Which museums can I visit in Washington DC?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?museum   WHERE{      ?museum a yago:wordnet_museum_103800563;    yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Washington_(state)>.   }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/EMP_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Vancouver   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Klondike_Gold_Rush_National_Historical_Park   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Okanogan   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Seattle_Art_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cape_Disappointment_State_Park   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Columbia_State_Park   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Flagler_State_Park   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Worden   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_Flight   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Washington_State_History_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Daybreak_Star_Cultural_Center   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pacific_Science_Center   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Flying_Heritage_Collection   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Seattle_Asian_Art_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Frye_Art_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_History_&_Industry_(MOHAI)   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Henry_Art_Gallery   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Center_for_Wooden_Boats   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Consolidated_Works   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mount_St._Helens_National_Volcanic_Monument   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_Glass   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Nordic_Heritage_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Camlann_Medieval_Village   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wing_Luke_Museum_of_the_Asian_Pacific_American_Experience   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northwest_Seaport   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Admiralty_Head_Light   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Vancouver_National_Historic_Site   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northwest_Railway_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/San_Juan_Island_National_Historical_Park   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ginkgo_Petrified_Forest_State_Park   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Walla_Walla   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_Northwest_Art   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Whitman_Mission_National_Historic_Site   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Nisqually   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tacoma_Art_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northern_Pacific_Railway_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Olympic_Flight_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Seattle_Children's_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mukilteo_Light   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/America's_Car_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Simcoe   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Steilacoom   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Padilla_Bay   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Browns_Point_Light   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/North_Head_Light   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Grays_Harbor_Light   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Dungeness_Light   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Point_No_Point_Light_(Washington)   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Naval_Undersea_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Future_of_Flight_Aviation_Center_&_Boeing_Tour   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Maryhill_Museum_of_Art   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Olympic_Sculpture_Park   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/SPARK_Museum_of_Electrical_Invention   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bellingham_Railway_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bellevue_Arts_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Georgetown_Steam_Plant   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Wenatchee_Valley_Museum_&_Cultural_Center   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Daniel_R._Bigelow_House   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pomeroy_Living_History_Farm   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northwest_African_American_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Makah_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ansorge_Hotel   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Riverside_State_Park   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/University_District_Museum_Without_Walls   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Museum_of_Communications   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Stonerose_Interpretive_Center   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/7_Wonders_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tenino_Depot   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/History_House_of_Greater_Seattle   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Camp_6_Logging_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Clark_County_Historical_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Seattle_Mariners_Hall_of_Fame   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Coast_Guard_Museum_Northwest   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/KidsQuest_Children's_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Karshner_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Olmstead_Place_State_Park   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Port_Townsend_Aero_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Puget_Sound_Navy_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Working_Waterfront_Maritime_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Edmonds_Historical_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Renton_History_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Heritage_Flight_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Leavenworth_Nutcracker_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Yakima_Valley_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Quilcene_Historical_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Living_Computer_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rosalie_Whyel_Museum_of_Doll_Art   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hands_On_Children's_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/DuPont_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Washington_Women's_History_Consortium   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Washington_National_Guard_Museum   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Vintage_Motorcycle_Museum_(Chehalis,_Washington)"
  },
  "605": {
    "Question": "In which county is located Disneyland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county   WHERE{    ?county a yago:wordnet_county_108546183.    yago:Disneyland yago:isLocatedIn ?county.   }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Orange_County,_California"
  },
  "606": {
    "Question": "From which countries do the Appalachian mountains pass by?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?country   WHERE{    ?country a yago:wordnet_country_108544813.        yago:Appalachian_Mountains yago:isLocatedIn ?country   }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/United_States   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Canada   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Quebec"
  },
  "607": {
    "Question": "The Midwest is comprised of which states ?",
    "Query": "Select ?state   where {                 ?state a a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.                  ?state yago:isLocatedIn yago:Midwest.  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "608": {
    "Question": "Which river runs through Londonderry?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?river  WHERE {      ?river a y2geoo:OSM_stream.      ?river geo:hasGeometry ?rGeom.      ?rGeom geo:asWKT ?rWKT.        ?londonderry y2geoo:hasOSNI_Name Londonderry.      ?londonderry geo:hasGeometry ?geom.      ?geom geo:asWKT ?WKT.        FILTER(geof:sfCrosses(?rWKT, ?WKT)).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "609": {
    "Question": "Which are the islands in Lake Okeechobee?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?island   WHERE {    ?island a y2geoo:OSM_island.    ?island geo:hasGeometry ?islandGeom.    ?islandGeom geo:asWKT ?islandWKT.        yago:Lake_Okeechobee geo:hasGeometry ?lGeom.    ?lGeom geo:asWKT ?lWKT.        FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?islandWKT, ?lWKT)).   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "610": {
    "Question": "Which cities does Missouri River flow through?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city   WHERE{    ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735.    yago:Missouri yago:isLocatedIn ?city.   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "611": {
    "Question": "Which rivers cross Reading, Berkshire?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?rivers   WHERE{    ?rivers a yago:wordnet_river_109411430;    yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Reading,_Berkshire>.   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "612": {
    "Question": "Which river cross Cape Canaveral?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?rivers   WHERE{    ?rivers a yago:wordnet_river_109411430;    yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cape_Canaveral>.   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "613": {
    "Question": "Which counties are located in the San Francisco Bay?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county   WHERE{    ?county a yago:wordnet_county_108546183;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:San_Francisco_Bay   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "614": {
    "Question": "In which county is located the Silicon Valley?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county   WHERE{    ?county a yago:wordnet_county_108546183.    yago:Silicon_Valley yago:isLocatedIn ?county.   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "615": {
    "Question": "In what region does Newry belong?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?region\r   WHERE{\r    ?region a yago:wordnet_region_108546183.\r    yago:Newry yago:isLocatedIn ?region.\r   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "616": {
    "Question": "Which streams flows through cities?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x where { ?x rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_stream; geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom1. ?cGeom1 geo:asWKT ?cWKT1. ?y rdf:type y2geoo:OSM_city; geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom2. ?cGeom2 geo:asWKT ?cWKT2.  FILTER(geof:sfCrosses(?cWKT1,?cWKT2)) }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "617": {
    "Question": "In which island of New York is the Statue of Liberty?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?island    WHERE{    ?island a yago:wikicat_Islands_of_New_York.    yago:Statue_of_Liberty yago:isLocatedIn ?island.   }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Manhattan   http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Liberty_Island"
  },
  "618": {
    "Question": "Which counties of England border Wales?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county  WHERE {      ?county a y2geoo:OS_County.      ?county geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom.      ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT.        yago:Wales geo:hasGeometry ?wGeom.      ?wGeom geo:asWKT ?wWKT.        yago:England geo:hasGeometry ?eGeom.      ?eGeom geo:asWKT ?eWKT.        FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cWKT, ?eWKT)).      FILTER(geof:sfTouches(?cWKT, ?wWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Gloucestershire"
  },
  "619": {
    "Question": "What cities in Connacht have castles?",
    "Query": null,
    "Answer": null
  },
  "620": {
    "Question": "In which street of Leeds is the Royal Armouries Museum ?",
    "Query": null,
    "Answer": null
  },
  "621": {
    "Question": "Which city in Northern Ireland has less than 10000 population?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city  WHERE {      ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735.      ?city yago:isLocatedIn yago:Northern_Ireland.      ?city yagoinfobox:population ?pop.      FILTER(xsd:integer(?pop) < 10000).  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Strangford"
  },
  "622": {
    "Question": "Is there a mountain taller than 1000 meters in Northern Ireland?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {      ?mountain a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803.      ?mountain yago:isLocatedIn yago:Northern_Ireland.      ?mountain yagoinfobox:elevationm ?height.        FILTER(xsd:float(?height) > 1000).  }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "623": {
    "Question": "Which is the most populous county of California?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county  WHERE {      ?county a yago:wordnet_county_108546183.      ?county yago:isLocatedIn yago:California.      ?county yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?population.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?population))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Los_Angeles_County,_California"
  },
  "624": {
    "Question": "Which rivers mount into Lake Lough Corrib?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?inflow  WHERE {      yago:Lough_Corrib yagoinfobox:inflow ?inflow.  }",
    "Answer": "[[Cregg River]], [[River Clare]], [[Black River (Ireland)|Black River]]"
  },
  "625": {
    "Question": "Which rivers in Ireland are longer than 5 km?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?river  WHERE {      ?river a yago:wordnet_river_109411430.      ?river yago:isLocatedIn yago:Ireland.      ?river yagoinfobox:length ?length.        FILTER(xsd:integer(?length) > 5).  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Corrib  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Lee  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Bandon  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Dodder  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Fergus"
  },
  "626": {
    "Question": "Which mountain of England has a height closeset to 950 meters in absolute value?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?x ?y  WHERE {      ?x a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803.      ?x yagoinfobox:elevationm ?y.      ?x yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_Kingdom.        }  ORDER BY ASC(ABS(xsd:integer(?y) - 950))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cairn_Gorm        1,245"
  },
  "627": {
    "Question": "Which lakes in Scotland have depth more than 100 meters?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?lakes  WHERE{    ?lakes a  yago:wordnet_lake_109328904;       yago:isLocatedIn yago:Scotland;       yagoinfobox:maxdepth ?depth.    FILTER(xsd:float(?depth) > 100)  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Loch_Shiel  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Loch_Loyal  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Loch_Arkaig  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Loch_Maree  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Loch_Lomond  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Loch_Morar  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Loch_Lochy  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Loch_Tay  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Loch_Ness"
  },
  "628": {
    "Question": "Which is the most famous monument in London?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mon (xsd:integer(REPLACE(?vis, ,|\\\\.|\\\\D+\\\\s, )) AS ?visitors)  WHERE{    ?mon a yago:wordnet_memorial_103743902;     yago:isLocatedIn yago:London;     yagoinfobox:visitationnum ?vis  }  ORDER BY DESC(?visitors)  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Tower_of_London"
  },
  "629": {
    "Question": "Which village in Scotland has less than 1000 population ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?village  WHERE{  ?village a yago:wordnet_village_108672738;           yago:isLocatedIn yago:Scotland;           yagoinfobox:population ?pop.  FILTER(xsd:integer(?pop)<1000)  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bowmore  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Lanark  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Kyle_of_Lochalsh  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Roxburgh  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Uig,_Skye  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Braemar  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Brodick  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lochranza  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ecclefechan  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dornie  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Aberlour  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Drumoak  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Allasdale  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Aberfoyle,_Stirling  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Isle_of_Whithorn  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Culross  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Aberlady  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Inverie  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Acharacle  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Abbey  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dallas,_Moray  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ravenscraig  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mellon_Udrigle"
  },
  "630": {
    "Question": "Which bridges in Ireland are longer than 10 meters?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?bridge  WHERE {      ?bridge a yago:wordnet_bridge_102898711.      ?bridge yago:isLocatedIn yago:Ireland.      ?bridge yagoinfobox:length ?length.        FILTER(xsd:integer(?length) > 10).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "631": {
    "Question": "Which cities have population more than 5.000.000 in United States ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city  WHERE{  ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;          yagoinfobox:populationtotal  ?pop;          yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_States.  FILTER(xsd:integer(?pop) > 5000000)  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "632": {
    "Question": "What is the length of the river that flows through New York?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?length   WHERE{    ?river a yago:wordnet_river_109411430;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:New_York;    yagoinfobox:length ?length.   }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "633": {
    "Question": "What are the 10 biggest stadiums in United States of America?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?stadium  WHERE {      ?stadium a yago:wordnet_stadium_104295881.      ?stadium yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_States.      ?statium yagoinfobox:capacity ?capacity.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?capacity))  LIMIT 10",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sleep_Train_Arena  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Staples_Center  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Robert_F._Kennedy_Memorial_Stadium  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Toyota_Park  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Columbus_Crew_Stadium  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Gillette_Stadium  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lucas_Oil_Stadium  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mercedes-Benz_Superdome  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Sun_Life_Stadium  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Edward_Jones_Dome"
  },
  "634": {
    "Question": "Which is the tallest dam in the USA?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?d (xsd:integer(replace(?height, ft, )) AS ?hint)  WHERE {      ?d a yago:wordnet_dam_103160309.      ?d yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_States.      ?d yagoinfobox:damheight ?height.  }  ORDER BY DESC(?hint)  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ah_Pah_Dam"
  },
  "635": {
    "Question": "Which city in the USA has the most airports?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city (COUNT(?airport) AS ?numAirports)  WHERE {      ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735.      ?city yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_States.            ?airport a yago:wordnet_airport_102692232.      ?airport yago:isLocatedIn ?city.  }  GROUP BY ?city  ORDER BY DESC(?numAirports)  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_York_City"
  },
  "636": {
    "Question": "How many lakes are in Michigan?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?lake) AS ?numLakes) WHERE { ?lake a y2geoo:OSM_lake. ?lake geo:hasGeometry ?lakeGeom. ?lakeGeom geo:asWKT ?lakeWKT. yago:Michigan geo:hasGeometry ?mGeom. ?mGeom geo:asWKT ?mWKT. FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?lakeWKT, ?mWKT)). }",
    "Answer": 2019
  },
  "637": {
    "Question": "How many libraries does Miami have?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?library) AS ?numLibraries)  WHERE {      ?library a yago:wordnet_library_103660909.      ?library yago:isLocatedIn yago:Miami.  }",
    "Answer": 0
  },
  "638": {
    "Question": "Which city has the largest park in the USA?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city  WHERE {        ?park a yago:wordnet_park_108615149.      ?park yagoinfobox:area ?area.      ?park yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_States.      ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735.      ?park yago:isLocatedIn ?city.  }  ORDER BY DESC(?area)  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_York_City"
  },
  "639": {
    "Question": "Which is the oldest monument in the UK?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?m  WHERE {        ?m a yago:wordnet_memorial_103743902.        ?m yagoinfobox:startdate ?date.        ?m yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_Kingdom.  }  ORDER BY ?date  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Watkin's_Tower"
  },
  "640": {
    "Question": "How many schools are in Brighton?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?school) AS ?numSchools)  WHERE {      ?school a yago:wordnet_school_108276720.      ?school yago:isLocatedIn yago:Brighton.  }",
    "Answer": 11
  },
  "641": {
    "Question": "How many universities are in Belfast?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?university) AS ?numUniversities)  WHERE {      ?university a yago:wordnet_university_108286569.      ?university yago:isLocatedIn yago:Belfast.  }",
    "Answer": 9
  },
  "642": {
    "Question": "How many lakes does Minneapolis have?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?lake) AS ?numLakes)  WHERE {      ?lake a yago:wordnet_lake_109328904.      ?lake yago:isLocatedIn yago:Minneapolis.  }",
    "Answer": 6
  },
  "643": {
    "Question": "How many States does USA have?",
    "Query": "select (count(distinct ?x) as ?totalX)  where { ?x rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/NBD_State>; geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom. ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT. <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/United_States> geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom. ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cWKT,?iWKT)) }",
    "Answer": 50
  },
  "644": {
    "Question": "How many ceremonial counties does England have?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?county) AS ?numCounties)  WHERE {      ?county a yago:wikicat_Ceremonial_counties.      ?county yago:isLocatedIn yago:England.  }",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  "645": {
    "Question": "Which is the highest mountain of Wales?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mountain  WHERE {      ?mountain a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803.      ?mountain yago:isLocatedIn yago:Wales.      ?mountain yagoinfobox:elevationm ?height.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?height))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Snowdon"
  },
  "646": {
    "Question": "How many islands does Scotland have?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?island) AS ?numIslands)  WHERE {      yago:Scotland geo:hasGeometry ?sGeom.      ?sGeom geo:asWKT ?sWKT.        ?island a y2geoo:OSM_island.      ?island geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom.      ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT.        FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?iWKT, ?sWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": 19
  },
  "647": {
    "Question": "How many National Parks does Wales have?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?park) AS ?numParks)  WHERE {      ?park a yago:wordnet_national_park_108600992.      ?park yago:isLocatedIn yago:Wales.  }",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  "648": {
    "Question": "How many County Councils does the Republic of Ireland have?",
    "Query": "select (count(distinct ?x) as ?totalX)  where { ?x rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSI_County_Council>; geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom. ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT. <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Republic_of_Ireland> geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom. ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfContains(?iWKT,?cWKT)) }",
    "Answer": 10
  },
  "649": {
    "Question": "Which are the three largest lakes of Republic of Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?lake  WHERE {      ?lake a yago:wordnet_lake_109328904.      ?lake yago:isLocatedIn yago:Republic_of_Ireland.      ?lake yago:hasArea ?area.  }  ORDER BY DESC(?area)  LIMIT 3",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lough_Gur"
  },
  "650": {
    "Question": "How many airports does England have ?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?airport) AS ?numAirports)  WHERE {    ?airport a yago:wordnet_airport_102692232.    ?airport yago:isLocatedIn yago:England.  }",
    "Answer": 34
  },
  "651": {
    "Question": "How many mountains that are more than 1km high are there in Scotland?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?mountain) AS ?numMountains)  WHERE {      ?mountain a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803.      ?mountain yago:isLocatedIn yago:Scotland.      ?mountain yagoinfobox:elevationm ?elevation.        FILTER(xsd:integer(?elevation) > 1000).  }",
    "Answer": 80
  },
  "652": {
    "Question": "How many bridges in Ireland have been opened in the last 10 years?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?bridge  WHERE {      ?bridge a yago:wordnet_bridge_102898711.      ?bridge yago:isLocatedIn yago:Ireland.      ?bridge yagoinfobox:constructiondate ?date.      FILTER(2021 - year(xsd:date(?date)) <= 10).  }",
    "Answer": "Virtuoso 22007 Error DT006: Cannot convert 18 May 1945 to datetime : Incorrect year delimiter"
  },
  "653": {
    "Question": "How many cities in the UK have a population of less than 5 million?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?city) AS ?numCities)  WHERE {      ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735.      ?city yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_Kingdom.      ?city yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?population.        FILTER(xsd:integer(?population) < 5000000)  }",
    "Answer": 6
  },
  "654": {
    "Question": "How many churches are there in Glasgow?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?church) AS ?numChurches)  WHERE {    ?church a yago:wordnet_church_103028079.    ?church yago:isLocatedIn yago:Glasgow.  }",
    "Answer": 5
  },
  "655": {
    "Question": "How many hotels are there in Central London?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?hotel) AS ?numHotels)  WHERE {      ?hotel a yago:wordnet_hotel_103542333.      ?hotel yago:isLocatedIn yago:Central_London.  }",
    "Answer": 0
  },
  "656": {
    "Question": "What is the longest river in Northern Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?river  WHERE {      ?river a yago:wordnet_river_109411430.      ?river yago:isLocatedIn yago:Northern_Ireland.      ?river yagoinfobox:length ?length  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?length))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Moyola"
  },
  "657": {
    "Question": "What are the 5 most populous cities in England?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city  WHERE {      ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735.      ?city yago:isLocatedIn yago:England.      ?city yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?population.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(replace(?population, ,, )))  LIMIT 5",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/London  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Birmingham  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Liverpool  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bristol  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/City_of_Sunderland"
  },
  "658": {
    "Question": "Which is the oldest castle in Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?castle  WHERE {      ?castle a yago:wordnet_palace_103878066.      ?castle yago:isLocatedIn yago:Ireland.      ?castle yagoinfobox:completiondate ?date.  }  ORDER BY ?date  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dunguaire_Castle"
  },
  "659": {
    "Question": "What are the largest malls in New York?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mall  WHERE {    ?mall a yago:wikicat_Shopping_malls_in_New_York_City.    ?mall yagoinfobox:floorarea ?area.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(replace(?area, ,, )))  LIMIT 3",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Queens_Center  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Rego_Center  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Bronx_Terminal_Market"
  },
  "660": {
    "Question": "How many museums are there in London?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?x) AS ?numMuseums)  Where{?x a  yago:wordnet_museum_103800563.          ?x    yago:isLocatedIn yago:London}",
    "Answer": 158
  },
  "661": {
    "Question": "How many churches are there in Newcastle Emlyn?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?church) AS ?numChurches)  WHERE {    ?church a yago:wordnet_church_103028079.    ?church yago:isLocatedIn yago:Glasgow.  }",
    "Answer": 0
  },
  "662": {
    "Question": "How many lakes are there in the Ireland?",
    "Query": "select (count(distinct ?x) as ?totalX)  where { ?x rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_lake>; geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom. ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT. <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Republic_of_Ireland> geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom. ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cWKT,?iWKT)) }",
    "Answer": 902
  },
  "663": {
    "Question": "How many international airports are there in Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?airp) AS ?numOfAirports)  WHERE {    ?airp a yago:wordnet_airport_102692232.    ?airp yago:isLocatedIn yago:Ireland.  }",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  "664": {
    "Question": "How many universities are there in Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?uni))  WHERE {    ?uni a yago:wordnet_university_108286569.    ?uni yago:isLocatedIn yago:Ireland.  }",
    "Answer": 10
  },
  "665": {
    "Question": "How many are the United States of America?",
    "Query": "select (count(distinct ?x) as ?totalX)  where { ?x rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/NBD_State>; geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom. ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT. <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/United_States> geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom. ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cWKT,?iWKT)) }",
    "Answer": 50
  },
  "666": {
    "Question": "Which state of USA has the lowest population density?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?state ?x ?y  WHERE {      ?state a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.      ?state yago:hasCapital ?x.      ?x yagoinfobox:populationdensitysqmi ?y  }  ORDER BY ASC(xsd:integer(?y))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Michigan"
  },
  "667": {
    "Question": "How many mountain peaks in Scotland are in a height of at least 900 meters?",
    "Query": "SELECT COUNT(?x)  WHERE {      ?x a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803.      ?x yagoinfobox:elevationm ?y.      ?x yago:isLocatedIn yago:Scotland.    FILTER(xsd:integer(?y) > 900). }",
    "Answer": 163
  },
  "668": {
    "Question": "Which state capital of USA has the largest population?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?state ?x ?y  WHERE {      ?state a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.      ?state yago:hasCapital ?x.      ?x yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?y  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?y))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Illinois"
  },
  "669": {
    "Question": "Is Galway the largest county in Connacht?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE {       ?x a yago:wordnet_county_108546183;           yago:isLocatedIn yago:Connacht;           yago:hasArea ?area.       yago:County_Galway yago:hasArea ?Garea;           yago:isLocatedIn yago:Connacht.       FILTER(xsd:float(?area)<xsd:float(?Garea))    }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "670": {
    "Question": "Which is the smallest lake in Ireland?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x ?property where { ?x rdf:type <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/wordnet_lake_109328904>; <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/hasArea> ?property. ?x yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ireland>. } ORDER BY ASC(xsd:float(?property)) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "671": {
    "Question": "What is the largest lake in United Kingdom?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x ?property where { ?x rdf:type <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/wordnet_lake_109328904>; <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/hasArea> ?property. ?x yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/United_Kingdom>. } ORDER BY DESC(xsd:float(?property)) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "672": {
    "Question": "What is the largest city in Florida?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x ?property where { ?x rdf:type <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/wordnet_city_108524735>; <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/infobox/en/area> ?property. ?x yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Florida>. } ORDER BY DESC(xsd:float(?property)) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "673": {
    "Question": "What is the highest mountain in Arizona?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mountain  WHERE{   ?mountain a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803;        yagoinfobox:elevationm ?height;        yago:isLocatedIn yago:Arizona.         }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(REPLACE(?height, ,, )))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Pusch_Ridge"
  },
  "674": {
    "Question": "What is the longest river in the England ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?rivers  WHERE{    ?rivers a yago:wordnet_river_109411430;           yago:isLocatedIn yago:England;           yagoinfobox:length ?length.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?length))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Nidd"
  },
  "675": {
    "Question": "Is Munster the least populated province of Ireland ?",
    "Query": "ASK  WHERE{   <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Munster>  yago:isLocatedIn ?irl.   FILTER(?irl=<http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ireland>)       }",
    "Answer": true
  },
  "676": {
    "Question": "What are the 5 biggest cities by land area , in the State of California ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city  WHERE{   ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;         yago:hasArea   ?area;         yago:isLocatedIn yago:California.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?area))  LIMIT 5",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Lake_Elsinore  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Los_Angeles  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/San_Diego  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Fort_Bragg  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/California_City,_California"
  },
  "677": {
    "Question": "What is the total population of the 5 biggest cities of the United Kingdom ?",
    "Query": "SELECT SUM(xsd:integer(REPLACE(?pop, \\\\(.*\\\\)|\\\\{.*\\\\}|\\\\(|\\\\)|\\\\[|\\\\]|\\\\D+, )) ) AS ?totalpop  WHERE{    {SELECT ?city  WHERE{   ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;         yago:hasArea   ?area;         yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_Kingdom.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?area))  LIMIT 5}    ?city yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?pop.  }",
    "Answer": 8495872
  },
  "678": {
    "Question": "Which is the largest lake in the USA ?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x ?property where { ?x rdf:type <http://kr.di.uoa.gr/yago2geo/ontology/OSM_lake>; geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom; <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/hasArea> ?property. ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT. <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/United_States> geo:hasGeometry ?iGeom. ?iGeom geo:asWKT ?iWKT.  FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?cWKT,?iWKT)) } ORDER BY DESC(xsd:float(?property)) LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "679": {
    "Question": "How many towns with a population between 5000 and 10000 are there in Norfolk ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?towns  WHERE{    ?towns a yago:wordnet_town_108665504;       yago:isLocatedIn yago:Norfolk;       yagoinfobox:population ?pop.    FILTER(xsd:integer(?pop)>5000 && xsd:integer(?pop)>10000)  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Thetford  http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dereham"
  },
  "680": {
    "Question": "How many towns in England , with a population less than 50000 have an airport ?",
    "Query": "SELECT DISTINCT ?towns  WHERE{    ?towns a yago:wordnet_town_108665504;       yago:isLocatedIn yago:England;       yagoinfobox:population ?pop.    ?airport a yago:wordnet_airport_102692232;             yago:isLocatedIn ?town.    FILTER(xsd:integer(?pop)>50000)  }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Royal_Tunbridge_Wells"
  },
  "681": {
    "Question": "Which county of England has the lowest number of rivers ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county  (COUNT(?rivers) AS ?numRivers)  WHERE{    ?county a yago:wordnet_county_108546183;       yago:isLocatedIn yago:England.    ?rivers a yago:wordnet_river_109411430;             yago:isLocatedIn ?county.  }  GROUP BY ?county  ORDER BY ASC(?numRivers)  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/City_of_London"
  },
  "682": {
    "Question": "In how many states are there Intercontinental hotels ?",
    "Query": "SELECT COUNT(?states) AS ?statesnum  WHERE{    ?states a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.    ?hotel a yago:wordnet_hotel_103542333;           yago:isLocatedIn ?states.    FILTER regex(?hotel, Intercontinental, i).  }",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  "683": {
    "Question": "How many inhabited islands belong to the United States ?",
    "Query": "SELECT COUNT(?x) AS ?islandnum  WHERE{   ?x a yago:wordnet_island_109316454;      yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_States;      yagoinfobox:populationestimate ?pop.  FILTER(xsd:integer(REPLACE(?pop, ,|\\\\.|\\\\D+, ))>0)  }",
    "Answer": 4
  },
  "684": {
    "Question": "What is 10th largest town in Alaska ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?town ?area  WHERE{  {SELECT DISTINCT ?town ?area  WHERE {      ?town a yago:wordnet_town_108665504;           yago:isLocatedIn yago:Alaska;           yago:hasArea   ?area.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:float(?area))  LIMIT 10}    ?town yago:hasArea  ?area.  }  ORDER BY ASC(xsd:float(?area))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/College,_Alaska"
  },
  "685": {
    "Question": "How many castles are there in Scotland?",
    "Query": "SELECT COUNT(?castles) AS ?castlesnum  WHERE{     ?castles a yago:wordnet_palace_103878066;           yago:isLocatedIn yago:Scotland.  }",
    "Answer": 77
  },
  "686": {
    "Question": "Which country has the biggest population in the United Kingdom?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county ?pop  WHERE{     ?county a yago:wordnet_county_108546183;             yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_Kingdom;             yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?pop.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(replace(?pop, ,, )))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cardiff"
  },
  "687": {
    "Question": "Which is the largest settlement in Northern Ireland?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x where { ?x rdf:type <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/wordnet_settlement_108672562>; yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northern_Ireland>. }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "688": {
    "Question": "How many cities are there in Alabama?",
    "Query": "SELECT COUNT(?cities) AS ?citiesnum  WHERE{        ?cities a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;               yago:isLocatedIn yago:Alabama.  }",
    "Answer": 561
  },
  "689": {
    "Question": "How many villages are there in California?",
    "Query": "SELECT COUNT(?villages) AS ?citiesnum  WHERE{        ?villages a yago:wordnet_village_108672738;               yago:isLocatedIn yago:California.  }",
    "Answer": 113
  },
  "690": {
    "Question": "Which county is the biggest in the United States?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county  WHERE{     ?county a yago:wordnet_county_108546183;             yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_States;             yago:hasArea ?area.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:float(replace(?area, ,, )))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Hawaii_(island)"
  },
  "691": {
    "Question": "Which county has the lowest population in the United States?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county ?pop  WHERE{     ?county a yago:wordnet_county_108546183;             yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_States;             yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?pop.  }  ORDER BY ASC(xsd:integer(replace(?pop, ,, )))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Garfield_Township,_Finney_County,_Kansas"
  },
  "692": {
    "Question": "How many stadiums Georgia has?",
    "Query": "SELECT COUNT(?stadium) AS ?stadiumnum  WHERE{        ?stadium a yago:wordnet_stadium_104295881;               yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Georgia_(country)>.  }",
    "Answer": 10
  },
  "693": {
    "Question": "How many cities are in Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT COUNT(?cities) AS ?citiesnum  WHERE{        ?cities a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;                yago:isLocatedIn yago:Republic_of_Ireland.  }",
    "Answer": 69
  },
  "694": {
    "Question": "Which settlement has the biggest population in the Republic of Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?pop  WHERE{        ?settlement a yago:wordnet_settlement_108672562;                yago:isLocatedIn yago:Republic_of_Ireland;                yagoinfobox:populationurban ?pop.  }  ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(replace(?pop, ,, )))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": 541
  },
  "695": {
    "Question": "How many hospitals does Cork city has?",
    "Query": "SELECT COUNT(?hospital) AS ?hospitalnum  WHERE{        ?hospital a yago:wordnet_hospital_103540595;                yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cork_(city)>.  }",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  "696": {
    "Question": "Which is the tallest mountain in Arkansas state?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mountain   WHERE {    ?mountain a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803.    ?mountain yago:isLocatedIn yago:Arkansas.    ?mountain yagoinfobox:elevationm ?height.   }   ORDER BY DESC(?height)    LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Mount_Ida,_Arkansas"
  },
  "697": {
    "Question": "Which is the longest river in Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?rivers   WHERE{    ?rivers a yago:wordnet_river_109411430;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:Ireland;    yagoinfobox:length ?length.   }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?length))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/River_Lee"
  },
  "698": {
    "Question": "What is the highest point of Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mountain   WHERE {    ?mountain a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803.    ?mountain yago:isLocatedIn yago:Ireland.    ?mountain yagoinfobox:elevationm ?height.   }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?height))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cnoc_na_Péiste"
  },
  "699": {
    "Question": "Which is the largest island in Ireland?",
    "Query": "select distinct ?x where { ?x rdf:type <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/wordnet_island_109316454>; yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Ireland>. }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "700": {
    "Question": "Which is the most populated city in California?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county    WHERE{    ?county a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:California;    yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?pop.   }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?pop))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/San_Diego"
  },
  "701": {
    "Question": "Which is the most populated county in United Kingdom?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county    WHERE{   ?county a yago:wordnet_county_108546183;   yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_Kingdom;   yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?pop.   }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?pop))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/City_of_London"
  },
  "702": {
    "Question": "How many counties are there in California?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?county) AS ?numCounties)   WHERE {    ?county a yago:wordnet_county_108546183.    ?county yago:isLocatedIn yago:California.   }",
    "Answer": 97
  },
  "703": {
    "Question": "How many stadiums there are in Liverpool?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?stadium) AS ?numStadia)   WHERE {    ?stadium a yago:wordnet_stadium_104295881.    ?stadium yago:isLocatedIn yago:Liverpool.   }",
    "Answer": 4
  },
  "704": {
    "Question": "Is Liverpool the largest city of the United Kingdom?",
    "Query": "ASK    WHERE {   ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_Kingdom;    yago:hasArea ?area.       yago:Liverpool yago:hasArea ?Larea.    FILTER NOT EXISTS{FILTER(?area>?Larea)}   }",
    "Answer": false
  },
  "705": {
    "Question": "Which is the oldest historic site of United Kingdom?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?historical_site   WHERE{    ?historical_site a yago:wordnet_memorial_103743902;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_Kingdom;    yagoinfobox:startdate ?date   }   ORDER BY ?date   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Watkin's_Tower"
  },
  "706": {
    "Question": "In which state is located the biggest mountain of the United States?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?state   WHERE {       ?state a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.       ?mountain a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803.    ?mountain yago:isLocatedIn ?state.    ?mountain yagoinfobox:elevationm ?height.       }   ORDER BY DESC(?height)   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/New_Hampshire"
  },
  "707": {
    "Question": "Which is the tallest building in the United States?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?building   WHERE{    ?building a yago:wordnet_building_102913152;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_States;    yagoinfobox:height ?height   }   ORDER BY DESC(?height)   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Middlebush_Reformed_Church"
  },
  "708": {
    "Question": "Which is the biggest city in Texas?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city   WHERE{    ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:Texas;    yago:hasArea ?area.   }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:float(?area))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Houston"
  },
  "709": {
    "Question": "What is the largest state by area in the USA?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?state   WHERE {    ?state a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.    ?state yago:hasArea ?area.   }   ORDER BY DESC(?area)   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Washington_Square_Park"
  },
  "710": {
    "Question": "Which is the most populated city in England?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city   WHERE{    ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:England;    yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?pop.   }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?pop))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Birmingham"
  },
  "711": {
    "Question": "What is the largest city in Scotland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city   WHERE {    ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735.    ?city yago:isLocatedIn yago:Scotland.    ?city yago:hasArea ?area.   }   ORDER BY DESC(?area)   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/St_Kilda,_Scotland"
  },
  "712": {
    "Question": "Which state of the USA has the most colleges?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?state    WHERE {    ?state a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.       ?university a yago:wordnet_university_108286569.     ?university yago:isLocatedIn ?state    }   GROUP BY ?state   ORDER BY DESC(COUNT(?university))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/California"
  },
  "713": {
    "Question": "Which is the most populated city in Ulster?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city    WHERE{    ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:Ulster;    yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?pop.   }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?pop))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Burtonport"
  },
  "714": {
    "Question": "How many universities are in the county of Donegal?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?university WHERE { ?university a yago:wordnet_university_108286569. ?university yago:isLocatedIn yago:Donegal }",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Burtonport"
  },
  "715": {
    "Question": "Which city in the UK has the most Hospitals?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city    WHERE {    ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735.    ?city yago:isLocatedIn yago:United_Kingdom.        ?hospital a yago:wordnet_hospital_103540595.    ?hospital yago:isLocatedIn ?city.   }   GROUP BY ?city   ORDER BY DESC(COUNT(?hospital))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/London"
  },
  "716": {
    "Question": "Which city in Ireland has the largest park?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city   WHERE {    ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:Ireland.       ?park a yago:wordnet_park_108615149;    yago:isLocatedIn ?city;    yago:hasArea ?area.       }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:float(?area))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Dublin"
  },
  "717": {
    "Question": "In which county is the tallest mountain of England?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?county   WHERE{   ?county a yago:wordnet_county_108546183.        ?mountain a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:England;    yagoinfobox:elevationm ?height.      ?mountain yago:isLocatedIn ?county.   }      ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?height))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Cumbria"
  },
  "718": {
    "Question": "Which is the third most populated city in the County of Waterford?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city    WHERE{   {SELECT DISTINCT ?city ?pop   WHERE{    ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:County_Waterford;    yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?pop.   }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?pop))   LIMIT 3}       ?city yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?pop.   }   ORDER BY ?pop   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Waterford"
  },
  "719": {
    "Question": "What is the 2nd tallest mountain in Arizona?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?mountain WHERE {   {SELECT DISTINCT ?mountain ?height   WHERE{    ?mountain a yago:wordnet_mountain_109359803;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:Arizona;    yagoinfobox:elevationm ?height   }      ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?height))      LIMIT 2}       ?mountain yagoinfobox:elevationm ?height.   }   ORDER BY ?height   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Oracle,_Arizona"
  },
  "720": {
    "Question": "Which is the most densely populated city in Scotland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city    WHERE{    ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:Scotland;    yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?pop.   }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?pop))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": "http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Edinburgh"
  },
  "721": {
    "Question": "Which is the tallest lighthouse in California?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?beacon  WHERE {      ?beacon a yago:wordnet_beacon_107264213.      ?beacon yago:isLocatedIn yago:California.      ?beacon yagoinfobox:height ?height.  }  ORDER BY DESC(?height)  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "722": {
    "Question": "Which is the oldest castle in Pennsylvania?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?castle ?date  WHERE {      ?castle a yago:wordnet_palace_103878066.      ?castle yagoinfobox:startdate ?date.      ?castle yago:isLocatedIn yago:Pennsylvania.  }  ORDER BY ?date  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "723": {
    "Question": "How many villages does Northern Ireland have?",
    "Query": "select (count(distinct ?x) as ?totalX)  where { ?x rdf:type <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/wordnet_village_108672738>; yago:isLocatedIn <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Northern_Ireland>. }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "724": {
    "Question": "How many villages are more than 50 kilometers away from another village?",
    "Query": "SELECT (COUNT(?village1) AS ?numVillages)  WHERE {        ?village1 a y2geoo:OSM_village.      ?village1 geo:hasGeometry ?v1Geom.      ?v1Geom geo:askWKT ?v1WKT.        NOT EXISTS {          ?village2 a y2geoo:OSM_village.          ?village2 geo:hasGeometry ?v2Geom.          ?v2Geom geo:asWKT ?v2WKT.            FILTER(geof:distance(?v1WKT, ?v2WKT, uom:meter) <= 50000).      }  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "725": {
    "Question": "Where is the oldest lighthouse in Northern Ireland?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?beacon ?location  WHERE {        ?beacon a yago:wordnet_beacon_107264213.      ?beacon yago:isLocatedIn yago:Northern_Ireland.      ?beacon yago:isLocatedIn ?location      ?beacon yagoinfobox:startdate ?date.  }  ORDER BY ?date  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "726": {
    "Question": "What is the largest park in Cambridge?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?park  WHERE {    yago:Cambridge geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom.    ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT.      ?park a y2geoo:OSM_park.    ?park geo:hasGeometry ?parkGeom.    ?parkGeom geo:asWKT ?parkWKT.      FILTER(strdf:within(?parkWKT, ?cWKT)).    }  ORDER BY DESC(strdf:area(?parkWKT))  LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "727": {
    "Question": "How many islands does Ireland have?",
    "Query": "SELECT COUNT(?island)  WHERE {      ?island a y2geoo:OSM_island.      ?island geo:hasGeometry ?islandGeom.      ?islandGeom geo:asWKT ?islandWKT.            yago:Ireland geo:hasGeometry ?irelandGeom.      ?irelandGeom geo:asWKT ?irelandkWKT.            FILTER(geof:sfWithin(?islandWKT, ?irelandWKT)).  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "728": {
    "Question": "What is the tallest building in Ireland ?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city  WHERE {      ?city a y2geoo:OSM_city.      ?city yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?cPop.      ?city geo:hasGeometry ?cGeom.      ?cGeom geo:asWKT ?cWKT.        <http://yago-knowledge.org/resource/Leeds,_Alabama> geo:hasGeometry ?lGeom.      ?lGeom geo:asWKT ?lWKT.        FILTER(xsd:integer(?cPop) < 1000000).  }    ORDER BY ASC(geof:distance(?cWKT, ?lWKT, uom:metre))",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "729": {
    "Question": "In which state is the largest forest in the United States?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?x ?height  WHERE{    ?x a     yago:wordnet_building_102913152;       yago:isLocatedIn yago:Ireland;       yagoinfobox:height ?height  }",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "730": {
    "Question": "What are the tourist site attractions that route 66 passes by?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?state   WHERE {       ?state a yago:wikicat_States_of_the_United_States.       ?forest a yago:wordnet_forest_108438533;    yago:isLocatedIn ?state;    yago:hasArea ?area.       }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:float(?area))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "731": {
    "Question": "Which is the biggest hospital in Los Angeles?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?hospital    WHERE{    ?hospital a yago:wordnet_hospital_103540595;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:Los_Angeles;     yago:hasArea ?area   }   ORDER BY DESC(?area)   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "732": {
    "Question": "Which is the tallest building in Downtown Los Angeles?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?building   WHERE{    ?building a yago:wordnet_building_102913152;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:Downtown_Los_Angeles;    yagoinfobox:height ?height   }   ORDER BY DESC(?height)   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  },
  "733": {
    "Question": "What is the most populated city in the county of Carlow?",
    "Query": "SELECT ?city    WHERE{    ?city a yago:wordnet_city_108524735;    yago:isLocatedIn yago:County_Carlow;    yagoinfobox:populationtotal ?pop.   }   ORDER BY DESC(xsd:integer(?pop))   LIMIT 1",
    "Answer": null
  }
}